entity,cluster,topic,article_id,reddit_id,parent_id,entity_type,sum_sentiment,sum_pos,sum_neg,weight_pos,weight_neg,weight,timestamp
"""](https://twitter.com/Acyn/status/1504301184663764995",4,9,[1787828],['i42yump'],['i42uebt'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-09T21:05:10']
"""](https://www.reuters.com",0,2,[2292360],['i6x1oh0'],['i6wn8qc'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-01T15:58:57']
"""oh",6,1,[1480953],['i3j7vwb'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T20:03:03']
& Germany,3,8,[425465],['i2ioalj'],['i2fv5sk'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T02:48:19']
+44273,1,7,[2041615],['i4wmptf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-16T01:36:23']
-Putin,4,6,[2155952],['i5u1wun'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-23T03:03:51']
100%](https://ground.news,4,1,[2346100],['i70iok9'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.8316,0.0,-0.8316,0,1,1,['2022-05-02T11:07:05']
2/25/2022,4,8,[494236],"['i2ozkt1', 'i2ozt6b']","['i2o79f6', 'i2ns0tg']",['GPE'],-0.8808,0.0,-0.8808,0,2,2,"['2022-03-30T09:10:46', '2022-03-30T09:14:11']"
9/+1096,4,7,[1587993],"['i3n9v9z', 'i3n9v1f']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-06T16:45:39', '2022-04-06T16:45:41']"
"> gdi

yes",1,2,[704263],['i33kc4b'],['i32boza'],['PERSON'],0.5411,0.5411,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T11:55:16']
A.D.,6,1,[1480953],['i3jv8qr'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T22:36:26']
ABC,3,8,[425465],['i2gbiux'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-28T16:14:53']
ABC,4,9,[1787828],['i43lzz7'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.2944,0.0,-0.2944,0,1,1,['2022-04-09T23:58:45']
ABC News,1,7,"[2053825, 2350926]","['i7mhsot', 'i4zst4n', 'i4zsygl', 'i4zr9x5']",['0'],['ORG'],-1.9457999999999998,0.0,-1.9457999999999998,0,3,3,"['2022-05-07T01:08:22', '2022-04-16T19:28:45', '2022-04-16T19:40:27', '2022-04-16T19:41:32']"
ABC News,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.31389999999999996,0.7906,-0.4767,1,1,2,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
ABC News Supreme Court,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.7096,0.7096,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
ABUNDANTLY,6,1,[1480953],['i3kcfan'],['0'],['NORP'],0.9198,0.9198,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T00:43:19']
AF,7,2,[1279574],['i3d3gyg'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.7269,0.0,-0.7269,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T15:34:26']
AFAIK,6,8,[2169477],['i5ynjhp'],['i5yjzx1'],['ORG'],-0.5106,0.0,-0.5106,0,1,1,['2022-04-24T04:12:57']
AG,2,4,[800487],"['i313a2f', 'i3122ry', 'i317g5o', 'i33wrla', 'i3202gw', 'i34i6hh', 'i31jy0t', 'i34l56p', 'i35e38c', 'i310mft', 'i31s3n8']","['i30na8k', 'i34i6hh', 'i33klgy', '0', 'i30pb0v']",['ORG'],1.2532,2.5140000000000002,-1.2608000000000001,7,4,11,"['2022-04-02T17:03:12', '2022-04-02T01:00:21', '2022-04-01T20:42:10', '2022-04-01T23:53:13', '2022-04-01T20:23:26', '2022-04-02T13:56:58', '2022-04-01T20:33:38', '2022-04-02T16:42:11', '2022-04-01T22:46:57', '2022-04-02T20:48:15', '2022-04-01T21:11:55']"
AK,2,7,[1138187],"['i38c9z6', 'i3997x6']","['0', 'i38xi6w']",['ORG'],-0.5256,0.0,-0.5256,0,1,1,"['2022-04-03T19:04:03', '2022-04-03T15:15:43']"
AKA,5,6,[2074813],['i57b65u'],['i55vha6'],['ORG'],0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-18T12:53:09']
ALMS,4,6,[2062426],['i51t17q'],['i51rxlv'],['ORG'],0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17T05:33:14']
ALWAYS,4,9,[1918680],['i474ww1'],['i464icl'],['ORG'],-0.7579,0.0,-0.7579,0,1,1,['2022-04-10T19:01:02']
AMA,1,7,[2053825],['i4zqho7'],['0'],['ORG'],0.5972,0.5972,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-16T19:22:41']
AMNESTY,6,1,[1480953],['i3n961b'],['0'],['ORG'],0.8947,0.8947,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T16:41:18']
AMP,1,0,[2333865],['i7cjhbh'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-05-04T21:51:57']
AMP,4,6,[2155952],['i5v8rup'],['i5v8qqd'],['ORG'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-23T11:49:45']
AMP,5,8,[2275096],['i6founi'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-27T18:51:25']
ANYONE,6,1,[1480953],"['i3k6rj1', 'i3kugoy']","['0', 'i3iywvg']",['ORG'],-0.0516,0.0,-0.0516,0,1,1,"['2022-04-06T02:59:12', '2022-04-06T00:01:02']"
AOC,6,1,[1480953],['i3n961b'],['0'],['ORG'],0.8947,0.8947,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T16:41:18']
AOE2,4,6,[2062426],['i549vt4'],['i52e1ys'],['ORG'],0.4199,0.4199,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17T19:33:33']
AP,1,0,"[2063107, 2242251]","['i5ff7fm', 'i4uu6nd']",['0'],['ORG'],-1.5775000000000001,0.0,-1.5775000000000001,0,2,2,"['2022-04-15T17:32:16', '2022-04-20T02:00:34']"
AP,1,2,[2325276],['i76fuf4'],['0'],['ORG'],0.5423,0.5423,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-03T16:34:47']
AP,1,7,[2053825],['i4yi48l'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.7506,0.0,-0.7506,0,1,1,['2022-04-16T14:01:31']
AP,2,4,[800487],"['i33klgy', 'i351ayh']","['0', 'i34ffot']",['ORG'],-0.5267,0.0,-0.5267,0,1,1,"['2022-04-02T19:05:13', '2022-04-02T11:58:17']"
AP,2,5,[413890],['i2ghiyk'],['i2g90ox'],['ORG'],-0.1316,0.0,-0.1316,0,1,1,['2022-03-28T16:54:29']
AP,3,8,[425465],['i2fvkgj'],['0'],['ORG'],0.3321,0.3321,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28T14:24:49']
AP,4,0,[2150320],['i5shzng'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.8176,0.0,-0.8176,0,1,1,['2022-04-22T19:56:33']
AP,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
AP,4,9,"[2042107, 1258901]","['i4m64gh', 'i3cikkq', 'i3cikc6', 'i3cikzt']",['0'],['ORG'],-2.0631,0.0,-2.0631,0,4,4,"['2022-04-04T13:02:53', '2022-04-04T13:02:50', '2022-04-13T20:58:20', '2022-04-04T13:02:59']"
AP,6,1,[1480953],['i3k3x20'],['i3k3snj'],['ORG'],-0.3252,0.0,-0.3252,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T23:39:59']
APC,4,6,[2062426],['i53fn2u'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-17T16:02:35']
APR,6,1,[1480953],"['i3mdxv9', 'i3kntsf']","['i3j4fs0', '0']",['ORG'],0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-06T02:07:09', '2022-04-06T13:12:52']"
AR,2,3,[1092237],['i34qtsm'],['0'],['GPE'],0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T17:43:39']
ARD,4,9,[1258901],"['i3cikkq', 'i3cikc6', 'i3cikzt']",['0'],['ORG'],-0.8196,0.0,-0.8196,0,3,3,"['2022-04-04T13:02:53', '2022-04-04T13:02:50', '2022-04-04T13:02:59']"
ASO,6,1,[1480953],['i3l4ji2'],['i3kg5tx'],['ORG'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-06T04:28:18']
ASUS,1,7,[1963245],['i4a5gwh'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-04-11T11:39:21']
AZOV,1,2,[2325276],['i75xkes'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.2732,0.0,-0.2732,0,1,1,['2022-05-03T14:35:24']
A_Tmeta,1,0,[1860324],['i427hkf'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-09T17:51:11']
A_Tmeta,4,2,[1878824],['i42gbcg'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-09T18:51:24']
Abdullah,1,7,[2041615],['i4xzb5p'],['i4wk1r6'],['PERSON'],0.8284,0.8284,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-16T10:46:38']
Abrams,1,1,[734285],['i2z93d1'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.7494,0.0,-0.7494,0,1,1,['2022-04-01T13:09:21']
Abrams,2,3,[340497],['i2e65q0'],['i2aoj0o'],['PERSON'],0.8271,0.8271,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28T03:04:03']
Abu Ghraib,4,0,[1093474],"['i39d68i', 'i39nuxg', 'i399thr']","['i37ho6s', 'i37d0t2', 'i39ib79']",['PERSON'],-0.7845,0.0,-0.7845,0,1,1,"['2022-04-03T19:30:34', '2022-04-03T19:08:07', '2022-04-03T20:44:41']"
Acadamy,8,9,[1811789],['i3y30us'],['i3y0h0o'],['ORG'],0.3818,0.3818,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-08T20:15:35']
Academi,4,9,[1918680],['i47zplr'],['i464icl'],['GPE'],0.4497,0.4497,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-10T22:39:05']
Academy,8,0,"[552242, 825466]","['i31oh98', 'i31uma2', 'i31ou1b', 'i2s4kg9', 'i321r2z', 'i321dwb', 'i325jxd']","['i31oh98', 'i31rzay', '0', 'i31tjf7']",['ORG'],1.6663999999999999,1.9986,-0.3322,4,1,5,"['2022-03-30T23:34:07', '2022-04-02T01:46:46', '2022-04-02T00:14:23', '2022-04-02T01:11:24', '2022-04-01T23:23:26', '2022-04-01T23:26:19', '2022-04-02T01:14:33']"
Academy,8,9,[1811789],['i3y71dj'],['i3y4cqw'],['ORG'],-0.7184,0.0,-0.7184,0,1,1,['2022-04-08T20:42:01']
Academy Awards,8,0,[552242],['i2s4kg9'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-30T23:34:07']
Adam Schiff,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.5267,0.5267,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Adam Smith's,7,4,[757828],['i3d2hbz'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-04T15:27:46']
Adams,5,2,[2313930],['i6nqlzq'],['i6nfh1i'],['PERSON'],0.7351,0.7351,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-29T12:41:30']
Adenoid Hynkel,9,2,[1936012],['i47upw8'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-10T22:02:30']
Adin,4,0,[1093474],['i39zj4j'],['i380fx9'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T22:08:47']
Administration,6,1,[1480953],['i3ko6lk'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.4927,0.0,-0.4927,0,1,1,['2022-04-06T02:09:49']
Administration,7,6,[623485],['i2v8xi3'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.2732,0.0,-0.2732,0,1,1,['2022-03-31T16:45:42']
Afghan,4,0,[824475],['i2m7ljr'],['i2l4ilf'],['NORP'],0.0258,0.0258,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T21:10:19']
Afghanistan,1,0,[2279161],['i6vsdr8'],['i6vd0kc'],['GPE'],-0.9129,0.0,-0.9129,0,1,1,['2022-05-01T07:48:00']
Afghanistan,1,2,[704263],"['i33oc5e', 'i34cabf', 'i33u6ya', 'i33vx2c', 'i33gkzy']","['i32buzn', '0', 'i33vsmm']",['GPE'],-0.8799999999999999,0.3612,-1.2412,1,2,3,"['2022-04-02T11:09:20', '2022-04-02T15:58:37', '2022-04-02T13:34:46', '2022-04-02T13:49:44', '2022-04-02T12:38:44']"
Afghanistan,1,7,[1907918],['i44sy29'],['i44ql83'],['GPE'],0.7248,0.7248,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-10T06:12:57']
Afghanistan,2,5,[413890],['i2ggsb8'],['i2g7m5w'],['GPE'],0.4118,0.4118,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28T16:49:34']
Afghanistan,4,0,[824475],['i2l4ilf'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.6705,0.0,-0.6705,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T17:03:29']
Afghanistan,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['GPE'],0.6124,0.6124,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
Afghanistan,4,6,"[2155952, 1296929, 2062426, 1251068]","['i50dy9i', 'i3d269b', 'i50n49v', 'i5vfvq1', 'i51nqmr', 'i4zctg3', 'i502cno']","['i50dy9i', 'i3cfg61', 'i4zs9b3', 'i4ytbbf', '0']",['GPE'],-1.3266999999999998,2.0133,-3.34,7,6,13,"['2022-04-16T22:18:43', '2022-04-17T04:36:12', '2022-04-04T15:25:41', '2022-04-23T13:00:04', '2022-04-16T20:51:48', '2022-04-16T17:41:21', '2022-04-16T23:27:45']"
Afghanistan,4,7,[1587993],"['i3n9v9z', 'i3n9v1f']",['0'],['GPE'],-2.2296,0.0,-2.2296,0,4,4,"['2022-04-06T16:45:39', '2022-04-06T16:45:41']"
Afghanistan,4,9,[1918680],['i48xdoe'],['i464icl'],['GPE'],-0.2424,0.0,-0.2424,0,1,1,['2022-04-11T03:03:07']
African,4,0,"[2150320, 1093474]","['i38u54m', 'i5r37k4']","['0', 'i37d0t2']",['NORP'],-0.36979999999999996,0.0,-0.36979999999999996,0,2,2,"['2022-04-03T17:20:25', '2022-04-22T14:22:01']"
African,4,9,[1694081],['i3tpl1j'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.765,0.0,-0.765,0,1,1,['2022-04-07T22:49:38']
African,7,4,[757828],['i3jkesd'],['i3azf1r'],['NORP'],-0.5423,0.0,-0.5423,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T21:21:07']
African American,2,3,[1092237],['i3j00n4'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.5325,0.0,-0.5325,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T19:13:30']
Aghan,4,0,[824475],['i2l4ilf'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.6705,0.0,-0.6705,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T17:03:29']
Ahahahah,6,1,[1480953],['i3l66ug'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T04:44:42']
Aidvantage,6,1,[1480953],['i3krg9p'],['i3j6i3w'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T02:35:00']
Air Force,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3eggn8'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T20:47:32']
AirBnb,5,6,[2074813],['i579vld'],['i53nm17'],['ORG'],-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-04-18T12:41:30']
Aka GFYS,2,4,[800487],['i316241'],['i3122ry'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T21:01:57']
Al Gross,2,7,[1138187],['i37xivd'],['i360eq9'],['PERSON'],-0.4588,0.0,-0.4588,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T13:17:19']
Al Gross(2020,2,7,[1138187],['i37xivd'],['i360eq9'],['PERSON'],0.0258,0.0258,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T13:17:19']
Alaska,2,7,[1138187],"['i39rluf', 'i362y5w', 'i37xivd', 'i36fgzn', 'i35h2nb', 'i360eq9', 'i366j9v']","['i360eq9', 'i38c9z6', '0', 'i366x0u']",['GPE'],0.7307,1.8407,-1.11,3,2,5,"['2022-04-02T21:11:49', '2022-04-03T13:17:19', '2022-04-03T02:53:20', '2022-04-03T00:09:35', '2022-04-03T01:39:16', '2022-04-03T21:11:33', '2022-04-02T23:48:09']"
Alaskan,2,7,[1138187],"['i38fek2', 'i36omt5']","['i36omt5', '0']",['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-03T04:13:58', '2022-04-03T15:38:18']"
Aldi,7,4,[757828],['i3c25tb'],['i3blrh3'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T10:12:23']
Alexander Lipstickonapigov,9,2,[1936012],['i4andn6'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-11T14:07:02']
Alexandria,4,8,[494236],"['i2mcug4', 'i2og8ka']",['i2lwyze'],['GPE'],0.5849,0.5849,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-03-29T21:41:26', '2022-03-30T04:57:49']"
Algeria,3,6,[1655560],"['i3tijlp', 'i3rakss']",['0'],['GPE'],-0.6582,0.0,-0.6582,0,2,2,"['2022-04-07T13:04:15', '2022-04-07T22:00:52']"
Aliens,1,0,[2333865],['i7b73fp'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-04T16:37:35']
Alinaghi,2,5,[413890],['i2g90ox'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.2732,0.0,-0.2732,0,1,1,['2022-03-28T15:58:03']
Allied,1,0,[2241438],['i605yuo'],['i6042z1'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-24T14:31:58']
Allied,4,9,[1787828],['i42s3it'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.6486,0.0,-0.6486,0,1,1,['2022-04-09T20:15:39']
Ally,6,1,[1480953],['i4g7fd1'],['i3kconz'],['PERSON'],0.6124,0.6124,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-12T16:55:03']
AmErIca,5,6,[2074813],['i5488xp'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T19:21:52']
Amadou Diallo,5,2,[2313930],['i6nqlzq'],['i6nfh1i'],['PERSON'],-0.9393,0.0,-0.9393,0,1,1,['2022-04-29T12:41:30']
Amazon,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3fro8n'],['i3fdwg7'],['ORG'],0.9936,0.9936,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-05T02:08:39']
America,0,2,[2292360],['i6ym7r2'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.0572,0.0,-0.0572,0,1,1,['2022-05-01T22:49:43']
America,1,2,[2212524],['i6a9ds2'],['i699044'],['GPE'],0.6697,0.6697,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-26T16:32:06']
America,1,7,"[1907918, 2041615]","['i44sy29', 'i4y8umh']","['i4wy8kj', 'i44ql83']",['GPE'],0.998,0.998,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-16T12:39:01', '2022-04-10T06:12:57']"
America,2,3,[340497],['i2glewe'],['i2gknni'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-28T17:20:24']
America,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
America,2,6,[898818],['i36jzrd'],['0'],['GPE'],0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T03:31:51']
America,4,0,[1093474],"['i3992tx', 'i39d68i', 'i39908b']","['i38mlt3', '0', 'i37d0t2']",['GPE'],-0.7845,0.0,-0.7845,0,1,1,"['2022-04-03T19:30:34', '2022-04-03T19:03:04', '2022-04-03T19:02:33']"
America,4,4,[2024078],['i4q48gf'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.2846,0.0,-0.2846,0,1,1,['2022-04-14T17:25:21']
America,4,6,"[1296929, 2062426, 1251068]","['i3g89mi', 'i502cno', 'i4z4yvq']","['i4zs9b3', '0', 'i4yl98l']",['GPE'],-2.0121,0.0,-2.0121,0,6,6,"['2022-04-16T20:51:48', '2022-04-16T16:45:32', '2022-04-05T04:24:30']"
America,4,9,"[1918680, 1024713]","['i3a3yof', 'i48qxgg']","['i39fihu', '0']",['GPE'],-0.0635,0.4939,-0.5574,1,1,2,"['2022-04-03T22:41:26', '2022-04-11T02:10:11']"
America,5,6,[2074813],['i54ilwk'],['i548bog'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T20:36:21']
America,6,1,[1480953],"['i3ju43p', 'i3ouwo5', 'i3lzfep']","['i3lf67s', '0']",['GPE'],0.08370000000000011,0.6104,-0.5267,1,1,2,"['2022-04-06T22:46:14', '2022-04-05T22:28:21', '2022-04-06T10:58:47']"
America,6,2,[2235430],['i6fcnig'],['i6fbr4q'],['GPE'],-0.3182,0.0,-0.3182,0,1,1,['2022-04-27T17:30:13']
America,6,8,"[1679152, 2169477]","['i5ykds6', 'i3sdkor', 'i5ykmr2']","['i3scewa', '0', 'i5ykds6']",['GPE'],-0.0388,0.3182,-0.357,1,1,2,"['2022-04-24T03:43:06', '2022-04-07T17:35:33', '2022-04-24T03:45:24']"
America,7,4,[757828],['i3ctr24'],['i3bngqz'],['GPE'],-0.8028,0.0,-0.8028,0,2,2,['2022-04-04T14:27:42']
America,7,6,[623485],['i2v33vg'],['i2uzcx0'],['GPE'],-0.743,0.0,-0.743,0,1,1,['2022-03-31T16:09:07']
American,0,2,[2292360],"['i6yj681', 'i6yj8qn', 'i6ym7r2']","['i6yj681', '0']",['NORP'],-0.43390000000000006,0.5539000000000001,-0.9878000000000001,2,3,5,"['2022-05-01T22:27:22', '2022-05-01T22:49:43', '2022-05-01T22:26:51']"
American,1,7,[2041615],['i4yh4y6'],['i4wy8kj'],['NORP'],-0.7332,0.0,-0.7332,0,1,1,['2022-04-16T13:53:27']
American,1,9,[2208607],['i5iwrn1'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.5859,0.0,-0.5859,0,1,1,['2022-04-20T20:02:56']
American,2,3,[1092237],['i3kv03c'],['0'],['NORP'],0.4019,0.4019,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T03:03:32']
American,2,4,[800487],"['i33klgy', 'i389seu', 'i38956n']","['0', 'i33wrla']",['NORP'],-0.09899999999999998,0.7075,-0.8065,3,2,5,"['2022-04-03T14:52:27', '2022-04-02T11:58:17', '2022-04-03T14:57:20']"
American,2,6,[898818],['i356wq5'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.3182,0.0,-0.3182,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T19:51:45']
American,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['NORP'],0.4207,0.4207,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
American,4,0,[1093474],"['i39d3yt', 'i37kgdi', 'i39nuxg']","['i37emmj', 'i37d0t2', 'i39ib79']",['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-03T19:30:09', '2022-04-03T20:44:41', '2022-04-03T10:51:32']"
American,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['NORP'],0.03510000000000002,0.6117,-0.5766,2,1,3,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
American,4,4,[2024078],['i4ox712'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T12:25:49']
American,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]","['i3dj2v2', 'i3e9stc', 'i3e7cuh', 'i3dmgq5', 'i3hh56g', 'i3ee1c2', 'i3eveur', 'i3g0zlb', 'i3hc8w2', 'i3cg0k7', 'i3ehxbk', 'i3e5cp3']","['i3czxyk', 'i3e4u0x', '0', 'i3cfo2u', 'i3cub6u']",['NORP'],-7.916,1.4792,-9.3952,8,24,32,"['2022-04-04T20:05:42', '2022-04-04T17:37:38', '2022-04-04T19:50:26', '2022-04-05T13:04:46', '2022-04-04T19:37:56', '2022-04-04T22:26:13', '2022-04-05T12:23:47', '2022-04-04T20:56:39', '2022-04-04T17:15:49', '2022-04-04T20:32:18', '2022-04-05T03:20:32', '2022-04-04T12:40:41']"
American,4,7,[2023465],['i4t7ddc'],['i4sh1gi'],['NORP'],0.9331,0.9331,0.0,2,0,2,['2022-04-15T09:00:30']
American,4,9,"[1918680, 1024713, 1787828]","['i39j3qt', 'i42tuxe', 'i42yump', 'i404wzt', 'i47zplr']","['i39fihu', 'i401466', 'i464icl', 'i42s3it', 'i42uebt']",['NORP'],-0.6019,1.4414,-2.0433,2,3,5,"['2022-04-09T06:13:25', '2022-04-10T22:39:05', '2022-04-03T20:11:17', '2022-04-09T20:28:32', '2022-04-09T21:05:10']"
American,5,2,[2313930],['i6nfdx8'],['i6newt6'],['NORP'],0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-29T10:48:57']
American,6,1,[1480953],"['i3l2mhb', 'i3ouwo5', 'i3k4b8z', 'i3k9wvo', 'i3ksnza', 'i3kaxwv', 'i3m5otl', 'i3mdxv9', 'i3mx6bl', 'i3mfilk']","['i3j4fs0', 'i3iqdoo', '0', 'i3jpcze']",['NORP'],-0.24679999999999996,1.2247000000000001,-1.4715,3,3,6,"['2022-04-06T00:32:17', '2022-04-06T22:46:14', '2022-04-06T12:03:34', '2022-04-06T13:24:37', '2022-04-05T23:42:54', '2022-04-06T15:24:47', '2022-04-06T13:12:52', '2022-04-06T00:24:33', '2022-04-06T04:10:02', '2022-04-06T02:44:43']"
American,6,2,[2235430],"['i6fbr4q', 'i6h0r9j']",['0'],['NORP'],-1.2085,0.0,-1.2085,0,2,2,"['2022-04-28T00:30:08', '2022-04-27T17:24:24']"
American,7,4,[757828],['i3ctr24'],['i3bngqz'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T14:27:42']
American,7,6,[623485],"['i2vfln8', 'i2v6bhw']",['0'],['NORP'],0.7096,0.7096,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-03-31T17:28:05', '2022-03-31T16:29:23']"
American,9,3,[678224],"['i2z0yyd', 'i3696l9']",['0'],['NORP'],0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-01T11:59:52', '2022-04-03T02:01:40']"
American Oligarchs,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3e79hw'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T19:49:52']
Americans,0,1,[2021946],['i4h15od'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,['2022-04-12T20:01:04']
Americans,0,2,[2292360],"['i6x6qrx', 'i6wnou0', 'i6yj8qn']","['i6yj681', '0', 'i6x2ze0']",['NORP'],-0.924,0.4404,-1.3644,1,2,3,"['2022-05-01T22:27:22', '2022-05-01T16:35:04', '2022-05-01T14:12:05']"
Americans,1,7,"[2345105, 2041615]","['i50k4jc', 'i7k2zo0']","['i7j0hm4', 'i502s95']",['NORP'],-1.1368,0.0,-1.1368,0,2,2,"['2022-05-06T14:21:19', '2022-04-16T23:04:56']"
Americans,2,3,"[340497, 1092237]","['i36f086', 'i2alcjc']",['0'],['NORP'],-0.1367,0.34,-0.4767,1,1,2,"['2022-04-03T02:49:29', '2022-03-27T08:58:39']"
Americans,2,4,[800487],['i34y4pc'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.7906,0.0,-0.7906,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T18:38:55']
Americans,4,0,[1093474],"['i39fnzi', 'i399mhe', 'i399thr']","['i37ho6s', 'i378925', 'i37kj5s']",['NORP'],-1.2243,0.0,-1.2243,0,2,2,"['2022-04-03T19:08:07', '2022-04-03T19:06:49', '2022-04-03T19:47:36']"
Americans,4,1,[2346100],"['i6yyv27', 'i70iok9', 'i6yz41b']",['0'],['NORP'],-1.3744,0.329,-1.7034,2,3,5,"['2022-05-02T00:33:22', '2022-05-02T11:07:05', '2022-05-02T00:35:26']"
Americans,4,6,"[1296929, 2062426, 1251068]","['i50dy9i', 'i55nk0s', 'i3clwxe', 'i50ju1l', 'i3eygru']","['i3errs2', 'i3cfg61', '0', 'i4yl98l']",['NORP'],1.8216999999999999,4.1653,-2.3436,7,4,11,"['2022-04-04T13:29:56', '2022-04-16T22:18:43', '2022-04-04T22:47:40', '2022-04-16T23:02:47', '2022-04-18T01:42:56']"
Americans,4,9,"[1918680, 1787828, 1276661]","['i42yump', 'i3gta2m', 'i47b8cl']","['i464icl', 'i3dvdum', 'i42uebt']",['NORP'],0.7187000000000001,0.8718000000000001,-0.1531,2,1,3,"['2022-04-10T19:44:57', '2022-04-09T21:05:10', '2022-04-05T08:39:58']"
Americans,5,6,[2074813],['i57f1qt'],['i57dla6'],['NORP'],-0.2244,0.0,-0.2244,0,1,1,['2022-04-18T13:25:52']
Americans,6,1,[1480953],"['i3jsmsg', 'i3k3ovt', 'i3iy2a9', 'i3kcc4z', 'i3j2tku', 'i3jo151', 'i3j47or', 'i3khbdm', 'i3lx50e', 'i3lrv6j', 'i3l91oj', 'i3m5otl', 'i3jbd19', 'i3oiqfr', 'i3lerd2', 'i3kcxj3', 'i3jtlky', 'i3q6x2m']","['i3iqdoo', 'i3j73by', 'i3jvd3j', 'i3j47or', 'i3izddy', '0', 'i3jtlky', 'i3isusl']",['NORP'],-3.0153,2.9596,-5.974900000000001,7,12,19,"['2022-04-06T09:20:19', '2022-04-06T06:19:46', '2022-04-06T00:42:40', '2022-04-06T01:19:44', '2022-04-06T10:31:26', '2022-04-05T20:24:26', '2022-04-07T05:20:34', '2022-04-05T19:00:54', '2022-04-06T12:03:34', '2022-04-05T22:17:51', '2022-04-05T19:31:22', '2022-04-05T21:45:09', '2022-04-05T19:40:15', '2022-04-06T05:13:56', '2022-04-06T21:22:49', '2022-04-06T00:47:06', '2022-04-05T22:24:40', '2022-04-05T23:38:17']"
Americans,6,2,[2235430],"['i6f9u28', 'i6hm40s', 'i6fnwtu', 'i6fiy9n']","['i6f9u28', '0']",['NORP'],-5.3822,0.0,-5.3822,0,6,6,"['2022-04-28T03:11:32', '2022-04-27T18:45:17', '2022-04-27T18:12:15', '2022-04-27T17:11:55']"
Americans,6,8,[1679152],['i3scewa'],['0'],['NORP'],0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-07T17:28:10']
Americans,6,9,[623417],"['i2vhbtp', 'i2vjjxn']",['0'],['NORP'],1.9468,1.9468,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-03-31T17:39:06', '2022-03-31T17:53:02']"
Americans,7,6,[623485],['i2x50bw'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.7579,0.0,-0.7579,0,1,1,['2022-04-01T00:18:33']
Amsterdam,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3gpwyl'],['0'],['GPE'],0.7116,0.7116,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-05T07:52:16']
Amy Schneider,6,9,[676909],['i2xgdqk'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.8885,0.8885,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-01T01:43:40']
Ancient,6,8,[476817],['i2rht2i'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.4419,0.0,-0.4419,0,1,1,['2022-03-30T20:50:33']
Andrei Sakharov,4,9,[1258901],['i3ckqts'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.1779,0.0,-0.1779,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T13:20:41']
Anja Osmon,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
Anna Prokopiuk,4,9,[2150382],['i4jgg29'],['i4f0r7p'],['PERSON'],0.5499,0.5499,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-13T08:05:48']
Ant&oacute;nio Guterres,1,7,[2262917],"['i6nt096', 'i6nt20g']",['0'],['PERSON'],-1.8372,0.0,-1.8372,0,2,2,"['2022-04-29T13:01:38', '2022-04-29T13:02:02']"
Anthony Fauci,0,2,[2292360],['i6wxca0'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-01T15:26:42']
Anthony Noto,6,1,[1480953],['i3k18ex'],['i3iszrp'],['PERSON'],0.5267,0.5267,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-05T23:20:07']
Anti-Aircraft,4,9,[1787828],['i3yi2ke'],['i3ygjx8'],['ORG'],-0.5859,0.0,-0.5859,0,1,1,['2022-04-08T21:56:37']
Anti-EU,4,6,[2023525],['i4lm8uo'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-13T18:45:01']
Antioch,4,8,[494236],"['i2mcug4', 'i2og8ka']",['i2lwyze'],['GPE'],0.5849,0.5849,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-03-29T21:41:26', '2022-03-30T04:57:49']"
Anton Shkaplerov,7,9,[502563],"['i2tqti2', 'i2tqszr']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-03-31T09:02:48', '2022-03-31T09:03:00']"
Antonov,1,7,[2345105],['i7jgs39'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.4939,0.0,-0.4939,0,1,1,['2022-05-06T11:11:36']
Archimedes,4,6,[2155952],['i5tvocu'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-23T02:12:11']
Are Merkel,4,2,[796098],['i2z9rd5'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T13:14:34']
Arkansan,2,3,[1092237],['i3h7sa1'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T11:41:51']
Arkansas,0,2,[2292360],['i6yj8qn'],['i6yj681'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-01T22:27:22']
Arkansas,2,3,[1092237],"['i3eek8k', 'i448062', 'i37on5f', 'i37mmet']",['0'],['GPE'],-1.3554,0.0,-1.3554,0,2,2,"['2022-04-04T20:35:34', '2022-04-10T02:58:47', '2022-04-03T11:45:32', '2022-04-03T11:20:28']"
Armenia,4,9,[1787828],"['i4057nd', 'i3zmm87']",['0'],['GPE'],0.0516,0.0516,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-09T03:09:08', '2022-04-09T06:16:53']"
Armenia & Azerbaijan,4,9,[1787828],['i3zaqa1'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-09T01:32:25']
Army,1,2,[704263],['i33t3mf'],['i32ef6x'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T13:24:58']
Army,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['ORG'],0.5859,0.5859,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
Army,4,6,[2062426],['i4yy56y'],['i4yxaqc'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-16T15:58:04']
Army,4,9,[1787828],['i403o0d'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-09T05:58:40']
Army,6,1,[1480953],['i3ky2wh'],['i3j6b17'],['ORG'],0.8415,0.8415,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T03:29:22']
Army,9,3,[678224],['i2xp8pq'],['i2xl6sl'],['ORG'],0.374,0.374,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-01T02:52:40']
Army Col,4,6,[2062426],['i5m8m5v'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.7003,0.0,-0.7003,0,1,1,['2022-04-21T13:59:36']
Art Thou,4,6,[2062426],['i51jldx'],['i51aj7a'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T03:56:29']
Article,0,1,[2021946],['i4g2xd8'],['i4fz11i'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-12T16:27:29']
Articles,1,0,[2333865],['i7cjg48'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-04T21:51:44']
Articles,4,7,[2023465],['i4ozz44'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T12:49:39']
Aryan,2,8,[528443],['i2rzupt'],['i2rumq8'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-30T22:58:06']
Asian,0,2,[2292360],['i6wko4m'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.6597,0.0,-0.6597,0,1,1,['2022-05-01T13:46:23']
Asian,4,4,[2024078],['i4ox712'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T12:25:49']
Asians,4,6,[2155952],['i5uhhik'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.6808,0.0,-0.6808,0,1,1,['2022-04-23T05:41:03']
Assad,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3d269b'],['i3cfg61'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T15:25:41']
Assembly,4,6,[1549013],['i2z3c28'],['i2yjyk4'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T12:21:26']
Associate Justice Clarence Thomas,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.8934,0.8934,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
Associate Supreme Court,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.7906,0.7906,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
Associated Press,1,0,[2063107],['i4uuq0i'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-15T17:35:49']
Associated Press,4,2,[1141524],['i37zla5'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T13:35:48']
Associated Press,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3cq224'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T14:01:26']
Associated Press,7,8,[1478141],['i3ile9x'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T17:36:14']
Asus,4,4,[2024078],['i4p3xzj'],['i4ox712'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T13:21:15']
Atgm,4,6,[1549013],['i31d5ul'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T21:54:19']
Attack,6,1,[1480953],['i3j91eo'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.2023,0.2023,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-05T20:10:05']
Attica,4,9,[2042107],['i4m3sz9'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.5984,0.0,-0.5984,0,1,1,['2022-04-13T20:43:20']
Augustus,4,9,[1787828],['i3zv0sg'],['i3zuof5'],['PERSON'],-0.9432,0.0,-0.9432,0,1,1,['2022-04-09T04:25:16']
Austin,4,7,[1470385],"['i3iya3j', 'i3iyady']",['0'],['PERSON'],1.5928,1.5928,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-05T19:02:20', '2022-04-05T19:02:17']"
Australia,1,7,[1011081],['i39b6lc'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.6808,0.0,-0.6808,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T19:17:09']
Australia,4,1,[578564],"['i25wfkr', 'i26iiwp']",['0'],['GPE'],1.4275,1.4275,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-03-26T11:19:53', '2022-03-26T06:03:32']"
Australia,4,6,[723811],['i2y5gyk'],['i2y4prk'],['GPE'],0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-01T05:23:57']
Australia,6,1,[1480953],"['i3m7djv', 'i3lu02e', 'i3lzecl']",['i3j4fs0'],['GPE'],0.3818,0.743,-0.3612,1,1,2,"['2022-04-06T09:50:12', '2022-04-06T12:19:04', '2022-04-06T10:58:27']"
Australian,1,7,[2041615],['i4wmptf'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.5106,0.0,-0.5106,0,1,1,['2022-04-16T01:36:23']
Australian,4,1,[578564],"['i25wfkr', 'i25vtw2']",['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-03-26T05:55:37', '2022-03-26T06:03:32']"
Austrian,4,2,[1878824],['i4299f6'],['0'],['NORP'],0.959,0.959,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-09T18:03:00']
Austrian,4,6,[2062426],['i528r10'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.0727000000000001,0.5267,-0.5994,1,1,2,['2022-04-17T09:00:42']
Austrian,4,9,[1983397],"['i4bte8d', 'i4btd82']",['0'],['NORP'],-2.152,0.0,-2.152,0,3,3,"['2022-04-11T19:01:39', '2022-04-11T19:01:25']"
Authoritarianism,1,7,[2345105],['i7k2zo0'],['i7j0hm4'],['NORP'],0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T14:21:19']
Awww,4,9,[2042107],['i4nfc63'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T02:21:18']
Azerbaijan,4,8,[959740],['i34ese0'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.34,0.0,-0.34,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T16:17:29']
Azerbaijan,4,9,[1787828],"['i3zf4ll', 'i3zmm87', 'i3zsovm']","['i3zaqa1', '0']",['GPE'],0.1543,0.1543,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-09T03:09:08', '2022-04-09T02:07:22', '2022-04-09T04:03:00']"
Azov,1,0,[2063107],['i4vc1tp'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.35509999999999997,0.2023,-0.5574,1,1,2,['2022-04-15T19:35:30']
Azov,1,2,[2325276],['i782wla'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.4945,0.4945,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-03T23:25:31']
Azov,1,7,"[2345105, 2350926]","['i7jrdhv', 'i7mhl9k', 'i7ju6vz', 'i7iwpas', 'i7ji5s5', 'i7kfh81']","['i7kcspp', '0']",['PERSON'],-0.7203999999999999,0.7901,-1.5105,1,4,5,"['2022-05-06T15:45:55', '2022-05-06T11:26:42', '2022-05-06T13:16:02', '2022-05-06T06:32:46', '2022-05-07T01:06:34', '2022-05-06T12:53:11']"
Azov,1,9,[2208607],['i5jg1jx'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-20T22:10:49']
Azov,9,3,[2104843],['i5f54lg'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.2732,0.0,-0.2732,0,1,1,['2022-04-20T00:48:39']
Azov Regiment,1,7,[2350926],['i7k68ir'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.6369,0.6369,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T14:43:47']
Azovstal,1,7,[2345105],['i7k1371'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-06T14:07:44']
Azovstal/Mariupol,1,0,[2279161],['i6rst1u'],['i6rp9le'],['ORG'],-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-04-30T09:19:32']
B-,1,7,[2053825],"['i4zst4n', 'i4zsygl', 'i4zr9x5']",['0'],['GPE'],-3.8108,0.0,-3.8108,0,5,5,"['2022-04-16T19:28:45', '2022-04-16T19:40:27', '2022-04-16T19:41:32']"
B.A.,6,1,[1480953],['i3isyri'],['i3ir3x7'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T18:27:41']
BBB,6,1,[1480953],"['i3k3y64', 'i3khw27', 'i3j4aad']","['i3j4aad', '0']",['ORG'],-1.1938,0.0,-1.1938,0,2,2,"['2022-04-05T19:40:42', '2022-04-06T01:23:54', '2022-04-05T23:40:13']"
BBC,9,3,[2104843],['i5gbe5z'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.8038,0.0,-0.8038,0,2,2,['2022-04-20T07:08:48']
BBC News,1,0,[1860324],['i41hc08'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-09T14:55:09']
BBC News,2,6,[1081722],['i3a00zp'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T22:12:26']
BBC News,4,2,[1878824],"['i45ya07', 'i460biq']",['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-10T14:08:37', '2022-04-10T14:24:08']"
BBC News - Mariupol,1,7,[2345105],['i7je1bl'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-05-06T10:39:19']
BEIJING,4,1,[578564],['i25vtw2'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-26T05:55:37']
BEIJING,4,4,[2024078],['i4oukkt'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.25,0.0,-0.25,0,1,1,['2022-04-14T12:01:46']
BERLIN,3,8,[425465],['i2fvkgj'],['0'],['ORG'],0.3321,0.3321,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28T14:24:49']
BERLIN,4,0,[2150320],['i5shzng'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.8176,0.0,-0.8176,0,1,1,['2022-04-22T19:56:33']
BERLIN - The Group,3,8,[425465],['i2g0wyo'],['0'],['ORG'],0.3321,0.3321,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28T15:02:38']
BLM,2,0,[634084],['i2wu20x'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.6369,0.0,-0.6369,0,1,1,['2022-03-31T22:57:29']
BLM,2,3,[340497],['i2glolb'],['i29vfbv'],['ORG'],-0.4215,0.0,-0.4215,0,1,1,['2022-03-28T17:22:14']
BLS,6,1,[1480953],['i3lfml7'],['0'],['ORG'],0.4877,0.4877,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T06:30:43']
BP,7,6,[623485],['i2xlhrn'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T02:23:30']
BREXIT,4,7,[2023465],['i4t7ddc'],['i4sh1gi'],['NORP'],-0.2057,0.0,-0.2057,0,1,1,['2022-04-15T09:00:30']
BTS,4,6,[2062426],['i4zbby3'],['i4ypysq'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-16T17:30:44']
Babyn Yar,1,0,[2170124],['i5pnu2f'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.6705,0.0,-0.6705,0,1,1,['2022-04-22T04:53:30']
"Babyn Yar,&quot",1,0,[2170124],['i5poj9m'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.6705,0.0,-0.6705,0,1,1,['2022-04-22T05:00:41']
Bachelor,6,1,[1480953],['i4ggwjx'],['i3lf67s'],['ORG'],0.4951,0.4951,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-12T17:53:36']
Bahrain,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3clwxe'],['i3cfg61'],['GPE'],2.8956,2.8956,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-04T13:29:56']
Ballanco,4,6,[2062426],['i578ett'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-18T12:27:56']
Baltic,4,7,[2023465],['i4sfj4v'],['i4sdmdl'],['NORP'],0.6486,0.6486,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-15T03:27:47']
Baltic,4,9,[1787828],['i3zmc7e'],['0'],['NORP'],0.2382,0.2382,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-09T03:06:47']
Baltimore,5,6,[2074813],['i53e6co'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T15:52:16']
Banks Crossing,2,3,[340497],['i2bf5b9'],['i29zhvn'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-27T14:31:23']
Bannon,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['GPE'],0.2247,0.2247,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Bannon,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],"['PERSON', 'GPE']",1.1155,1.1155,0.0,3,0,3,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
Barbara,4,6,[1549013],['i32cc6v'],['i301282'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T02:46:15']
Barbaric,4,2,[1878824],"['i45ya07', 'i460biq']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.5464,0.5464,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-10T14:08:37', '2022-04-10T14:24:08']"
Barbarisms,4,6,[1549013],['i32cc6v'],['i301282'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T02:46:15']
Barr,2,4,[800487],['i3122ry'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T20:33:38']
Bastogne,1,7,[2345105],['i7k4c36'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-06T14:30:41']
Batman,0,1,[2021946],['i4g4rxx'],['i4g28xc'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-12T16:38:48']
Beasley,7,9,[1896851],['i2nw6hd'],['0'],['ORG'],0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-30T02:01:23']
Beijing,0,2,[2292360],"['i6yj681', 'i6yj8qn']","['i6yj681', '0']",['GPE'],-0.16520000000000004,0.9165,-1.0817,4,2,6,"['2022-05-01T22:27:22', '2022-05-01T22:26:51']"
Beijing,4,4,[2024078],['i4oukkt'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.25,0.0,-0.25,0,1,1,['2022-04-14T12:01:46']
Beijing,6,8,[2169477],"['i5ykjss', 'i5yjzx1', 'i5yqzpr', 'i5x94pm']",['0'],['GPE'],-0.5491,0.4939,-1.043,1,3,4,"['2022-04-23T21:16:02', '2022-04-24T04:47:03', '2022-04-24T03:44:39', '2022-04-24T03:39:31']"
Belarus,1,0,[2333865],['i7akdl5'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-05-04T14:02:39']
Belarus,1,7,[1963245],['i4a7rnh'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.2023,0.0,-0.2023,0,1,1,['2022-04-11T12:01:44']
Belarus,4,0,[1093474],['i37nn12'],['i37bv7t'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T11:33:24']
Belarus,4,3,[1682674],['i3vwee5'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-08T11:15:37']
Belarus,4,8,[426218],['i2by5p4'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.34049999999999997,0.4019,-0.7424,1,1,2,['2022-03-27T16:48:53']
Belarus,7,6,[1479648],['i3hzj63'],['i3hxfpd'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T15:12:37']
Belarus,9,3,"[678224, 2104843]","['i2yrmrk', 'i35z737', 'i5eq6b9']","['0', 'i5ep0ft']",['GPE'],0.7032999999999999,1.2456,-0.5423,2,2,4,"['2022-04-02T23:38:04', '2022-04-01T10:16:21', '2022-04-19T23:01:38']"
Belarus,9,7,[560493],['i2s1xa9'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-30T23:13:54']
Belgian Malinois,9,3,[678224],['i36k5yt'],['i3696l9'],['ORG'],-0.8176,0.0,-0.8176,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T03:33:22']
Belgorod,9,3,[678224],['i2z0yyd'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.3612,0.0,-0.3612,0,1,1,['2022-04-01T11:59:52']
Belorusian Giga Chad,9,2,[1936012],['i49tgn4'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-11T09:13:41']
Benghazi,0,2,[2292360],"['i6y4b9c', 'i6wj3ye']",['0'],"['PERSON', 'GPE']",-0.2357,0.0,-0.2357,0,2,2,"['2022-05-01T20:36:07', '2022-05-01T13:32:34']"
Bennie Thompson,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
Berlin,4,9,[1787828],['i42s3it'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.6486,0.0,-0.6486,0,1,1,['2022-04-09T20:15:39']
Bernie,2,7,[1138187],['i36wlyy'],['i367a64'],['PERSON'],0.3612,0.3612,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T05:36:29']
Bernie Sanders,4,7,[2023465],['i4t7ddc'],['i4sh1gi'],['PERSON'],0.3612,0.3612,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-15T09:00:30']
Bernie Sanders,6,1,[1480953],"['i3jivhm', 'i3kf7t0']","['i3joblv', 'i3is6lk']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",0.5201,0.5994,-0.0793,1,1,2,"['2022-04-06T01:04:03', '2022-04-05T21:11:08']"
Berīgād-e qazzāq,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3d269b'],['i3cfg61'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T15:25:41']
Betsy DeVos,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3cdtx8'],['i3cdeam'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T12:20:52']
Betsy DuVos,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3dufbn'],['0'],['PERSON'],2.0092,2.0092,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-04T18:28:08']
Bettigole,0,9,[2060872],['i50usy4'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.5423,0.0,-0.5423,0,1,1,['2022-04-17T00:27:40']
Beuler’s before,0,9,[2060872],['i5614o8'],['i54z8qb'],['ORG'],-0.3818,0.0,-0.3818,0,1,1,['2022-04-18T03:36:06']
Bezos,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]","['i3ds0ms', 'i3d9wga', 'i3cfo2u', 'i3d26i7', 'i3cg0k7', 'i3dj2v2']","['0', 'i3cfo2u']",['PERSON'],1.0159999999999998,2.376,-1.36,4,4,8,"['2022-04-04T18:12:47', '2022-04-04T17:15:49', '2022-04-04T12:37:37', '2022-04-04T16:16:57', '2022-04-04T12:40:41', '2022-04-04T15:25:44']"
Biden,0,2,[2292360],"['i6z0kcf', 'i74od6l']","['i6y4b9c', 'i6whp7m']",['PERSON'],0.17060000000000003,0.5106,-0.34,1,1,2,"['2022-05-02T00:47:46', '2022-05-03T06:26:07']"
Biden,1,0,[2279161],"['i6w4gkt', 'i6vsdr8']","['i6vrczc', 'i6vd0kc']",['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-05-01T07:48:00', '2022-05-01T10:47:07']"
Biden,1,7,[2345105],['i7kiezf'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T16:05:15']
Biden,2,4,"[439459, 800487]","['i31eqdp', 'i33nbfe', 'i30orqp', 'i30na8k', 'i39qpxa', 'i30qgit', 'i2j5jrf', 'i351s6r', 'i34smjk', 'i3114vd']","['i3114vd', 'i30o9l2', '0', 'i30na8k']",['PERSON'],2.5991,3.489,-0.8898999999999999,7,3,10,"['2022-04-02T17:56:42', '2022-04-01T19:01:19', '2022-04-01T22:06:18', '2022-04-01T20:27:00', '2022-04-02T12:28:02', '2022-04-03T21:05:05', '2022-04-01T18:51:01', '2022-04-01T19:12:58', '2022-04-02T19:09:18', '2022-03-29T05:41:39']"
Biden,2,5,[413890],['i2ghiyk'],['i2g90ox'],['PERSON'],0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28T16:54:29']
Biden,2,6,[898818],"['i351x2v', 'i3525tk']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-02T19:12:30', '2022-04-02T19:10:26']"
Biden,2,7,[1138187],['i36wlyy'],['i367a64'],['PERSON'],0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T05:36:29']
Biden,4,0,[824475],['i2kho4y'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.025300000000000003,0.128,-0.1027,1,1,2,['2022-03-29T14:35:55']
Biden,4,2,[796098],"['i2za5z6', 'i31s97q', 'i304pwc']",['0'],['PERSON'],-0.8022,0.0,-0.8022,0,2,2,"['2022-04-01T23:54:33', '2022-04-01T16:48:05', '2022-04-01T13:17:44']"
Biden,4,7,[1587993],"['i3n9v9z', 'i3n9v1f']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-06T16:45:39', '2022-04-06T16:45:41']"
Biden,4,8,"[517355, 959740]","['i2l0orw', 'i34ese0']",['0'],['PERSON'],1.0206,1.0206,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-03-29T16:39:26', '2022-04-02T16:17:29']"
Biden,4,9,"[1024713, 1276661, 1258901]","['i3d98tu', 'i3f7ehk', 'i39kg4c', 'i3da216']","['i39fihu', '0']",['PERSON'],-2.3880999999999997,0.0,-2.3881,0,4,4,"['2022-04-03T20:20:38', '2022-04-04T16:17:58', '2022-04-04T16:12:39', '2022-04-04T23:44:40']"
Biden,5,2,[2313930],['i6nfdx8'],['i6newt6'],['PERSON'],0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-29T10:48:57']
Biden,6,1,[1480953],"['i3kly9a', 'i3kfjd5', 'i3ka5va', 'i3m81tl', 'i3rrlvz', 'i3k6xmb', 'i3k4mac', 'i3mz00g', 'i3msug4', 'i3kmazi', 'i3mnnwt', 'i3isyri', 'i3jz9bg', 'i3j6x28', 'i3josxq', 'i3lzu3a', 'i3l1e33', 'i3rrli8', 'i3n6b9f', 'i3j0bwq', 'i3j47or', 'i3jhund', 'i3jtbq2', 'i3iskvq', 'i3k77ty', 'i3mnd02', 'i3ivxps', 'i3mthkf', 'i3ivkl3', 'i3l1cek', 'i3js7pb', 'i3j5skb', 'i3mosmb', 'i3mdg2u', 'i3lo6pl', 'i3k3y64', 'i3jygcc', 'i3juh47', 'i3itf8y', 'i3k2mbc', 'i3kh4mi', 'i3kwz9c', 'i3mfilk', 'i3k2fre', 'i3j8mah', 'i3jnvu8', 'i3ixx3h', 'i3j17ao', 'i3iy2a9', 'i3jt3vi', 'i3jsxq3', 'i3k92vf', 'i3kp0nz', 'i3j5ye2', 'i3le1oz', 'i3j8fv6', 'i3mbo5y', 'i3iu341', 'i3jotwt', 'i3ir3x7', 'i3jugcj', 'i3jhkmn', 'i3k9i11', 'i3kjfiu', 'i3jwje0', 'i3kvzaa', 'i3lc2nb', 'i3jrjos', 'i3krupf', 'i3lqyw5', 'i3nqr1w', 'i3j82ul', 'i3jqq79', 'i3l26ec', 'i3jkpl3', 'i3k0w2e', 'i3kx81w', 'i3n8p2a', 'i3kldfq', 'i3j4977', 'i3lzfep', 'i3it1kx', 'i3jvbjg', 'i3kqsqk', 'i3kz70g', 'i3jdrgd', 'i3k4b8z', 'i3k6o30', 'i3jq2ii', 'i3j0vnr']","['i3is6lk', 'i3iszrp', 'i3j4aad', 'i3j5skb', 'i3jnfer', 'i3joblv', 'i3l2itp', 'i3ir3x7', 'i3k4s7l', 'i3iv398', 'i3ityz6', 'i3jnf83', 'i3j4977', 'i3jvd3j', 'i3j12s0', '0', 'i3j6b17', 'i3josxq', 'i3it1kx', 'i3kconz', 'i3lf67s', 'i3iqdoo', 'i3j0bwq', 'i3iv393', 'i3lydfw']",['PERSON'],6.0135,21.1689,-15.1554,49,38,87,"['2022-04-05T18:35:07', '2022-04-05T19:00:00', '2022-04-05T18:47:10', '2022-04-05T21:02:50', '2022-04-06T05:47:33', '2022-04-05T20:06:30', '2022-04-05T20:39:16', '2022-04-06T04:05:50', '2022-04-05T22:09:58', '2022-04-05T23:45:09', '2022-04-05T19:00:54', '2022-04-06T00:21:25', '2022-04-06T02:29:50', '2022-04-06T03:11:40', '2022-04-06T03:39:01', '2022-04-05T21:04:36', '2022-04-05T19:21:02', '2022-04-06T00:18:17', '2022-04-06T00:26:26', '2022-04-05T20:07:34', '2022-04-06T00:04:25', '2022-04-05T23:29:01', '2022-04-06T00:02:18', '2022-04-07T15:08:40', '2022-04-06T01:35:08', '2022-04-06T12:25:01', '2022-04-05T23:30:22', '2022-04-06T14:22:02', '2022-04-05T19:15:32', '2022-04-06T18:30:01', '2022-04-05T21:50:21', '2022-04-06T15:00:41', '2022-04-05T19:40:31', '2022-04-05T22:30:58', '2022-04-05T19:50:04', '2022-04-05T23:42:54', '2022-04-06T03:21:59', '2022-04-06T00:00:20', '2022-04-06T16:38:19', '2022-04-05T22:30:49', '2022-04-05T22:59:50', '2022-04-05T21:50:32', '2022-04-05T18:44:48', '2022-04-05T22:21:11', '2022-04-05T18:25:09', '2022-04-05T23:40:13', '2022-04-05T22:03:30', '2022-04-06T01:55:58', '2022-04-06T14:56:30', '2022-04-06T13:09:05', '2022-04-06T06:11:05', '2022-04-05T22:22:43', '2022-04-06T15:36:31', '2022-04-06T14:19:59', '2022-04-06T12:55:06', '2022-04-06T01:18:23', '2022-04-06T10:58:47', '2022-04-06T09:07:21', '2022-04-05T20:04:14', '2022-04-05T18:27:41', '2022-04-05T19:57:03', '2022-04-05T19:51:03', '2022-04-05T23:05:43', '2022-04-05T23:17:39', '2022-04-06T03:58:16', '2022-04-06T01:06:27', '2022-04-06T03:58:42', '2022-04-06T11:03:22', '2022-04-06T01:49:11', '2022-04-06T03:19:58', '2022-04-06T14:29:36', '2022-04-06T02:16:06', '2022-04-05T18:28:13', '2022-04-05T21:58:58', '2022-04-05T22:20:00', '2022-04-05T18:15:28', '2022-04-05T19:40:15', '2022-04-05T21:23:06', '2022-04-06T13:24:37', '2022-04-07T15:08:44', '2022-04-05T18:30:44', '2022-04-06T01:53:21', '2022-04-05T22:37:00', '2022-04-05T22:14:52', '2022-04-06T02:38:14', '2022-04-05T21:44:11', '2022-04-06T08:27:29', '2022-04-05T22:45:46', '2022-04-06T16:22:46', '2022-04-05T19:19:02']"
Biden,6,2,[559922],['i2vtd9t'],['i2vq5zq'],['PERSON'],-0.3875,0.0,-0.3875,0,1,1,['2022-03-31T18:55:38']
Biden,6,9,[623417],"['i2ug0v4', 'i2uv72n', 'i2uca92', 'i2vcdeg']","['i2v8up7', '0']",['PERSON'],0.43560000000000004,0.7316,-0.296,3,1,4,"['2022-03-31T13:03:37', '2022-03-31T15:18:22', '2022-03-31T17:07:27', '2022-03-31T13:33:00']"
Biden,7,4,[757828],['i3ctr24'],['i3bngqz'],['PERSON'],0.6486,0.6486,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-04T14:27:42']
Biden,7,6,[623485],"['i30ht37', 'i2vfln8', 'i2v7qiy', 'i2v8gxn', 'i2vfjcg', 'i2viow9', 'i2v8xi3', 'i30uf6f', 'i2v1gx8']","['i309aom', 'i2uzw5e', '0']",['PERSON'],0.5485,1.7706,-1.2221,4,3,7,"['2022-03-31T17:28:05', '2022-04-01T18:13:41', '2022-03-31T17:47:40', '2022-03-31T15:58:33', '2022-03-31T16:38:12', '2022-04-01T19:40:14', '2022-03-31T17:27:41', '2022-03-31T16:42:48', '2022-03-31T16:45:42']"
Biden,9,3,[678224],"['i2yg2vf', 'i2xjskr']","['i2xjskr', '0']",['PERSON'],0.0258,0.0258,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-01T02:10:37', '2022-04-01T07:34:02']"
Biden,9,5,[2150388],['i5qikg2'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-04-22T11:32:12']
Biden](https://np.reddit.com,4,8,[959740],['i34ese0'],['0'],['ORG'],0.3818,0.3818,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T16:17:29']
Bidens,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3fi2u4'],['i3cn5ov'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T00:58:29']
Bidens,6,1,[1480953],['i3jbele'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-05T20:24:42']
Bidens,7,7,[1227715],['i3ixb8z'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T18:56:04']
Bill,4,0,[1093474],['i39d68i'],['i37d0t2'],['PERSON'],0.1779,0.1779,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T19:30:34']
Bill Clinton,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.0258,0.0,-0.0258,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Bishoprics,4,8,[494236],['i2og8ka'],['i2lwyze'],['NORP'],0.5849,0.5849,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-30T04:57:49']
Bitcoin,6,1,[1480953],"['i3jy5jt', 'i3msug4']","['i3jjv36', '0']","['PERSON', 'NORP']",0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-06T14:56:30', '2022-04-05T22:57:39']"
Black,2,3,[1092237],['i3hjsfo'],['0'],['GPE'],0.5859,0.5859,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-05T13:25:16']
Black Americans,6,1,[1480953],['i3iy2a9'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.2023,0.0,-0.2023,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T19:00:54']
"Black, Latino",2,3,[1092237],['i37mmet'],['0'],['ORG'],0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T11:20:28']
Blackmail,3,2,[2231218],['i6eiey1'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-27T14:12:30']
Blick,4,8,[959740],['i35hof0'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T21:16:40']
Blinken,7,4,[757828],['i3ctr24'],['i3bngqz'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T14:27:42']
Blow putin,4,9,[1983397],['i4bx7ox'],['i4br3ut'],['PERSON'],0.3612,0.3612,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11T19:28:34']
Board,8,0,[825466],['i31oh98'],['0'],['ORG'],0.1779,0.1779,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-01T23:23:26']
Boebart,2,7,[1138187],['i37cntx'],['0'],['GPE'],0.6486,0.6486,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T09:04:19']
Boebert,2,7,[1138187],"['i36wlyy', 'i36hc3u']","['i367a64', '0']",['PERSON'],0.6124,0.6124,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-03T03:08:58', '2022-04-03T05:36:29']"
Bologna,4,8,[959740],['i358wuw'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.6249,0.6249,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T20:07:42']
Boo hoo,4,0,[1093474],['i3awsfw'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T02:23:07']
Boo hoo.,4,9,[2042107],['i4nkz1q'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T03:06:21']
Boooooooooo,6,1,[1480953],['i3k2f4z'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T23:28:53']
Boris,4,2,[1878824],"['i445y7t', 'i43i25k']","['0', 'i4346vt']",['PERSON'],0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-10T02:41:45', '2022-04-09T23:28:03']"
Boris,4,9,[1024713],['i3a3yof'],['i39fihu'],['PERSON'],-0.9535,0.0,-0.9535,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T22:41:26']
Boris Johnson,4,2,[1878824],"['i4299f6', 'i45ya07', 'i460biq']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.959,0.959,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-09T18:03:00', '2022-04-10T14:08:37', '2022-04-10T14:24:08']"
Boris Johnson,4,9,[1024713],"['i3a3yof', 'i3a35io']","['i39fihu', '0']",['PERSON'],0.8957999999999999,0.8957999999999999,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-03T22:41:26', '2022-04-03T22:35:24']"
Boris Johnson Makes,4,2,[1878824],"['i45ya07', 'i460biq']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.5464,0.5464,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-10T14:08:37', '2022-04-10T14:24:08']"
Bornholm,4,9,[2150382],['i4jgg29'],['i4f0r7p'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-13T08:05:48']
Bosnia,1,2,[704263],['i33vq58'],['i32buzn'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T13:48:06']
Boston,0,0,[2025595],"['i4t2vz7', 'i4ryk2f', 'i4sje8f']","['0', 'i4sje8f']",['GPE'],-0.0008000000000000229,0.2934,-0.2942,2,1,3,"['2022-04-15T01:10:26', '2022-04-15T04:02:37', '2022-04-15T07:57:03']"
Boychenko,1,0,[2170124],['i5poj9m'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.6705,0.0,-0.6705,0,1,1,['2022-04-22T05:00:41']
"Boychenko, Piotr Andryushchenko",1,0,[2170124],['i5pnu2f'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.7906,0.0,-0.7906,0,1,1,['2022-04-22T04:53:30']
Brain,1,1,[1998813],['i4gcxlc'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-12T17:29:05']
Brandon,2,3,[1092237],['i365sps'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T01:32:46']
Brandon,7,6,[623485],['i2xvs3k'],['i2v0uw5'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T03:48:07']
Brexit,4,6,[2023525],['i4lz3i0'],['i4lm8uo'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-13T20:12:07']
Brexit,4,7,[2023465],"['i4t7ddc', 'i4sh1gi']","['i4sh1gi', '0']",['PERSON'],0.4136,0.7096,-0.296,1,1,2,"['2022-04-15T03:41:11', '2022-04-15T09:00:30']"
Brian Kemp,2,3,[340497],['i2aoj0o'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-27T09:44:34']
Brig,4,6,[2062426],['i51mtaw'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T04:26:56']
Brigade,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3d269b'],['i3cfg61'],['ORG'],2.0836,2.0836,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-04T15:25:41']
Britain,1,0,[2279161],['i6vsdr8'],['i6vd0kc'],['GPE'],0.1027,0.1027,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-01T07:48:00']
Britain,4,9,[1024713],['i39fihu'],['0'],['GPE'],0.13590000000000002,0.5574,-0.4215,1,1,2,['2022-04-03T19:46:33']
British,2,5,[413890],['i2g90ox'],['0'],['NORP'],0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28T15:58:03']
British,4,9,"[1918680, 1787828]","['i3yqyxn', 'i47b8cl']","['i3ygjx8', 'i464icl']",['NORP'],1.6128,1.6128,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-04-08T23:00:02', '2022-04-10T19:44:57']"
Brits,4,0,[1093474],['i39fnzi'],['i378925'],['NORP'],-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T19:47:36']
Bronchitis,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
Bronx,4,9,[1511077],['i3ak5rw'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T00:45:45']
Brutal,1,2,[704263],['i34thw0'],['i33oc5e'],['ORG'],-0.836,0.0,-0.836,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T18:03:03']
Bucha,1,0,[2170124],"['i5pnu2f', 'i5poj9m']",['0'],['PERSON'],-1.9020000000000001,0.0,-1.9020000000000001,0,2,2,"['2022-04-22T05:00:41', '2022-04-22T04:53:30']"
Bucha,1,7,"[1011081, 2041615]","['i4xcwz0', 'i4wmptf', 'i3ahm1e']","['i4wvily', '0']","['PERSON', 'GPE', 'ORG']",-1.2023,0.4939,-1.6962,1,2,3,"['2022-04-16T01:36:23', '2022-04-16T05:38:52', '2022-04-04T00:26:24']"
Bucha,4,0,"[2150320, 1093474]","['i5qlfts', 'i39ib79']",['0'],['PERSON'],-0.6597,0.0,-0.6597,0,1,1,"['2022-04-03T20:05:47', '2022-04-22T12:00:52']"
Bucha,4,8,[959740],['i35ukhz'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.7579,0.0,-0.7579,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T23:00:23']
Bucha,4,9,"[1918680, 1276661, 1694081, 1258901]","['i47qvlf', 'i3drifp', 'i3tpl1j', 'i3hmuqh', 'i3cikc6', 'i3cikkq', 'i3cikzt']","['i3f7ehk', '0', 'i464icl']","['PERSON', 'GPE', 'ORG']",-2.6848,0.0,-2.6848,0,7,7,"['2022-04-04T13:02:59', '2022-04-04T18:09:33', '2022-04-10T21:34:52', '2022-04-04T13:02:53', '2022-04-07T22:49:38', '2022-04-04T13:02:50', '2022-04-05T13:47:55']"
Bucha,9,3,"[678224, 2104843]","['i35yoit', 'i37z3za', 'i365ulg', 'i366y6f', 'i5gbe5z']","['i35yde7', '0']","['PERSON', 'GPE', 'ORG']",-0.9940999999999999,1.1299000000000001,-2.124,2,3,5,"['2022-04-03T13:31:37', '2022-04-03T01:42:57', '2022-04-02T23:33:47', '2022-04-03T01:33:14', '2022-04-20T07:08:48']"
Bucha](https://www.bbc.com/news/,2,6,[1081722],['i3a00zp'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.7096,0.0,-0.7096,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T22:12:26']
Buchas,1,7,[1907918],['i44r8pm'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-10T05:54:49']
Bueller,2,9,[419795],['i2k204z'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T12:37:39']
Build Back,6,1,[1480953],['i3k4szk'],['i3jr4ii'],['GPE'],-0.066,0.0,-0.066,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T23:46:31']
Bulgaria,4,8,[494236],['i2mcug4'],['i2lwyze'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T21:41:26']
Bullshit,2,4,[800487],['i34l56p'],['i33klgy'],['PERSON'],-0.5859,0.0,-0.5859,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T17:03:12']
Bully,4,9,[1787828],['i43rrbq'],['i42s3it'],['PERSON'],0.3089,0.3089,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-10T00:45:19']
Burgh,5,6,[2074813],['i53e6co'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T15:52:16']
Bush,2,7,[1138187],['i36wlyy'],['i367a64'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T05:36:29']
Bush,4,8,[959740],['i35t83o'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T22:49:25']
Bush,4,9,[1276661],['i3gta2m'],['i3dvdum'],['PERSON'],-0.07999999999999996,0.3415,-0.4215,1,1,2,['2022-04-05T08:39:58']
Business Management,6,1,[1480953],['i3ocqhk'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T20:44:52']
Byzantium,4,8,[494236],['i2mcug4'],['i2lwyze'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T21:41:26']
C'est,4,6,[2023525],['i4pt2vu'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T16:12:26']
CBS,1,7,[2345105],['i7kgb08'],['0'],['ORG'],0.3612,0.3612,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T15:51:17']
CBS,4,9,[1258901],['i3czxjh'],['i3czt9f'],['ORG'],-0.7506,0.0,-0.7506,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T15:10:25']
CBS News,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
CCP,0,2,[2292360],"['i6xstec', 'i713b7c']","['0', 'i6x2ze0']",['ORG'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,"['2022-05-01T19:13:18', '2022-05-02T14:14:24']"
CCP,6,8,[2169477],['i5yjzx1'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-04-24T03:39:31']
CDC,0,1,[2021946],"['i4gydt5', 'i4glido']","['i4g4opl', 'i4g6eof']",['ORG'],0.37040000000000006,0.7506,-0.3802,1,1,2,"['2022-04-12T19:44:00', '2022-04-12T18:22:22']"
CDC,0,9,"[2060872, 457434]","['i2ys31n', 'i54sk9p']",['0'],['ORG'],-0.2244,0.0,-0.2244,0,1,1,"['2022-04-01T10:22:15', '2022-04-17T21:47:48']"
CDC,6,8,[2284154],['i6r5heo'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.1531,0.0,-0.1531,0,1,1,['2022-04-30T04:09:26']
CERN,4,8,[426218],['i2by5p4'],['0'],['GPE'],0.4019,0.4019,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-27T16:48:53']
CGTN,4,1,[578564],['i25wfkr'],['0'],['ORG'],0.06369999999999998,0.7906,-0.7269,1,1,2,['2022-03-26T06:03:32']
CIA,4,0,[1093474],['i39d68i'],['i37d0t2'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T19:30:34']
CIA,4,9,[1024713],"['i381z83', 'i38mk6p', 'i37u7mu']","['0', 'i37u7mu']",['ORG'],0.0494,0.7845,-0.7351,1,1,2,"['2022-04-03T13:56:21', '2022-04-03T16:28:17', '2022-04-03T12:45:54']"
CNN,3,8,[425465],['i2gbiux'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-28T16:14:53']
CNN,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.6808,0.0,-0.6808,0,1,1,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
CNN,9,7,[560493],['i2s20wi'],['i2s1xa9'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-30T23:14:41']
COVID,0,1,[2021946],"['i4gdgx5', 'i4h15od', 'i4gydt5', 'i4durxh', 'i4g04q9']","['i4g4opl', 'i4fz11i', '0', 'i4g7of5']",['ORG'],1.0184,1.2684,-0.25,3,1,4,"['2022-04-12T16:10:11', '2022-04-12T19:44:00', '2022-04-12T03:43:06', '2022-04-12T20:01:04', '2022-04-12T17:32:23']"
COVID,0,2,[2292360],"['i6xkjiq', 'i6xrkre']","['i6xd41z', '0']",['ORG'],-0.5106,0.0,-0.5106,0,1,1,"['2022-05-01T18:13:42', '2022-05-01T19:04:19']"
COVID,0,7,[2354712],['i7vol9k'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.4019,0.0,-0.4019,0,1,1,['2022-05-09T03:46:03']
COVID,0,9,[2060872],"['i535z22', 'i574z3p']","['i54sk9p', 'i52q4l2']",['ORG'],0.6486,0.6486,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-18T11:53:30', '2022-04-17T14:53:22']"
COVID,2,3,[340497],['i2b82jf'],['i2alcjc'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-27T13:34:06']
COVID,4,6,[2062426],['i578ett'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.5267,0.0,-0.5267,0,1,1,['2022-04-18T12:27:56']
COVID,6,1,"[2194486, 1480953, 2186286]","['i3l0d8l', 'i62i05i', 'i3j73by', 'i651376', 'i3kgcp1', 'i61xk5o', 'i3iq837', 'i3jevtn']","['i61htae', '0']",['ORG'],1.5135,1.8662,-0.3527,5,2,7,"['2022-04-05T19:58:08', '2022-04-25T00:31:25', '2022-04-05T20:46:13', '2022-04-24T21:55:21', '2022-04-05T18:09:23', '2022-04-06T03:49:23', '2022-04-25T15:15:31', '2022-04-06T01:12:39']"
COVID,7,3,[920306],['i33l0ux'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.25,0.0,-0.25,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T12:03:05']
COVID-19,0,1,[2021946],"['i4durxh', 'i4gmkbs']","['0', 'i4g7iiv']",['ORG'],0.017299999999999982,0.7269,-0.7096,1,1,2,"['2022-04-12T18:28:59', '2022-04-12T03:43:06']"
COVID-19,0,2,[2292360],"['i6y4b9c', 'i6wko4m']",['0'],['ORG'],0.3818,0.3818,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-05-01T13:46:23', '2022-05-01T20:36:07']"
COVID-19,0,7,[2354712],['i7vedv1'],['0'],['ORG'],0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-09T02:14:06']
COVID-19,0,9,[2060872],['i50usy4'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T00:27:40']
COVID-19,6,1,"[1480953, 2186286]","['i3iq837', 'i60zn07']",['0'],['ORG'],0.38359999999999994,1.5699,-1.1863000000000001,3,2,5,"['2022-04-24T17:56:20', '2022-04-05T18:09:23']"
COVID-19,6,2,[2235430],['i6euqdb'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.5574,0.0,-0.5574,0,1,1,['2022-04-27T15:34:56']
COVID-19,6,8,[476817],"['i2ohiqf', 'i2ohgv9']",['0'],['ORG'],0.7269,0.7269,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-03-30T05:11:29', '2022-03-30T05:10:55']"
COVID-19,7,3,[920306],['i33l0ux'],['0'],['ORG'],0.017299999999999982,0.7269,-0.7096,1,1,2,['2022-04-02T12:03:05']
CPS,6,1,[1480953],['i3ktkvh'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T02:52:00']
CRISPR,0,2,[2292360],['i6yj8qn'],['i6yj681'],['PERSON'],0.7443,0.7443,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-01T22:27:22']
CTC,6,1,[1480953],['i3k3a0x'],['i3jtcwp'],['ORG'],-0.1027,0.0,-0.1027,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T23:35:13']
Cadia,1,7,[2350926],"['i7k5apn', 'i7l9cbf']","['i7jrdhv', 'i7jkq9c']",['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-05-06T14:37:22', '2022-05-06T19:16:13']"
Calif.,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['GPE'],0.6124,0.6124,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
California,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.0258,0.0,-0.0258,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
California,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['GPE'],0.6124,0.6124,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
California,4,6,[2062426],['i51em60'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.8479,0.0,-0.8479,0,1,1,['2022-04-17T03:12:08']
California,4,8,[494236],['i2qhkz7'],['i2m8n6p'],['GPE'],0.0772,0.0772,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-30T16:53:17']
Cambodia,1,2,[704263],"['i32buzn', 'i3452pr', 'i32f40d', 'i33odb2']","['i32buzn', '0']",['GPE'],-1.341,0.0,-1.341,0,2,2,"['2022-04-02T03:11:17', '2022-04-02T02:41:55', '2022-04-02T12:39:04', '2022-04-02T15:03:43']"
Cameo,2,7,[1138187],['i390ivo'],['i386dar'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T18:03:35']
Canada,2,5,[413890],['i2j5de4'],['i2gmf5c'],['GPE'],-0.5423,0.0,-0.5423,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T05:39:28']
Canada,3,8,[425465],['i2fvkgj'],['0'],['GPE'],0.6808,0.6808,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28T14:24:49']
Canada,4,0,[1093474],['i3b4txj'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.2732,0.0,-0.2732,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T03:28:19']
Canada,4,7,[1587993],"['i3n9v9z', 'i3n9v1f']",['0'],['GPE'],1.1988,1.1988,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-06T16:45:39', '2022-04-06T16:45:41']"
Canada,6,1,[1480953],['i3kzaj3'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T03:39:52']
Canada,7,6,[623485],['i2v8ru3'],['0'],['GPE'],0.126,0.126,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-31T16:44:42']
Canadas,7,6,[623485],['i2v8ru3'],['0'],['ORG'],0.126,0.126,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-31T16:44:42']
Canadian,0,9,[2060872],['i53cks5'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T15:40:50']
Canadian,4,9,[1694081],['i3tpl1j'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-07T22:49:38']
Canadian,6,1,[1480953],['i3kkip3'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.0936,0.0,-0.0936,0,1,1,['2022-04-06T01:43:00']
Canadians,6,2,[2235430],['i6fnwtu'],['i6f9u28'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-27T18:45:17']
Cancel,6,1,[1480953],"['i3kimy4', 'i3k7tq7']",['0'],['PERSON'],-0.5,0.0,-0.5,0,2,2,"['2022-04-06T00:08:59', '2022-04-06T01:29:23']"
Cap,6,1,[1480953],"['i3ldnty', 'i3iufw5']","['i3iravh', '0']",['PERSON'],0.2263,0.2263,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-05T18:37:26', '2022-04-06T06:06:17']"
Capitol,2,0,[634084],['i2wfe9u'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.4215,0.0,-0.4215,0,1,1,['2022-03-31T21:17:10']
Capitol,2,4,"[439459, 800487]","['i2j5jrf', 'i33klgy']",['0'],['ORG'],-1.0345,0.0,-1.0345,0,2,2,"['2022-04-02T11:58:17', '2022-03-29T05:41:39']"
Capitol,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.7269,0.0,-0.7269,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
Capitol Hill,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.3612,0.3612,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
Cardozo Law,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.7096,0.7096,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
Carla Del Ponte,4,8,[959740],['i34st55'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T17:58:00']
Carry Ukrainian,4,9,[1787828],['i3ynx5x'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.3505,0.0,-0.3505,0,1,1,['2022-04-08T22:38:01']
Carter,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.8088,0.8088,0.0,2,0,2,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Casper the Ghost,2,9,[419795],['i2icynh'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.3182,0.0,-0.3182,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T01:16:26']
Catholic,4,8,[494236],['i2mh1br'],['i2m8n6p'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T22:04:11']
Catholic,4,9,[1511077],['i3bdlqv'],['i3afx0o'],['NORP'],-0.2411,0.0,-0.2411,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T04:50:59']
Catholics,4,8,[494236],['i2nmxpl'],['i2lwyze'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-30T00:50:11']
Catholics,4,9,[1511077],['i3ag1jn'],['0'],['NORP'],0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-04T00:14:27']
Caucasian,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3d269b'],['i3cfg61'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T15:25:41']
Caucasians,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3d269b'],['i3cfg61'],['NORP'],1.0928,1.0928,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-04T15:25:41']
Cela,4,6,[2023525],['i4pt2vu'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T16:12:26']
Chappelle,8,9,[1811789],['i3y6ti0'],['i3y0eji'],['PERSON'],-0.0516,0.0,-0.0516,0,1,1,['2022-04-08T20:40:34']
Charlatan,6,1,[1480953],['i3mc3eh'],['i3jjv36'],['ORG'],-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-04-06T12:58:29']
Charlie,6,1,[1480953],['i3kelf6'],['i3k4s7l'],['PERSON'],0.8257,0.8257,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T00:59:30']
Charlie Mike,4,6,[2062426],['i51vxt1'],['i51rxlv'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T06:07:33']
Charlie Murphy,8,0,[825466],['i32k0eq'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.6278,0.6278,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T03:57:44']
Chechen,1,0,[2241438],['i60l8ag'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-24T16:19:15']
Chechen,1,7,[2345105],['i7ji1mm'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0772,0.0772,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T11:25:28']
Chechnya,1,7,[2345105],['i7k2zo0'],['i7j0hm4'],['GPE'],0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T14:21:19']
Chechnya,4,6,"[2062426, 1549013]","['i2yf9b0', 'i4zaynn']","['i4z8n9s', '0']",['GPE'],-0.8126,0.0,-0.8126,0,1,1,"['2022-04-16T17:28:03', '2022-04-01T07:22:50']"
Cheeto,6,1,[1480953],['i3mh0x6'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T13:35:36']
Chef Jose Andres,7,9,[1896851],['i2nvafs'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.7469,0.7469,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-30T01:54:24']
Chemical,4,9,[1787828],['i3yi2ke'],['i3ygjx8'],['ORG'],-0.836,0.0,-0.836,0,1,1,['2022-04-08T21:56:37']
Cheney,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.7377,0.0,-0.7377,0,2,2,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
Cheney,4,9,[1276661],['i3gta2m'],['i3dvdum'],['PERSON'],-0.4215,0.0,-0.4215,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T08:39:58']
Cheng Lei,4,1,[578564],"['i25wfkr', 'iaolot5']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.057599999999999985,0.7845,-0.7269,1,1,2,"['2022-03-26T06:03:32', '2022-05-31T17:04:29']"
Chernihiv,4,9,[1258901],['i3czt9f'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T15:09:35']
Chernobyl,4,0,[1093474],['i3ajfl7'],['i38c48q'],['GPE'],0.5267,0.5267,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-04T00:40:13']
Chernobyl,4,6,"[2155952, 1549013]","['i5um9dv', 'i2yht6c']","['0', 'i5tmwhu']",['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-01T07:57:59', '2022-04-23T06:41:17']"
Cheryl Bettigole,0,9,[2060872],['i50usy4'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T00:27:40']
Chicago,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
Chicago,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]","['i3cgne9', 'i3czral']","['0', 'i3cgne9']",['GPE'],-3.5804,0.0,-3.5804,0,4,4,"['2022-04-04T12:46:16', '2022-04-04T15:09:12']"
Chicago,7,6,[623485],['i2v93qv'],['0'],['GPE'],0.27880000000000005,0.7003,-0.4215,1,1,2,['2022-03-31T16:46:46']
Chill,4,0,[1093474],['i37b9m4'],['i378925'],['ORG'],0.0624,0.0624,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T08:44:57']
Chin,0,9,[2060872],['i51u3c6'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T05:45:26']
China,0,2,[2292360],"['i6wko4m', 'i713b7c', 'i6wp694', 'i72asjb', 'i6wrjf6', 'i72m1gy', 'i6yj681', 'i6y4b9c', 'i6wlnbd', 'i6x2ikx', 'i6z921g', 'i6xeby5', 'i6yj8qn']","['i6wqyqc', 'i6yj681', '0']",['GPE'],-3.7520000000000002,1.4506000000000001,-5.2026,4,11,15,"['2022-05-02T20:25:07', '2022-05-01T22:27:22', '2022-05-01T13:54:49', '2022-05-01T17:29:21', '2022-05-01T20:36:07', '2022-05-01T22:26:51', '2022-05-01T13:46:23', '2022-05-01T14:24:14', '2022-05-01T16:04:58', '2022-05-01T14:42:58', '2022-05-02T01:59:39', '2022-05-02T19:09:36', '2022-05-02T14:14:24']"
China,1,0,"[2279161, 2170124]","['i6vsdr8', 'i6w4gkt', 'i5qr1b2']","['i5pnu2f', 'i6vrczc', 'i6vd0kc']",['GPE'],-1.309,0.1306,-1.4396,1,2,3,"['2022-05-01T07:48:00', '2022-05-01T10:47:07', '2022-04-22T12:50:40']"
China,1,7,"[1521144, 2053825]","['i522jhs', 'i3plzgk', 'i50j61c', 'i3pk7ui']","['i4zrqcu', '0']",['GPE'],-1.5943,0.1396,-1.7339,1,4,5,"['2022-04-07T01:57:27', '2022-04-07T02:10:41', '2022-04-17T07:33:41', '2022-04-16T22:57:45']"
China,4,0,"[1093474, 824475, 2266890]","['i2kho4y', 'i6rhst2', 'i389phu', 'i38k70m', 'i3b4txj']","['i6re90h', '0']",['GPE'],-0.13459999999999994,0.7599,-0.8945,2,1,3,"['2022-04-04T03:28:19', '2022-03-29T14:35:55', '2022-04-03T14:56:43', '2022-04-03T16:11:55', '2022-04-30T06:36:15']"
China,4,1,[578564],"['i26j923', 'i25wfkr', 'i25vtw2', 'i26l4ys']",['0'],['GPE'],-1.3824999999999998,0.0,-1.3824999999999998,0,2,2,"['2022-03-26T11:29:10', '2022-03-26T05:55:37', '2022-03-26T11:52:02', '2022-03-26T06:03:32']"
China,4,2,[796098],['i37agoe'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T08:34:00']
China,4,3,[1682674],"['i3vwee5', 'i3t2b97']","['i3s5d1b', '0']",['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-08T11:15:37', '2022-04-07T20:11:35']"
China,4,4,[2024078],"['i4oukkt', 'i4ox712', 'i4q48gf', 'i4pkbql', 'i4pjfc7', 'i4oypfv']",['0'],['GPE'],-0.6295,0.8726,-1.5021,2,5,7,"['2022-04-14T15:09:59', '2022-04-14T12:25:49', '2022-04-14T17:25:21', '2022-04-14T12:38:58', '2022-04-14T15:15:52', '2022-04-14T12:01:46']"
China,4,6,"[1296929, 2062426, 1251068]","['i56a795', 'i3d269b', 'i51em60']","['i51djua', 'i3cfg61', '0']",['GPE'],-0.8479,0.0,-0.8479,0,1,1,"['2022-04-18T05:07:40', '2022-04-17T03:12:08', '2022-04-04T15:25:41']"
China,4,7,[1470385],['i3kh0y1'],['0'],['GPE'],0.7865,0.7865,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T01:17:39']
China,4,8,[959740],['i34ese0'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T16:17:29']
China,4,9,"[1024713, 1787828, 1276661, 1258901]","['i404wzt', 'i39gmlw', 'i3dbbfo', 'i3czt9f']","['i3da216', 'i401466', '0']",['GPE'],0.1856,0.4588,-0.2732,1,1,2,"['2022-04-04T16:26:06', '2022-04-09T06:13:25', '2022-04-04T15:09:35', '2022-04-03T19:54:08']"
China,6,8,[2169477],"['i5yplm7', 'i5wne3o', 'i5yjzx1', 'i5wqtu9', 'i629wdt', 'i5ynjhp']","['i5wnavi', 'i5yk6eu', 'i5yjzx1', '0', 'i5z8r83']",['GPE'],1.1944,1.6711,-0.4767,4,1,5,"['2022-04-24T03:39:31', '2022-04-24T04:33:05', '2022-04-23T18:56:42', '2022-04-24T23:27:54', '2022-04-23T18:31:09', '2022-04-24T04:12:57']"
China,7,6,[623485],['i2v26fl'],['i2uzw5e'],['GPE'],-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,['2022-03-31T16:03:10']
China,9,3,[678224],['i2yg2vf'],['i2xjskr'],['GPE'],-0.34,0.0,-0.34,0,1,1,['2022-04-01T07:34:02']
China](https://np.reddit.com,4,9,[1258901],['i3czt9f'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T15:09:35']
Chinese,0,2,[2292360],"['i6wko4m', 'i6yj681', 'i6yj8qn']","['i6yj681', '0']",['NORP'],0.08669999999999978,2.7058999999999997,-2.6191999999999998,7,8,15,"['2022-05-01T13:46:23', '2022-05-01T22:27:22', '2022-05-01T22:26:51']"
Chinese,4,1,[578564],"['i25wfkr', 'i25vtw2']",['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-03-26T05:55:37', '2022-03-26T06:03:32']"
Chinese,4,4,[2024078],['i4phyxt'],['0'],['NORP'],0.25,0.25,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-14T15:00:21']
Chinese,4,6,[2062426],['i51ep9w'],['i51aj7a'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T03:12:52']
Chinese,6,8,[2169477],"['i5xgksi', 'i5yk6eu']",['0'],['NORP'],-0.34,0.0,-0.34,0,1,1,"['2022-04-23T22:13:59', '2022-04-24T03:41:12']"
Chomsky,1,7,[2345105],['i7kiezf'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T16:05:15']
Chris,8,0,"[552242, 825466]","['i31oh98', 'i2s4kg9', 'i31ph5a']",['0'],['PERSON'],1.8851,1.8851,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-03-30T23:34:07', '2022-04-01T23:31:32', '2022-04-01T23:23:26']"
Chris,8,9,[639144],['i30fz1z'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.6808,0.6808,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-01T18:01:13']
Chris Rock,4,9,[1511077],['i3bzjxi'],['i3aewf7'],['PERSON'],0.1531,0.1531,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-04T09:37:19']
Chris Rock,8,0,"[552242, 825466]","['i32fxd9', 'i2s50ca']","['0', 'i31tjf7']","['PERSON', 'GPE']",-0.7506,0.0,-0.7506,0,1,1,"['2022-03-30T23:37:31', '2022-04-02T03:18:47']"
Chris Rock’s,8,0,[825466],['i321dwb'],['i31tjf7'],['PERSON'],0.2057,0.2057,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T01:11:24']
Chris brown,8,9,[1811789],['i3y0eji'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.8402,0.8402,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-08T19:58:08']
Christian,1,7,[1963245],['i4a5q4p'],['0'],['NORP'],0.2996,0.2996,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11T11:41:57']
Christian,2,6,[1081722],['i3bsd3m'],['0'],['NORP'],0.2415,0.2415,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-04T07:53:40']
Christian,4,8,[494236],['i2ok8k4'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.3612,0.0,-0.3612,0,1,1,['2022-03-30T05:42:05']
Christianity,4,8,[494236],['i2og8ka'],['i2lwyze'],['NORP'],0.5849,0.5849,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-30T04:57:49']
Christians,4,9,[1511077],['i3ag1jn'],['0'],['NORP'],0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-04T00:14:27']
Christine Lambrecht,4,9,[1258901],"['i3cikkq', 'i3cikc6', 'i3cikzt']",['0'],['PERSON'],-0.8196,0.0,-0.8196,0,3,3,"['2022-04-04T13:02:53', '2022-04-04T13:02:50', '2022-04-04T13:02:59']"
Church,4,9,[1511077],['i3aj25e'],['i3afx0o'],['ORG'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T00:37:20']
Cisco,4,9,[1511077],['i3ajwtb'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T00:43:51']
City Council,5,2,[2313930],['i6newt6'],['0'],['ORG'],0.6705,0.6705,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-29T10:43:08']
Civil Guard,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3cq224'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T14:01:26']
Civilian,1,7,[2345105],['i7kfk47'],['i7kfa7w'],['NORP'],-0.9245,0.0,-0.9245,0,1,1,['2022-05-06T15:46:26']
Civilian Houses,1,7,[2041615],['i4wmptf'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-16T01:36:23']
Clarence,2,4,[439459],['i2je77h'],['0'],['ORG'],0.431,0.431,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T07:36:42']
Clarence Thomas,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['PERSON'],1.6418,1.6418,0.0,3,0,3,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
Clayton County,2,3,[340497],['i2glolb'],['i29vfbv'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-28T17:22:14']
Clinton,0,2,[2292360],"['i6x9qew', 'i6wi0io']",['0'],['PERSON'],-0.3257,0.0,-0.3257,0,1,1,"['2022-05-01T16:56:25', '2022-05-01T13:22:29']"
Clinton,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Cmon,6,1,[1480953],['i3l1cek'],['0'],['ORG'],0.2732,0.2732,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T03:58:16']
Cobra Kai,8,0,[825466],['i32h4jo'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.1779,0.0,-0.1779,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T03:29:58']
Cody Hall,2,3,[340497],['i2aoj0o'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.5994,0.5994,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-27T09:44:34']
Colorado,2,3,[340497],['i2aly99'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-27T09:07:12']
Colorado,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['GPE'],1.2248,1.2248,0.0,2,0,2,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
Columbia,6,1,[1480953],['i3m0ccs'],['i3letdr'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T11:09:09']
Combine,4,9,[1787828],['i3zyf4i'],['i3ymba6'],['NORP'],0.9468,0.9468,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-09T05:00:10']
Commie,4,0,[1093474],['i38011z'],['i37d0t2'],['PERSON'],-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T13:39:41']
Committee,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['ORG'],-1.4561,0.0,-1.4561,0,3,3,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
Congo,1,7,[1907918],['i44vp4i'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.5719,0.0,-0.5719,0,1,1,['2022-04-10T06:43:15']
Congress,2,4,"[439459, 800487]","['i31eqdp', 'i2j5jrf', 'i34i6hh', 'i33klgy', 'i34l56p']","['i33klgy', '0']",['ORG'],-1.7934,0.5267,-2.3200999999999996,1,6,7,"['2022-04-02T17:03:12', '2022-04-02T11:58:17', '2022-04-02T16:42:11', '2022-04-01T22:06:18', '2022-03-29T05:41:39']"
Congress,2,7,[1138187],"['i36omt5', 'i364qdg', 'i38bktu', 'i3aut79']",['0'],['ORG'],0.4019,0.4019,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-03T04:13:58', '2022-04-03T01:22:31', '2022-04-03T15:10:31', '2022-04-04T02:07:24']"
Congress,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['ORG'],-1.539,0.0,-1.5390000000000001,0,3,3,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
Congress,6,1,[1480953],"['i3k9i11', 'i3iy2a9', 'i3k7b5n', 'i3iyv6q', 'i3kfjd5', 'i3k3y64', 'i3j8mah', 'i3jtcbj', 'i3jxjgn', 'i40if7d', 'i3jtlky', 'i3ja9jo', 'i3jlfyu', 'i3j6zvn']","['i3jifmd', 'i3is6lk', 'i3ixbrg', 'i3j4fs0', 'i3iv393', 'i3j4aad', '0']",['ORG'],-0.7863999999999999,2.1185000000000005,-2.9049,6,8,14,"['2022-04-05T21:27:56', '2022-04-09T09:05:03', '2022-04-06T01:06:27', '2022-04-05T20:07:34', '2022-04-05T19:00:54', '2022-04-06T00:05:06', '2022-04-05T23:40:13', '2022-04-06T00:21:25', '2022-04-05T22:22:51', '2022-04-05T20:17:40', '2022-04-05T19:06:02', '2022-04-05T22:24:40', '2022-04-05T19:57:32', '2022-04-05T22:53:06']"
Connecticut,2,3,[340497],['i2glolb'],['i29vfbv'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-28T17:22:14']
Conservative Black Supreme Court,2,4,[439459],['i2jxw2l'],['0'],['ORG'],0.7906,0.7906,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T11:59:14']
Conservatives,2,4,[439459],['i2k9n76'],['i2j9ygi'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T13:39:44']
Conservatives,6,1,[1480953],['i3josxq'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.25,0.0,-0.25,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T21:50:21']
Contribute,6,1,[1480953],['i3khdcw'],['i3k93b8'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T01:20:08']
Corey,5,2,[2313930],['i6nqlzq'],['i6nfh1i'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-29T12:41:30']
Coronavirus kinda,6,1,[1480953],['i3mfilk'],['i3iqdoo'],['PERSON'],-0.576,0.0,-0.576,0,1,1,['2022-04-06T13:24:37']
Cortez,2,7,[1138187],['i36wlyy'],['i367a64'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T05:36:29']
Costco,6,1,[1480953],['i4fvzhm'],['i3ywr6j'],['ORG'],0.6249,0.6249,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-12T15:44:07']
Cotton,0,2,[2292360],['i6yj8qn'],['i6yj681'],['PERSON'],-0.3612,0.0,-0.3612,0,1,1,['2022-05-01T22:27:22']
Council,4,3,[1682674],['i3s6pvx'],['0'],['ORG'],0.4003,0.4003,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-07T16:50:40']
Cover Up Tracks,4,9,[1694081],['i3tpl1j'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-07T22:49:38']
Covid,0,1,[2021946],['i4ggeam'],['i4g4opl'],['PERSON'],-0.4939,0.0,-0.4939,0,1,1,['2022-04-12T17:50:29']
Covid,0,2,[2292360],"['i6yaq51', 'i6xstec', 'i6yj681', 'i6x6qrx']","['0', 'i6x2ze0']",['PERSON'],-0.609,0.0,-0.609,0,2,2,"['2022-05-01T19:13:18', '2022-05-01T16:35:04', '2022-05-01T21:23:02', '2022-05-01T22:26:51']"
Covid,0,9,[2060872],['i574z3p'],['i54sk9p'],['PERSON'],-0.5423,0.0,-0.5423,0,1,1,['2022-04-18T11:53:30']
Covid,6,1,[1480953],"['i3lae9c', 'i3k7jjf', 'i3iywvg', 'i3kv62q', 'i3ivepx', 'i3j6zma', 'i3mdfm3', 'i3lr9to', 'i3jv302']","['i3iravh', '0', 'i3iywvg']","['PERSON', 'GPE']",1.5783,2.8977,-1.3194,4,2,6,"['2022-04-06T00:06:52', '2022-04-05T22:35:16', '2022-04-06T05:28:42', '2022-04-06T13:08:59', '2022-04-06T03:04:54', '2022-04-05T19:06:20', '2022-04-05T19:57:30', '2022-04-06T09:11:50', '2022-04-05T18:43:44']"
Covid,6,2,"[559922, 2235430]","['i6fbr4q', 'i6hm40s', 'i6fkyx9', 'i6h137p', 'i2vtd9t', 'i6fh8gl', 'i6gia6a']","['i6f9u28', 'i2vq5zq', '0']","['PERSON', 'GPE']",-2.546,0.0,-2.546,0,4,4,"['2022-04-27T18:25:45', '2022-04-28T03:11:32', '2022-04-27T22:08:07', '2022-04-27T18:00:37', '2022-04-27T17:24:24', '2022-04-28T00:32:45', '2022-03-31T18:55:38']"
Covid,6,8,[2169477],['i5yjzx1'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.6644,0.0,-0.6644,0,2,2,['2022-04-24T03:39:31']
Covid,7,6,[623485],['i2vfln8'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0258,0.0258,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-31T17:28:05']
Covid &,6,2,[2235430],['i6fkyx9'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,['2022-04-27T18:25:45']
Covidian,0,7,[2354712],['i7wfkpo'],['0'],['NORP'],0.6124,0.6124,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-09T09:38:28']
Cowboys,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3drkg6'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T18:09:55']
Crash Hill,4,6,[2062426],['i5m8m5v'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.7003,0.0,-0.7003,0,1,1,['2022-04-21T13:59:36']
Cretan,4,0,[1093474],['i37kn0f'],['i378925'],['GPE'],-0.34,0.0,-0.34,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T10:54:04']
Cretans,4,0,[1093474],['i37kn0f'],['i378925'],['NORP'],-0.34,0.0,-0.34,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T10:54:04']
Crimea,1,0,[2241438],['i605yuo'],['i6042z1'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-24T14:31:58']
Crimea,1,1,[1998813],['i4gcz1h'],['i4g8ddj'],['ORG'],0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-12T17:29:20']
Crimea,1,7,"[2053825, 2345105]","['i7jc2fa', 'i5224r8']",['0'],['PERSON'],-1.3138,0.0,-1.3138,0,2,2,"['2022-04-17T07:28:04', '2022-05-06T10:13:40']"
Crimea,4,0,[1093474],['i37cg08'],['0'],['ORG'],0.2263,0.2263,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T09:01:19']
Crimea,4,6,[2155952],['i5vpn5u'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-23T14:22:06']
Crimea,4,8,[517355],['i2nn1gr'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-30T00:50:58']
Crimea,7,4,[757828],['i3ctr24'],['i3bngqz'],['ORG'],-0.5556,0.0,-0.5556,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T14:27:42']
Cuba,4,8,[426218],['i2by5p4'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-27T16:48:53']
Curt Taylor,4,6,[2062426],['i51mtaw'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.7506,0.7506,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17T04:26:56']
Czech,4,6,[1549013],['i2z3c28'],['i2yjyk4'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T12:21:26']
Czech Technical University,4,6,[1549013],['i2z3c28'],['i2yjyk4'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T12:21:26']
D.C.,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['GPE'],1.684,1.684,0.0,2,0,2,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
DC,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['GPE'],0.2732,0.2732,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
DCF,6,1,[1480953],['i3ksz5t'],['i3j6zma'],['ORG'],-0.5719,0.0,-0.5719,0,1,1,['2022-04-06T02:47:11']
DJT,0,2,[2292360],['i74od6l'],['i6whp7m'],['ORG'],0.5106,0.5106,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-03T06:26:07']
DL,6,1,[1480953],['i3mew7c'],['0'],['ORG'],0.5859,0.5859,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T13:20:02']
DMZ,1,2,[704263],['i334wvm'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T08:20:22']
DMZ,4,8,[517355],['i2oz0g8'],['i2nn1gr'],['ORG'],0.2382,0.2382,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-30T09:02:34']
DNC,6,1,[1480953],"['i3jz9bg', 'i3jpo5p', 'i3jua5r']","['i3is6lk', '0']",['ORG'],-0.2192,0.4019,-0.6211,1,2,3,"['2022-04-05T23:05:43', '2022-04-05T22:29:34', '2022-04-05T21:56:14']"
DO / DON'T](https://www.reddit.com,1,0,[2279161],['i6stm2n'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-30T15:40:44']
DO / DON'T](https://www.reddit.com,1,7,[2350926],['i7jjqsg'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-06T11:43:11']
DO / DON'T](https://www.reddit.com,4,0,[2150320],"['i5sz2xz', 'i5shz25']",['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-22T21:58:22', '2022-04-22T19:56:27']"
DO / DON'T](https://www.reddit.com,9,5,[2150388],['i5qa5u4'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-22T09:48:39']
DOJ,2,4,[800487],"['i34i6hh', 'i30wbtl', 'i34ffot', 'i39qpxa']",['0'],['ORG'],-0.3163,0.2411,-0.5574,1,1,2,"['2022-04-01T19:53:27', '2022-04-03T21:05:05', '2022-04-02T16:22:17', '2022-04-02T16:42:11']"
DOJ,2,6,[898818],['i34uefd'],['i348xod'],['ORG'],-0.2498,0.0,-0.2498,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T18:09:52']
DOJ,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
DRASTICALLY,4,9,[1787828],['i43d8bg'],['i43asri'],['ORG'],0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-09T22:51:02']
DTI,6,1,[1480953],['i3ldnty'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T06:06:17']
Dahmer,4,6,[2155952],['i5u41up'],['i5tw7ph'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-23T03:22:50']
Dallas,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3drkg6'],['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T18:09:55']
Damn,7,4,[757828],['i3cv2i4'],['i3cj34c'],['PERSON'],-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T14:36:59']
Dan,4,6,[2062426],['i57s2u1'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-18T15:01:12']
Dan Scavino,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.7845,0.0,-0.7845,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
Dan Scavino,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.6369,0.6369,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
Danish,4,9,[2150382],"['i4f0r7p', 'i4jgg29']","['i4f0r7p', '0']",['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-12T11:58:44', '2022-04-13T08:05:48']"
David Beasley,7,9,[1896851],['i2nw6hd'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-30T02:01:23']
David Carter,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.0258,0.0,-0.0258,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
David Perdue,2,3,[340497],['i29ung4'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.3919,0.0,-0.3919,0,1,1,['2022-03-27T03:28:14']
David Rubin,8,0,[825466],['i31syhy'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.0258,0.0,-0.0258,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T00:00:28']
David vs Goliath,1,7,[2350926],['i7ks6wu'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.1531,0.0,-0.1531,0,1,1,['2022-05-06T17:10:47']
DeVos,6,1,[1480953],['i3iu341'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.743,0.743,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-05T18:35:07']
Deep Durbin,2,4,[439459],['i2kgow9'],['i2j5jrf'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T14:29:15']
Defense,2,5,[413890],['i2ibm0m'],['0'],['ORG'],0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T01:05:29']
Defense,4,9,[1258901],"['i3cikkq', 'i3cikc6', 'i3cikzt']",['0'],['ORG'],-0.8196,0.0,-0.8196,0,3,3,"['2022-04-04T13:02:53', '2022-04-04T13:02:50', '2022-04-04T13:02:59']"
Del Ponte,4,8,[959740],['i34cpuo'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.9313,0.0,-0.9313,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T16:01:52']
Delaware,2,3,[340497],['i2glolb'],['i29vfbv'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-28T17:22:14']
Delaware,4,1,[943443],['i3ek78r'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.0516,0.0,-0.0516,0,1,1,['2022-04-04T21:11:07']
Delta,0,1,[2021946],['i4glido'],['i4g6eof'],['ORG'],-0.25,0.0,-0.25,0,1,1,['2022-04-12T18:22:22']
Dem,2,7,[1138187],['i35h2nb'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.3566,0.0,-0.3566,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T21:11:49']
Dem,6,1,[1480953],"['i3ja9jo', 'i3m0ou1', 'i3l2uz9', 'i3mfilk']","['i3kfjd5', 'i3iqdoo', '0', 'i3iv393']",['NORP'],0.6222000000000001,0.9971000000000001,-0.3749,3,1,4,"['2022-04-06T11:13:03', '2022-04-05T20:17:40', '2022-04-06T04:12:16', '2022-04-06T13:24:37']"
Dem,7,6,[623485],['i2vkylh'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-31T18:01:47']
Dem Midterm,6,1,[1480953],['i3nyclu'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T19:16:58']
Democrat,2,3,[340497],['i2aoj0o'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.7184,0.0,-0.7184,0,1,1,['2022-03-27T09:44:34']
Democrat,2,4,"[439459, 800487]","['i2j5jrf', 'i30wbtl']",['0'],['NORP'],-0.3311,0.2263,-0.5574,1,1,2,"['2022-04-01T19:53:27', '2022-03-29T05:41:39']"
Democrat,2,6,[898818],['i34dlp7'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.4754,0.0,-0.4754,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T16:08:31']
Democrat,6,1,[1480953],"['i3krr9e', 'i3jgi8t', 'i3lz8ra']","['i3is6lk', '0']",['NORP'],0.8981,0.8981,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-05T20:56:09', '2022-04-06T02:37:26', '2022-04-06T10:56:40']"
Democratic,0,7,[2354712],['i7vedv1'],['0'],['NORP'],0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-09T02:14:06']
Democratic,0,9,[2060872],['i52uuq6'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17T13:25:37']
Democratic,2,3,[1092237],"['i351zd4', 'i3fep6z', 'i37mmet', 'i3e2blq']",['0'],['NORP'],-0.5574,0.0,-0.5574,0,1,1,"['2022-04-02T19:10:58', '2022-04-04T19:18:59', '2022-04-03T11:20:28', '2022-04-05T00:34:13']"
Democratic,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Democratic,2,5,[413890],['i2j4nnb'],['i2grqgr'],['NORP'],0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T05:31:05']
Democratic,6,1,[1480953],"['i3jxgiw', 'i3jrjos']","['i3joblv', '0']",['NORP'],0.7935,0.7935,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-05T22:09:58', '2022-04-05T22:52:29']"
Democratic House,2,5,[413890],['i2hq2xi'],['i2gc432'],['ORG'],-0.0772,0.0,-0.0772,0,1,1,['2022-03-28T22:05:27']
Democrats,0,2,[2292360],['i6y4b9c'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.0188,0.0,-0.0188,0,2,2,['2022-05-01T20:36:07']
Democrats,2,3,[1092237],"['i3eek8k', 'i35q12a', 'i37mmet']","['i34mum6', '0']",['NORP'],-0.21610000000000007,0.5859,-0.802,1,1,2,"['2022-04-04T20:35:34', '2022-04-02T22:23:26', '2022-04-03T11:20:28']"
Democrats,2,4,[800487],"['i30uxwc', 'i3526pt']","['0', 'i30rtn6']",['NORP'],-0.8627,0.0,-0.8627,0,2,2,"['2022-04-01T19:43:51', '2022-04-02T19:12:43']"
Democrats,2,5,[413890],"['i2j4nnb', 'i2grqgr', 'i2k08nk', 'i2j44kz']","['i2jh0we', 'i2grqgr', 'i2g7m5w', '0']",['NORP'],-1.9307,0.6705,-2.6012000000000004,1,5,6,"['2022-03-29T05:24:44', '2022-03-29T05:31:05', '2022-03-28T18:03:43', '2022-03-29T12:21:39']"
Democrats,2,6,[898818],['i34dlp7'],['0'],['NORP'],0.5779999999999998,1.0534,-0.4754,2,1,3,['2022-04-02T16:08:31']
Democrats,2,7,[1138187],"['i367a64', 'i36wlyy', 'i37xivd']","['i367a64', 'i360eq9', '0']",['NORP'],0.1663,0.6251,-0.4588,2,1,3,"['2022-04-03T01:45:49', '2022-04-03T13:17:19', '2022-04-03T05:36:29']"
Democrats,6,1,[1480953],"['i3iy2a9', 'i3jixqk', 'i3kfzli', 'i3iso1i', 'i3j5skb', 'i3iyoy1', 'i3mz00g', 'i3l1xk1', 'i3j01mz', 'i3jnbx1', 'i3j9jyb', 'i3jwdp4', 'i3jz9bg', 'i3kil9k', 'i4gg35z', 'i3jbele', 'i3kvzaa', 'i3k2fre', 'i3k84w5', 'i3j0bwq', 'i3jd91s', 'i3j47or', 'i3jhund', 'i3iv393', 'i3k77ty', 'i3jrjos', 'i3jdi84']","['i3joblv', 'i3iqdoo', 'i3isx8l', 'i3j0bwq', 'i3ixxge', 'i3ir5uf', 'i3ixx3h', '0', 'i3j6b17', 'i3iv398', 'i3m891u', 'i3j5skb']",['NORP'],0.1335999999999999,5.686800000000001,-5.5531999999999995,14,16,30,"['2022-04-05T20:13:16', '2022-04-06T01:29:02', '2022-04-06T00:04:25', '2022-04-05T23:29:01', '2022-04-06T01:09:53', '2022-04-05T18:25:43', '2022-04-05T22:44:38', '2022-04-05T20:36:05', '2022-04-05T21:40:30', '2022-04-05T21:11:31', '2022-04-05T19:04:56', '2022-04-05T19:40:15', '2022-04-06T15:36:31', '2022-04-05T18:41:41', '2022-04-05T19:15:32', '2022-04-12T17:48:35', '2022-04-05T19:50:04', '2022-04-05T22:09:58', '2022-04-05T20:24:42', '2022-04-05T23:05:43', '2022-04-05T20:37:40', '2022-04-05T19:00:54', '2022-04-06T04:03:36', '2022-04-06T00:11:17', '2022-04-06T03:11:40', '2022-04-05T19:13:41', '2022-04-05T21:04:36']"
Democrats,6,9,[623417],['i2vh53s'],['i2uv72n'],['NORP'],0.4046,0.4046,0.0,2,0,2,['2022-03-31T17:37:54']
Democrats,7,6,[623485],"['i2vnn5t', 'i2v33vg']","['i2uzcx0', '0']",['NORP'],-0.7746999999999999,0.0772,-0.8519,1,1,2,"['2022-03-31T16:09:07', '2022-03-31T18:18:53']"
Demoncrats,7,6,[623485],['i2w1p9l'],['i2vtp0p'],['PERSON'],-0.6597,0.0,-0.6597,0,1,1,['2022-03-31T19:49:43']
Dems,2,4,[439459],['i2j6omh'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T05:55:20']
Dems,2,5,[413890],"['i2hkyz0', 'i2j44kz']","['i2g7m5w', '0']",['NORP'],-0.9084000000000001,0.0,-0.9084000000000001,0,2,2,"['2022-03-29T05:24:44', '2022-03-28T21:25:23']"
Dems,2,7,[1138187],['i36wlyy'],['i367a64'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T05:36:29']
Dems,6,1,[1480953],"['i3meggo', 'i3ixbrg', 'i3ku9so', 'i3kfs80', 'i3m9qjr', 'i3m0u4w', 'i3jx07n', 'i3n8p2a', 'i3lon3e', 'i3j01mz', 'i3jh223', 'i3kvtpi', 'i3jzh8j', 'i3kncqw', 'i3m0ou1', 'i3kwz9c', 'i3lsrde', 'i3k7j3t', 'i3mfvt9', 'i3jivhm', 'i3k338c', 'i3mfilk', 'i3k4n4z', 'i3kqsqk', 'i3jevst', 'i3jl3gh', 'i3jkdm0']","['i3jnfer', 'i3ir7i1', 'i3iqdoo', 'i3is6lk', 'i3kfjd5', 'i3l2itp', 'i3ir5uf', '0', 'i3ken8d', 'i3j5skb']",['NORP'],5.0714,7.739800000000002,-2.6683999999999997,17,10,27,"['2022-04-06T03:10:22', '2022-04-06T13:27:18', '2022-04-06T03:19:58', '2022-04-06T00:06:46', '2022-04-06T11:14:48', '2022-04-05T21:20:54', '2022-04-06T11:13:03', '2022-04-06T09:33:02', '2022-04-06T02:03:40', '2022-04-05T20:59:34', '2022-04-05T21:25:37', '2022-04-05T23:33:50', '2022-04-05T21:11:08', '2022-04-05T22:49:11', '2022-04-06T02:57:38', '2022-04-05T23:07:20', '2022-04-06T13:24:37', '2022-04-06T08:33:55', '2022-04-06T16:38:19', '2022-04-06T12:39:19', '2022-04-06T01:08:19', '2022-04-06T02:29:50', '2022-04-06T13:16:48', '2022-04-05T18:56:10', '2022-04-05T19:13:41', '2022-04-05T20:46:13', '2022-04-05T23:45:19']"
Dems,6,9,[623417],"['i2vn391', 'i2vcdeg']","['i2v8up7', 'i2uca92']",['NORP'],-0.049400000000000006,0.0516,-0.101,1,1,2,"['2022-03-31T17:07:27', '2022-03-31T18:15:19']"
Denisova,4,6,[2062426],['i4zd0l5'],['i4ylf4z'],['GPE'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-16T17:42:46']
Denisovans,4,6,[2062426],['i4zd0l5'],['i4ylf4z'],['NORP'],-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-16T17:42:46']
Denmark,1,7,[2041615],['i4y2438'],['i4wy8kj'],['GPE'],-0.7939,0.0,-0.7939,0,1,1,['2022-04-16T11:23:50']
Denmark,3,8,[425465],['i2ioalj'],['i2fv5sk'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T02:48:19']
Denmark,4,7,[2023465],['i4ta70i'],['i4skc2a'],['GPE'],0.1413000000000001,0.7717,-0.6304,1,1,2,['2022-04-15T09:41:25']
Denmark,4,9,[2150382],['i4jgg29'],['i4f0r7p'],['GPE'],0.5499,0.5499,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-13T08:05:48']
Denovian,4,6,[2062426],"['i4ylf4z', 'i5m8m5v', 'i51s5y1']",['0'],['NORP'],-1.8747,0.0,-1.8747,0,3,3,"['2022-04-17T05:23:13', '2022-04-16T14:27:58', '2022-04-21T13:59:36']"
Denovians,4,6,[2062426],"['i4ylf4z', 'i5m8m5v', 'i4zd0l5']","['i4ylf4z', '0']",['NORP'],-1.9884,0.0,-1.9884,0,3,3,"['2022-04-16T14:27:58', '2022-04-16T17:42:46', '2022-04-21T13:59:36']"
Denys,1,7,[2350926],['i7k68ir'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-05-06T14:43:47']
Denys Prokopenko,1,7,[2350926],['i7k68ir'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.6369,0.6369,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T14:43:47']
Dick Cheney,2,9,[419795],['i2kwko6'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.5106,0.0,-0.5106,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T16:13:29']
Dick Durbin,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.2263,0.2263,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
Dickens,0,9,[2060872],['i54z8qb'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.2732,0.2732,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17T22:36:11']
Ding Ding Ding,6,1,[1480953],['i3kelf6'],['i3k4s7l'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T00:59:30']
Direct Consolidation Loan,6,1,[1480953],['i3msm2a'],['i3k56ks'],['ORG'],0.743,0.743,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T14:54:58']
Direct Subsidized,6,1,[1480953],['i3msm2a'],['i3k56ks'],['ORG'],0.743,0.743,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T14:54:58']
DirectLoans,6,1,[1480953],['i3k6kwt'],['0'],['NORP'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T23:59:41']
Disney,8,9,[1811789],['i3y7ems'],['i3y3ojy'],['ORG'],-0.3679,0.0,-0.3679,0,1,1,['2022-04-08T20:44:28']
Djibouti,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3clwxe'],['i3cfg61'],['GPE'],2.8956,2.8956,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-04T13:29:56']
Dmitry Medvedev,4,9,[2042107],['i4m521r'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.4215,0.0,-0.4215,0,1,1,['2022-04-13T20:51:30']
Dmitry Peskov,3,8,[425465],"['i2fvkgj', 'i2g0wyo']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.2935,0.4215,-0.128,1,1,2,"['2022-03-28T14:24:49', '2022-03-28T15:02:38']"
Dmitry Shkrebets,4,6,[2155952],['i5tmryk'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.1531,0.0,-0.1531,0,1,1,['2022-04-23T01:00:31']
Dnipropetrovsk,1,7,[2262917],"['i6nt096', 'i6nt20g']",['0'],['GPE'],0.743,0.743,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-29T13:01:38', '2022-04-29T13:02:02']"
DoD,4,9,[1787828],['i43zmg4'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.659,0.0,-0.659,0,1,1,['2022-04-10T01:49:55']
DoE,6,1,[1480953],['i3mbo5y'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.0516,0.0,-0.0516,0,1,1,['2022-04-06T12:55:06']
Dombas,1,7,[429128],['i2lnk71'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T19:03:02']
Don Young,2,7,[1138187],"['i324j7f', 'i360eq9']",['0'],['PERSON'],-1.4167,0.0,-1.4167,0,2,2,"['2022-04-02T01:38:02', '2022-04-02T23:48:09']"
Donald,4,8,[517355],['i2pr0j5'],['i2m90zj'],['PERSON'],0.6486,0.6486,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-30T13:53:40']
Donald Trump,0,2,[2292360],['i6yj681'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.0772,0.0,-0.0772,0,1,1,['2022-05-01T22:26:51']
Donald Trump,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.2732,0.2732,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Donald Trump,2,9,[419795],['i2iek9l'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.4939,0.0,-0.4939,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T01:29:18']
Donald Trump,4,9,[1787828],['i42yump'],['i42uebt'],['PERSON'],0.7506,0.7506,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-09T21:05:10']
Donald Trump Jr.,7,7,[1227715],['i3h6o6v'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-05T11:30:29']
Donbas,1,0,[2242251],['i5g4pcy'],['i5g2eje'],['PERSON'],0.6808,0.6808,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-20T05:45:53']
Donbas,1,1,[2094538],['i5812rt'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.749,0.0,-0.749,0,1,1,['2022-04-18T16:01:52']
Donbas,1,2,"[2325276, 704263]","['i77rfon', 'i77rfgr', 'i33ezwx']","['i32bqk2', '0']",['GPE'],-0.843,0.0,-0.843,0,2,2,"['2022-05-03T22:00:47', '2022-04-02T10:48:18', '2022-05-03T22:00:50']"
Donbas,1,7,"[2053825, 1907918]","['i50j61c', 'i44ruhw']","['i4zrqcu', '0']",['GPE'],-0.6449,0.1396,-0.7845,1,1,2,"['2022-04-10T06:01:29', '2022-04-16T22:57:45']"
Donbas,4,7,[1587993],"['i3n9v9z', 'i3n9v1f']",['0'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-06T16:45:39', '2022-04-06T16:45:41']"
Donbas,4,9,[1787828],"['i3yqjas', 'i43tnv1', 'i3yu6yg']","['i42ujw2', 'i3ynn6q', '0']",['GPE'],0.8811,1.5129000000000001,-0.6317999999999999,2,2,4,"['2022-04-08T23:23:37', '2022-04-10T01:00:59', '2022-04-08T22:56:55']"
Donbas,9,3,[2104843],['i5g37mf'],['i5fybpx'],['GPE'],-0.8271,0.0,-0.8271,0,1,1,['2022-04-20T05:29:05']
Donbas,9,7,[560493],['i2s20wi'],['i2s1xa9'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-30T23:14:41']
Donbass,4,9,[1787828],['i3znxb1'],['i3zmm87'],['PERSON'],-0.3818,0.0,-0.3818,0,1,1,['2022-04-09T03:20:26']
Donetsk,9,3,[2104843],"['i5g0lrx', 'i5g0llx']",['0'],['GPE'],-1.6352,0.0,-1.6352,0,2,2,"['2022-04-20T05:00:49', '2022-04-20T05:00:52']"
Doubt,9,2,[1936012],['i49i1i6'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.3612,0.0,-0.3612,0,1,1,['2022-04-11T06:38:17']
Doug Emhoff,6,9,[676909],['i2xgdqk'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01T01:43:40']
Doug Jones,2,4,[800487],"['i30orqp', 'i30na8k']","['0', 'i30na8k']",['PERSON'],1.1000999999999999,1.1000999999999999,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-01T19:01:19', '2022-04-01T18:51:01']"
Doug Lute,1,0,[2241438],['i60ldyh'],['i60l8ag'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-24T16:20:17']
Draft,4,6,[1549013],['i305u89'],['0'],['ORG'],0.4588,0.4588,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-01T16:55:17']
Drill,7,6,[623485],['i2v1gx8'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-31T15:58:33']
Drop,2,4,[439459],['i2j8o8i'],['i2j5v2e'],['PERSON'],-0.5106,0.0,-0.5106,0,1,1,['2022-03-29T06:20:46']
Dua Lipa,8,9,[1811789],['i3y3cjh'],['i3xz9ia'],['PERSON'],0.7351,0.7351,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-08T20:17:47']
Dubna,4,8,[426218],['i2by5p4'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.3182,0.0,-0.3182,0,1,1,['2022-03-27T16:48:53']
Dugin,4,7,[2023465],['i4t7ddc'],['i4sh1gi'],['PERSON'],0.7845,0.7845,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-15T09:00:30']
Dunkirk,1,7,[2345105],['i7kmbhf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.5106,0.5106,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-06T16:31:03']
Dunleavy(Governor,2,7,[1138187],['i37xivd'],['i360eq9'],['ORG'],0.0258,0.0258,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03T13:17:19']
Durbin,2,4,[439459],['i2j5jrf'],['0'],['PERSON'],1.6324,1.6323999999999999,0.0,3,0,3,['2022-03-29T05:41:39']
Dutch,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3gpwyl'],['0'],['NORP'],0.3088,0.3088,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-05T07:52:16']
EASILY,6,1,[1480953],['i3k6xmb'],['0'],['ORG'],0.8531,0.8531,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T00:02:18']
ECB,7,4,[757828],"['i3bn7gk', 'i3bmsn9', 'i3bngqz', 'i3bykn2']","['i3blrh3', '0']",['ORG'],1.4069,1.6480000000000001,-0.2411,3,1,4,"['2022-04-04T06:46:55', '2022-04-04T06:38:15', '2022-04-04T06:43:34', '2022-04-04T09:23:39']"
ED,6,1,[1480953],['i3iu341'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.7574,0.7574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-05T18:35:07']
EF,1,2,[704263],['i32fset'],['i32buzn'],['GPE'],0.3612,0.3612,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-02T03:17:30']
EITC,6,1,[1480953],['i3k3a0x'],['i3jtcwp'],['ORG'],-0.1027,0.0,-0.1027,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T23:35:13']
END,6,1,[1480953],['i3kwz9c'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06T03:19:58']
EO,6,1,[1480953],['i3jhund'],['i3j0bwq'],['ORG'],-0.4019,0.0,-0.4019,0,1,1,['2022-04-05T21:04:36']
EPAYE,6,1,[1480953],['i3k7b5n'],['i3j4fs0'],['ORG'],0.5875,0.5875,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T00:05:06']
ESPECIALLY,0,1,[2021946],['i4hfeen'],['i4g4opl'],['ORG'],0.4588,0.4588,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-12T21:30:31']
ETA,8,0,[825466],['i31tjf7'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T00:05:20']
EU,1,0,[1860324],"['i429v64', 'i427v4b', 'i427vzc', 'i41hc08']",['0'],['ORG'],-2.3976,0.0,-2.3976,0,4,4,"['2022-04-09T14:55:09', '2022-04-09T17:53:42', '2022-04-09T18:07:03', '2022-04-09T17:53:52']"
EU,1,7,"[1011081, 2053825, 1907918]","['i39b6lc', 'i50bwn1', 'i3ahm1e', 'i44ruhw']","['i4zsemd', '0']",['ORG'],-1.2271999999999998,0.0,-1.2271999999999998,0,3,3,"['2022-04-16T22:03:36', '2022-04-03T19:17:09', '2022-04-04T00:26:24', '2022-04-10T06:01:29']"
EU,2,4,[800487],['i33nkxw'],['i33fktr'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T12:30:53']
EU,2,6,[1081722],['i3bsd3m'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T07:53:40']
EU,3,0,[2311760],['i71jk2o'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-02T16:08:42']
EU,3,2,"[2231218, 2241325]","['i6fxt5b', 'i6e72wi']",['0'],['ORG'],-0.0258,0.0,-0.0258,0,1,1,"['2022-04-27T12:47:13', '2022-04-27T19:50:36']"
EU,3,8,[425465],"['i2g2wky', 'i2hdkng', 'i2ioalj']","['i2fv5sk', '0', 'i2g0d0m']",['ORG'],0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-03-29T02:48:19', '2022-03-28T20:34:21', '2022-03-28T15:16:42']"
EU,4,0,[1093474],['i37nn12'],['i37bv7t'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T11:33:24']
EU,4,2,"[1878824, 528021]","['i433b66', 'i439v0z', 'i2t0x40']","['i42g1ev', '0', 'i42dnwo']",['ORG'],-0.6188,0.2896,-0.9084000000000001,1,2,3,"['2022-04-09T21:37:27', '2022-04-09T22:25:42', '2022-03-31T03:47:58']"
EU,4,4,[2024078],['i4q48gf'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-14T17:25:21']
EU,4,6,[2023525],['i4mfpk7'],['i4lmcw5'],['ORG'],0.3291,0.3291,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-13T22:01:40']
EU,4,7,"[1587993, 2023465]","['i4ta70i', 'i4sh1gi', 'i3n71wx', 'i4syd9l', 'i4skc2a']","['i3n553k', 'i4skc2a', '0']",['ORG'],-0.7491,1.6714,-2.4205,3,5,8,"['2022-04-15T09:41:25', '2022-04-06T16:27:24', '2022-04-15T06:55:03', '2022-04-15T03:41:11', '2022-04-15T04:11:51']"
EU,4,8,"[517355, 959740]","['i2l0orw', 'i34ese0']",['0'],['ORG'],0.359,0.655,-0.296,2,1,3,"['2022-03-29T16:39:26', '2022-04-02T16:17:29']"
EU,4,9,"[1024713, 2042107, 1787828]","['i431kge', 'i4m9huw', 'i401nvc', 'i382txf', 'i3yofkt']","['0', 'i42s3it']",['ORG'],0.2840999999999999,1.4266,-1.1425,3,3,6,"['2022-04-09T05:35:33', '2022-04-09T21:24:50', '2022-04-03T14:03:24', '2022-04-08T22:41:40', '2022-04-13T21:20:00']"
EU,7,4,[757828],"['i3bn7gk', 'i3bykn2', 'i3bngqz', 'i3ctr24', 'i3azf1r']","['i3bngqz', 'i3blrh3', '0']",['ORG'],0.8255,1.4837,-0.6582,3,2,5,"['2022-04-04T06:46:55', '2022-04-04T09:23:39', '2022-04-04T06:43:34', '2022-04-04T02:44:08', '2022-04-04T14:27:42']"
EU,9,3,[2104843],['i5fzie6'],['0'],['ORG'],-0.9493,0.0,-0.9493,0,1,1,['2022-04-20T04:49:35']
EUA,6,2,[2235430],['i6jgr7a'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0772,0.0772,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-28T14:54:41']
EVERYONE,6,1,[1480953],['i3ouwo5'],['0'],['ORG'],0.4767,0.4767,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T22:46:14']
EVRYONE,4,0,[1093474],['i399qq0'],['i388cff'],['ORG'],-0.9325,0.0,-0.9325,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T19:07:36']
Eastasia,1,1,[1998813],['i4g8rc2'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-04-12T17:03:20']
Eastern,1,7,[2345105],['i7jc2fa'],['0'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-06T10:13:40']
Eastern,4,8,[494236],['i2mcug4'],['i2lwyze'],['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T21:41:26']
Eastern European,4,9,[1276661],"['i3cz18p', 'i3cyhkp']",['0'],['NORP'],-1.486,0.0,-1.486,0,2,2,"['2022-04-04T15:00:28', '2022-04-04T15:04:14']"
Eastman,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['PERSON'],-0.21200000000000002,0.128,-0.34,1,1,2,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Ecumenical Patriarch/of Constantinople,4,8,[494236],"['i2m4yup', 'i2m3i12']","['i2m27rc', 'i2m04kf']",['ORG'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-03-29T20:52:59', '2022-03-29T20:43:36']"
Ed,6,1,[1480953],['i3lbcc6'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.5719,0.5719,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06T05:39:13']
Eddie Lampert's,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3e1ooj'],['i3drkg6'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T19:14:58']
Eddy Etue,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.6124,0.6124,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
Egypt,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3clwxe'],['i3cfg61'],['GPE'],2.8956,2.8956,0.0,4,0,4,['2022-04-04T13:29:56']
Egypt,4,8,[494236],['i2m7w4q'],['i2lwyze'],['GPE'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29T21:12:17']
Egypt,6,8,[1679152],['i3sdkor'],['i3scewa'],['GPE'],-0.7783,0.0,-0.7783,0,1,1,['2022-04-07T17:35:33']
Egyre,2,6,[1081722],['i39y6j3'],['i39xic2'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03T21:58:49']
Elaine Luria,2,4,[800487],['i33klgy'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-02T11:58:17']
Elon Musk,7,2,[1279574],['i3cx7q7'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.1027,0.1027,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-04T14:51:45']
Elon Musk's,7,2,[1279574],['i3cx7q7'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-04T14:51:45']
Emmanuel Macron,4,6,[2023525],"['i4lp1yn', 'i4lm8uo']",['0'],['PERSON'],0.8038,0.8038,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-13T18:45:01', '2022-04-13T19:03:08']"
Emmy Awards,8,9,[1811789],['i3y69ry'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.7245,0.7245,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-08T20:36:54']
England,1,7,[2350926],['i7kbjtj'],['i7k40g8'],['GPE'],-0.3818,0.0,-0.3818,0,1,1,['2022-05-06T15:19:44']
Enjoy,1,0,[2242251],['i5fxakd'],['0'],['GPE'],0.7351,0.7351,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-20T04:28:08']
Eric Adams,5,2,[2313930],['i6nqlzq'],['i6nfh1i'],['PERSON'],0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-29T12:41:30']
Eric Garner,5,2,[2313930],['i6nqlzq'],['i6nfh1i'],['PERSON'],-1.8786,0.0,-1.8786,0,2,2,['2022-04-29T12:41:30']
Ernest Hemingway's,4,6,"[1296929, 1251068]",['i3fw2d6'],['i3cub6u'],['PERSON'],-1.7616,0.0,-1.7616,0,4,4,['2022-04-05T02:41:27']
Ethiopia,4,0,[2150320],['i5r615d'],['i5r37k4'],['GPE'],-1.2738,0.0,-1.2738,0,2,2,['2022-04-22T14:41:25']
Etue,4,1,[2346100],['i6yyv27'],['0'],['PERSON'],0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-02T00:33:22']
Eurasia,1,1,[1998813],['i4g8rc2'],['0'],['GPE'],-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-04-12T17:03:20']
Europe& USA,4,0,[1093474],['i38u54m'],['i37d0t2'],['ORG'],-0.6641,0.0,-0.6641,0,1,1,['2022-04-03T17:20:25']
European,1,0,[2170124],['i5qr1b2'],['i5pnu2f'],['NORP'],-0.7717,0.0,-0.7717,0,1,1,['2022-04-22T12:50:40']
European,1,1,[1998813],['i4go5n2'],['i4gn9f0'],['NORP'],-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-04-12T18:38:57']
European,1,7,[1907918],"['i44vp4i', 'i44rdpm']",['0'],['NORP'],-0.17719999999999997,0.2247,-0.4019,1,1,2,"['2022-04-10T06:43:15', '2022-04-10T05:56:20']"
European,1,9,[2208607],['i5iwrn1'],['0'],['NORP'],-0.5859,0.0,-0.5859,0,1,1,['2022-04-20T20:02:56']
European,3,8,[425465],"['i2fvkgj', 'i2g0wyo']",['0'],['NORP'],0.2935,0.4215,-0.128,1,1,2,"['2022-03-28T14:24:49', '2022-03-28T15:02:38']"
European,4,2,[1878824],"['i4299f6', 'i42gg3s']","['i42gbcg', '0']",['NORP'],3.84,3.8400000000000003,0.0,5,0,5,"['2022-04-09T18:52:20', '2022-04-09T18:03:00']"
European,4,6,[2023525],"['i4lag6g', 'i4lp1yn']","['i4l8xwj', '0']",['NORP'],-1.4432,0.0,-1.4432,0,2,2,"['2022-04-13T19:03:08', '2022-04-13T17:30:22']"
European,4,7,"[1470385, 2023465]","['i3iya3j', 'i3iyady', 'i3issr4', 'i4sfj4v']","['i4sdmdl', '0']",['NORP'],0.19599999999999995,0.6486,-0.4526,1,2,3,"['2022-04-05T19:02:20', '2022-04-05T19:02:17', '2022-04-15T03:27:47', '2022-04-05T18:26:34']"
