node_id,article_id,entity,entity_type,cluster,topic,sum_sentiment,sum_pos,sum_neg,weight_pos,weight_neg,weight,downloaded_date
0,"[2115330, 1330472, 512396, 1092237, 676909, 419795, 1438965, 2339286, 623417, 457434, 597596]",Florida,['GPE'],0,9,-1.283,0.87,-2.153,4,7,11,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-19', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-04', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-03-31']"
1,"[2339287, 516006, 2348780, 2186286, 2284154, 524887, 457434, 2353054]",FDA,['ORG'],0,9,1.6007000000000002,3.5932,-1.9925000000000002,9,5,14,"['2022-05-05', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06']"
2,[457434],Fla.,['GPE'],0,9,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-29']
3,"[1596545, 898818, 2292360, 510857, 512396, 1092237, 340497, 449428, 1497495, 821274, 1330472, 428457, 676909, 1092926, 413890, 1281862, 419795, 457434, 597596, 1138141, 1696099, 800487, 2299880, 1438965, 623485]",Republican,['NORP'],0,9,1.7687999999999995,14.103699999999996,-12.334900000000001,30,25,55,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
4,"[457434, 512396, 676909]",Ron DeSantis,['PERSON'],0,9,-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,"['2022-03-30', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-31']"
5,[457434],Ashley Moody,['PERSON'],0,9,-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-03-29']
6,[457434],Tampa,['GPE'],0,9,-1.3209,0.0,-1.3209,0,2,2,['2022-03-29']
8,"[2115330, 2339287, 780740, 2313861, 516006, 2235430, 2060872, 2186286, 1227730, 559922, 2021946, 2339286, 524887, 2194486, 2284154, 457434, 597596, 2353054]",CDC,['ORG'],0,9,2.1300000000000003,8.3137,-6.1837,21,13,34,"['2022-04-19', '2022-05-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31']"
9,"[2115330, 2169477, 2313861, 1240455, 2292360, 2092686, 476817, 623380, 2354712, 2353054, 2008485, 516006, 2235430, 1850283, 524972, 2186286, 793395, 2158132, 2194486, 2021946, 528443, 372284, 780740, 757828, 2060872, 1089225, 728906, 1227730, 2339286, 1845206, 524887, 2339287, 457434, 1554267, 597596, 2348780, 2239728, 920306, 2115319, 2284154, 2025595, 2207612, 2134015]",COVID-19,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",0,9,4.468100000000001,27.700300000000002,-23.23219999999999,61,49,110,"['2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-27']"
10,[457434],Moody,['ORG'],0,9,-0.8442,0.0,-0.8442,0,1,1,['2022-03-29']
11,[457434],Moody mentioned,['ORG'],0,9,-0.3612,0.0,-0.3612,0,1,1,['2022-03-29']
12,"[413890, 1696099, 1227715, 800487, 2292360, 510857, 1850283, 512396, 1092237, 1227730, 449428, 2354712, 623417, 457434, 597596]",Democratic,['NORP'],0,9,1.5742,5.0472,-3.473,9,8,17,"['2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-28', '2022-05-08', '2022-03-31']"
13,"[755329, 510857, 1635467, 2170124, 512396, 1092237, 449428, 623380, 1227928, 1587993, 2241438, 1296929, 439459, 1421348, 1850283, 524972, 676909, 1679152, 457650, 793395, 623417, 528443, 372284, 2137276, 807615, 471744, 413890, 1227715, 2314180, 533829, 848839, 2053959, 1024713, 728906, 2242251, 931403, 1276621, 1089225, 1227730, 419795, 943443, 1498194, 455511, 457434, 1554267, 597596, 1138141, 2208607, 1566688, 627043, 800487, 541160, 422893, 1543153, 2150388, 1438965, 1276661, 1480953, 1251068, 623485, 1298430]",Joe Biden,['PERSON'],0,9,-0.14560000000000026,14.065499999999995,-14.211100000000002,31,30,61,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-24', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-28']"
14,"[340497, 457434]",Atlanta,['GPE'],0,9,0.0469,0.2732,-0.2263,1,1,2,"['2022-03-27', '2022-03-29']"
15,"[428457, 457434, 898818, 512396]",Alabama,['GPE'],0,9,-0.4347999999999999,0.3182,-0.7529999999999999,1,2,3,"['2022-03-30', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29']"
16,"[1696099, 1281862, 1330472, 510857, 1138187, 1850283, 340497, 1227730, 1497495, 457434]",Alaska,['GPE'],0,9,5.1954,9.017599999999998,-3.8221999999999996,15,6,21,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29']"
17,"[1551502, 1227730, 2157012, 457434, 597596]",Arizona,['GPE'],0,9,0.4610000000000001,1.6282,-1.1672,3,2,5,"['2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-22', '2022-03-31']"
18,"[457434, 821274, 1092237]",Arkansas,['GPE'],0,9,0.01189999999999991,1.037,-1.0251000000000001,2,3,5,"['2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-02']"
19,"[898818, 848839, 2299880, 931403, 512396, 1092237, 2033521, 340497, 1470385, 1438965, 457434, 597596]",Georgia,['GPE'],0,9,-0.07050000000000001,2.8996000000000004,-2.9700999999999995,7,11,18,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-14', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-26', '2022-03-31']"
20,[457434],Idaho,['GPE'],0,9,-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,['2022-03-29']
21,[457434],Indiana,['GPE'],0,9,-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,['2022-03-29']
22,[457434],Kansas,['GPE'],0,9,-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,['2022-03-29']
23,"[2292360, 457434, 512396, 1092237]",Kentucky,['GPE'],0,9,3.5049,3.7312,-0.2263,6,1,7,"['2022-03-30', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-30']"
24,"[457434, 2062426]",Louisiana,['GPE'],0,9,-0.6081,0.0,-0.6081,0,2,2,"['2022-03-29', '2022-04-16']"
25,[457434],Mississippi,['GPE'],0,9,-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,['2022-03-29']
26,"[340497, 457434, 1092926, 413890]",Missouri,['GPE'],0,9,-1.2372999999999998,0.5499,-1.7872,1,4,5,"['2022-03-27', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-03']"
27,[457434],Montana,['GPE'],0,9,-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,['2022-03-29']
28,"[457434, 821274]",Nebraska,['GPE'],0,9,-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,"['2022-04-01', '2022-03-29']"
29,"[428457, 512396, 340497, 1438965, 2339286, 457434]",Ohio,['GPE'],0,9,1.3104,1.5367,-0.2263,3,1,4,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-05-04', '2022-03-30', '2022-03-29']"
30,"[457434, 597596, 1092237]",Oklahoma,['GPE'],0,9,0.46240000000000003,0.891,-0.4286,1,2,3,"['2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-31']"
31,"[2097544, 510857, 457434, 676909]",South Carolina,['GPE'],0,9,-0.4042,0.4215,-0.8257000000000001,1,2,3,"['2022-03-30', '2022-04-18', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-31']"
32,"[1696099, 1281862, 428457, 510857, 1850283, 1497495, 457434]",Utah,['GPE'],0,9,0.8492,1.7336999999999998,-0.8845000000000001,3,3,6,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29']"
33,"[457434, 943443, 800487]",Virginia,['GPE'],0,9,-1.1363,0.0,-1.1363,0,2,2,"['2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-02']"
34,"[457434, 512396]",West Virginia,['GPE'],0,9,-0.2263,0.0,-0.2263,0,1,1,"['2022-03-30', '2022-03-29']"
35,[2008485],Northeast US,['ORG'],0,5,0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
36,"[2008485, 800487, 2060872, 2186286, 2021946]",Philadelphia,['GPE'],0,5,1.1316000000000002,3.5898,-2.4581999999999997,6,5,11,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-11']"
37,"[517635, 1138187, 1792524, 2104843, 340497, 2354712, 2101788, 1296929, 615461, 2235430, 726571, 676909, 2186286, 1354803, 2194486, 2021946, 528443, 372284, 757828, 2060872, 1497161, 429128, 931403, 734285, 1279574, 524887, 2062426, 597596, 1478141, 2023525, 2346100, 425589, 2224758, 755329, 2313861, 2292360, 1635467, 1936012, 1092237, 2024078, 2345105, 476817, 528021, 1979029, 824475, 625314, 2333865, 2212524, 524972, 623292, 807615, 471744, 2053825, 413890, 2028224, 1024713, 2313930, 2242251, 1089225, 1276621, 1918680, 634084, 800487, 1682674, 1438965, 1276661, 1251068, 2115330, 1228546, 777480, 1655560, 2170124, 2041615, 623380, 1588501, 733976, 1587993, 2275096, 502563, 1330472, 1679152, 559922, 896313, 623417, 1092926, 533829, 2053959, 426824, 728906, 2350926, 678224, 943443, 1554267, 2208607, 627043, 723811, 560493, 2033521, 2207612, 623485, 1694081, 1240455, 1011081, 2048393, 1896851, 1258901, 2241438, 2008485, 516006, 1850283, 1470385, 457650, 1787828, 2203583, 796098, 2314180, 780740, 848839, 2094538, 1227730, 2339286, 1478103, 1845206, 2339287, 1998813, 1479648, 1566688, 1584099, 541160, 2299880, 422893, 2150382, 1543153, 2150388, 1521144, 425465, 1293309, 1298430, 2134015]",U.S.,['GPE'],0,5,-31.4742,74.09870000000001,-105.57289999999993,178,206,384,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
38,"[2008485, 516006, 2060872, 2207612, 512396, 524972, 2239728, 623380, 2194486, 2284154, 2025595, 372284]",COVID,['ORG'],0,5,1.0198,3.7322,-2.7124000000000006,8,5,13,"['2022-03-27', '2022-04-25', '2022-04-14', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31']"
39,"[2060872, 2021946, 2008485]",Cheryl Bettigole,['PERSON'],0,5,0.1955,0.1955,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-16', '2022-04-11']"
40,[2008485],Philadelphians,['NORP'],0,5,0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
41,"[2060872, 2021946, 2008485]",Bettigole,['PERSON'],0,5,0.47419999999999995,2.5846,-2.1104000000000003,5,3,8,"['2022-04-16', '2022-04-11']"
42,[2008485],Columbia University,['ORG'],0,5,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-11']
43,"[1227715, 2008485, 2092686, 1551502, 2158132, 2354712, 2021946]",New York City,['GPE'],0,5,0.8619999999999999,1.3939,-0.5319,5,1,6,"['2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-11', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-17']"
44,[2008485],Donna Lynne,['PERSON'],0,5,0.2484,0.2484,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
45,[2008485],Georgetown University,['ORG'],0,5,0.4767,0.4767,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
46,"[1596545, 2170124, 1936012, 2024078, 2345105, 340497, 1588501, 821274, 1296929, 2008485, 615461, 428457, 726571, 2212524, 2241325, 676909, 1354803, 2021946, 2053825, 1227715, 533829, 2053959, 429128, 1024713, 2242251, 2350926, 419795, 1845206, 1478103, 1998813, 1138141, 2208607, 1479648, 2158690, 1860324, 800487, 2033521, 2346100, 2224758, 425465, 1251068]",Washington,['GPE'],0,5,-2.2955000000000005,5.7111,-8.0066,11,13,24,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-23', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-05-01', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-26']"
47,"[2021946, 1354803, 2008485, 1227715]",D.C.,['GPE'],0,5,2.5393,2.6924,-0.1531,4,1,5,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-11']"
48,[2008485],Omicron,['ORG'],0,5,0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
49,"[1228546, 578564, 2097544, 1936012, 2024078, 2279161, 1588501, 1979029, 2101788, 419614, 2241438, 2353054, 1296929, 2008485, 726571, 2212524, 517164, 726445, 1679152, 1470385, 1787828, 2041653, 2137276, 1092926, 2203583, 780740, 848839, 2053959, 1089225, 931403, 943443, 1775573, 2339286, 1478103, 1918680, 597596, 1566688, 2023525, 2299880, 517355, 2033521, 2346100, 1276661, 1521144, 425465, 2025595, 2207612]",the United States,['GPE'],0,5,22.9537,25.143400000000003,-2.1896999999999998,49,9,58,"['2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-26', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
50,"[422893, 439459, 2008485]",DC,['GPE'],0,5,0.9281999999999999,0.9282,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-03-28', '2022-04-11']"
52,"[2115330, 2008485, 528021]",Johns Hopkins University,['ORG'],0,5,0.1491,0.2263,-0.0772,1,1,2,"['2022-03-30', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-11']"
53,[2008485],Rice University,['ORG'],0,5,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-11']
54,"[2060872, 2021946]",PHILADELPHIA,['GPE'],0,1,0.7717,0.7717,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-16', '2022-04-11']"
55,"[755329, 2115330, 512396, 449428, 623380, 2353054, 502563, 1421348, 516006, 2235430, 524972, 2186286, 2194486, 623417, 2021946, 1578681, 2137276, 807615, 533829, 2060872, 1089225, 1498194, 2339286, 524887, 2339287, 455511, 1554267, 597596, 2348780, 2346100, 1438965, 1480953, 2207612, 623485]",Americans,['NORP'],0,1,-4.6949000000000005,10.573300000000001,-15.268199999999998,27,34,61,"['2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27']"
56,[2021946],Ben Fileccia,['PERSON'],0,1,0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
57,[2021946],the Pennsylvania Restaurant & Lodging Association,['ORG'],0,1,0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
58,[2021946],PolicyLab,['ORG'],0,1,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-11']
59,[2021946],Children’s Hospital of Philadelphia,['ORG'],0,1,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-11']
60,"[2354712, 2021946]",Eric Adams,['PERSON'],0,1,0.5574,0.5574,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-05-08', '2022-04-11']"
61,"[439459, 2292360, 428457, 728906, 931403, 1092237, 340497, 2021946, 528443, 1138141]",Democrat,['NORP'],0,1,0.836,2.4537999999999998,-1.6178,6,3,9,"['2022-03-27', '2022-04-30', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03']"
62,"[2354712, 2021946]",New Yorkers,['NORP'],0,1,0.3612,0.3612,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-05-08', '2022-04-11']"
63,"[1296929, 458246, 639144, 1497161, 1138187, 2092686, 340497, 733976, 793395, 2339286, 1478103, 2354712, 2021946, 1251068]",New York,['GPE'],0,1,1.3904,5.8238,-4.4334,13,8,21,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-05-04', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-17']"
64,"[2021946, 2203583]",Cabinet,['ORG'],0,1,-0.7267,0.0,-0.7267,0,2,2,"['2022-04-25', '2022-04-11']"
65,"[1596545, 1694081, 1138187, 512396, 1092237, 449428, 821274, 419614, 439459, 1330472, 428457, 1850283, 1679152, 2021946, 623292, 1092926, 2314180, 848839, 419795, 540892, 597596, 800487, 1438965, 1480953, 2284154]",House,['ORG'],0,1,-6.428,8.4056,-14.8336,19,27,46,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-09', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
66,"[2021946, 2314180]",Nancy Pelosi,['PERSON'],0,1,1.498,1.748,-0.25,2,1,3,"['2022-04-11', '2022-05-02']"
67,"[2021946, 1227715, 2339286]",New Jersey,['GPE'],0,1,-0.10009999999999997,0.34,-0.4401,1,2,3,"['2022-04-04', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-11']"
68,"[2354712, 1296929, 2021946, 1251068]",Connecticut,['GPE'],0,1,0.552,0.802,-0.25,1,1,2,"['2022-04-04', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-11']"
69,"[2060872, 512396, 340497, 1227730, 2021946]",Pennsylvania,['GPE'],0,1,0.9931000000000001,1.1191,-0.126,3,1,4,"['2022-03-27', '2022-04-04', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-11']"
70,"[2262917, 704263, 1011081, 2170124, 1092237, 1551502, 2041615, 1936012, 2345105, 340497, 476817, 1141524, 1258901, 2354712, 2325276, 1296929, 1511077, 2333865, 2081578, 428457, 2212524, 676909, 2015530, 2021946, 471744, 2053825, 757828, 1024713, 2094538, 2242251, 2313930, 1907918, 2350926, 2157012, 1478103, 1998813, 2208607, 2158690, 627043, 1860324, 723811, 1262570, 2033521, 1543153, 920306, 1276661, 2224758, 1521144, 2279161, 1081722, 1251068, 623485]",Associated Press,['ORG'],0,1,0.07729999999999992,2.4774000000000003,-2.4000999999999997,6,5,11,"['2022-04-20', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-30', '2022-05-02', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-26']"
71,[2021946],Michelle L. Price,['PERSON'],0,1,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-11']
72,[2025595],Boston COVID,['ORG'],0,0,0.7184,0.7184,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-14']
73,"[2339287, 2095815, 639144, 1811789, 2092686, 436119, 1480953, 2025595]",Boston,['GPE'],0,0,4.5583,6.7591,-2.2008,13,4,17,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-14', '2022-03-26', '2022-04-17']"
74,[2025595],the Boston Public Health Commission,['ORG'],0,0,0.5106,0.5106,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-14']
75,"[2081578, 2025595]",Easter,['PERSON'],0,0,0.9119,0.9119,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-17']"
76,[2025595],126th,['ORG'],0,0,0.7096,0.7096,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-14']
77,"[2025595, 2092686, 2095815]",the Boston Marathon,['ORG'],0,0,2.3005,2.3005,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-17']"
78,[2025595],BPHC,['ORG'],0,0,2.4291,2.4291,0.0,3,0,3,['2022-04-14']
79,[2025595],Bisola Ojikutu,['PERSON'],0,0,0.9545,0.9545,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-14']
80,[2025595],Public Health and Executive,['ORG'],0,0,0.9545,0.9545,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-14']
83,"[2025595, 2235430, 2339287]",Shira Doron,['PERSON'],0,0,1.2525,1.2525,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-05']"
84,"[2025595, 2235430, 2339287]",Tufts Medical Center,['ORG'],0,0,1.2525,1.2525,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-05']"
85,"[1694081, 2010882, 898818, 755329, 2097544, 1138187, 512396, 1635467, 449428, 623380, 1227928, 2144793, 821274, 2026013, 439459, 516003, 516006, 2351271, 2235430, 524972, 559922, 1354803, 2194486, 623292, 2137276, 2203583, 1227715, 780740, 533829, 2053959, 426824, 734285, 1227730, 419795, 1498194, 524887, 1918680, 2339287, 2069978, 455511, 597596, 634084, 541160, 2348780, 422893, 2150388, 1438965, 2115319, 2025595]",ABC News,['ORG'],0,0,-1.9076000000000002,15.4224,-17.330000000000002,42,40,82,"['2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-17', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-25', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27']"
86,[2025595],Paul Sax,['PERSON'],0,0,0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-14']
87,[2025595],Brigham and Women's Hospital,['ORG'],0,0,0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-14']
88,[2025595],"Tufts Medical Center, Doron",['ORG'],0,0,-0.3491,0.0,-0.3491,0,1,1,['2022-04-14']
89,"[2025595, 2235430, 2339287]",Doron,['PERSON'],0,0,-0.25939999999999996,1.0584,-1.3178,2,2,4,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-05']"
90,[2025595],Sax,['PERSON'],0,0,1.0812,1.0812,0.0,2,0,2,['2022-04-14']
91,"[2025595, 2348780, 2235430, 2339287]",Paxlovid,['PERSON'],0,0,2.6515,5.2252,-2.5737,11,7,18,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-06', '2022-05-05']"
92,"[2339287, 780740, 516006, 2235430, 426824, 2186286, 524887, 2025595, 2207612, 2353054]",Pfizer,"['PERSON', 'ORG']",0,0,1.5484,4.9568,-3.4084000000000003,11,10,21,"['2022-05-05', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-27']"
93,[2060872],Commonwealth Court,['ORG'],0,9,-0.4215,0.0,-0.4215,0,1,1,['2022-04-16']
96,[2060872],the state department of health,['ORG'],0,9,-0.2732,0.0,-0.2732,0,1,1,['2022-04-16']
97,[2060872],Kevin Lessard,['PERSON'],0,9,-0.5267,0.0,-0.5267,0,1,1,['2022-04-16']
98,[2060872],Lessard,['ORG'],0,9,0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-16']
99,"[1696099, 2060872, 510857, 1850283, 512396, 422893, 1807056, 1227730, 449428, 1497495, 1092926]",Supreme Court,['ORG'],0,9,13.7466,14.277700000000001,-0.5311,20,2,22,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03']"
100,[2092686],The Boston Marathon,['ORG'],0,6,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17']
101,"[2092686, 436119]",BOSTON,['GPE'],0,6,-0.7579,0.0,-0.7579,0,1,1,"['2022-03-26', '2022-04-17']"
102,"[2092686, 2095815]",Hopkinton,['GPE'],0,6,0.6189,1.092,-0.47309999999999997,2,2,4,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-17']"
103,"[2092686, 2095815]",Patriots,['ORG'],0,6,-0.38150000000000006,0.5719,-0.9534,1,2,3,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-17']"
104,[2092686],Des Linden,['GPE'],0,6,0.5859,0.5859,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
105,[2092686],Boston Marathon,['ORG'],0,6,0.6486,0.6486,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
106,"[2092686, 2095815]",Boston Athletic Association,['ORG'],0,6,0.0772,0.0772,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-17']"
107,"[2092686, 2095815]",Tom Grilk,['PERSON'],0,6,0.0772,0.0772,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-17']"
108,[2092686],Olympic,['ORG'],0,6,0.7717,0.7717,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
109,"[2092686, 2095815]",Peres Jepchirchir,['PERSON'],0,6,2.3626,2.3626,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-17']"
110,"[1228546, 1860324, 429128, 1024713, 1878824, 2242251, 2170124, 1964200, 2092686, 1543153, 2224758, 1578681]",London,['GPE'],0,6,1.4521000000000002,2.1329,-0.6808,4,1,5,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-17']"
111,[2092686],Joyciline Jepkosgei,['PERSON'],0,6,0.7717,0.7717,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
112,"[2144793, 2092686, 2095815]",Ethiopia,['GPE'],0,6,0.8102,1.2121,-0.4019,2,1,3,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-17']"
113,[2092686],Tokyo,['GPE'],0,6,0.2023,0.2023,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
114,[2092686],Molly Seidel,['PERSON'],0,6,0.2023,0.2023,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
115,"[1596545, 755329, 517635, 1635467, 512396, 2092686, 2345105, 623380, 1296929, 2212524, 524972, 457650, 623292, 2203583, 413890, 780740, 533829, 2053959, 426824, 1024713, 2350926, 419795, 1918680, 2062426, 597596, 1138141, 2208607, 1860324, 800487, 2299880, 2346100, 425589, 2284154, 1251068]",American,['NORP'],0,6,-6.4123,7.5286,-13.940899999999997,19,25,44,"['2022-04-20', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
116,"[2092686, 2095815]",Benson Kipruto,"['PERSON', 'ORG']",0,6,1.4585,1.4585,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-17']"
117,"[2092686, 2095815]",Kenya,['GPE'],0,6,0.4376,0.8591,-0.4215,1,1,2,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-17']"
118,[2092686],Robert Kipkoech Cheruiyot,['PERSON'],0,6,0.8591,0.8591,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
119,[2092686],Lawrence Cherono,['PERSON'],0,6,0.4767,0.4767,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
120,[2092686],Lemi Berhanu,['PERSON'],0,6,0.4767,0.4767,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
121,[2092686],Lelisa Desisa,['PERSON'],0,6,0.4767,0.4767,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
122,[2092686],Colin Bennie,['PERSON'],0,6,0.2023,0.2023,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
123,[2092686],Princeton,['GPE'],0,6,0.2023,0.2023,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
124,"[1694081, 1227715, 2092686, 2339287]",Massachusetts,['GPE'],0,6,0.394,0.5635,-0.1695,2,1,3,"['2022-04-07', '2022-04-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-17']"
125,[2092686],CJ Albertson,['PERSON'],0,6,0.2023,0.2023,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
126,[2092686],Fresno,['GPE'],0,6,0.2023,0.2023,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
127,"[2097544, 2092686, 1551502, 528021, 1227928, 1964200, 2194486, 623292, 1092926, 1227715, 2313930, 1227730, 2339287, 2069978, 2062426, 800487, 1543153, 2346100, 2115319]",California,['GPE'],0,6,-2.1414,2.5987,-4.740100000000001,9,11,20,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-17']"
128,[2092686],Aaron Baggish,['PERSON'],0,6,0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
129,[2092686],Brooklyn,['GPE'],0,6,-0.8779,0.0,-0.8779,0,1,1,['2022-04-17']
130,[2092686],Frank James,['PERSON'],0,6,-0.4767,0.0,-0.4767,0,1,1,['2022-04-17']
131,"[2092686, 458246]",James,['PERSON'],0,6,-0.6808,0.0,-0.6808,0,1,1,"['2022-03-29', '2022-04-17']"
132,[2092686],Kenneth Green,['PERSON'],0,6,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17']
133,"[517635, 2104843, 1792524, 2144793, 2101788, 2026013, 615453, 1296929, 2355237, 615461, 2023465, 726571, 517164, 1354803, 2338356, 372284, 757828, 429128, 1497161, 931403, 734285, 2311760, 1498194, 2062426, 597596, 1478141, 2158690, 2219618, 2274916, 2023525, 2346100, 425589, 2224758, 625786, 755329, 1635467, 1936012, 2092686, 2024078, 2345105, 587411, 528021, 1979029, 824475, 494236, 625314, 1511077, 2351271, 2114216, 2333865, 2212524, 1578681, 623292, 2137276, 471744, 2053825, 413890, 2226371, 2028224, 2095815, 1024713, 1089225, 2242251, 1276621, 1907918, 1549013, 1918680, 1860324, 426218, 517355, 1963245, 1682674, 920306, 1276661, 2279161, 2042107, 959740, 1251068, 2010882, 2063107, 1228546, 704263, 1655560, 2266890, 2170124, 2041615, 1141524, 1588501, 623380, 733976, 1587993, 2325276, 502563, 1878824, 2081578, 2015530, 2241325, 1679152, 2041653, 896313, 1092926, 746815, 1749828, 533829, 2053959, 426824, 2350926, 678224, 943443, 455511, 2208607, 1093474, 627043, 723811, 560493, 2033521, 2334069, 1081722, 623485, 1694081, 2262917, 1240455, 1011081, 2048393, 512396, 1896851, 449428, 1258901, 2241438, 1983397, 1850283, 726445, 2150320, 1470385, 2231218, 2155952, 1787828, 457650, 2203583, 2314180, 2094538, 560588, 2157012, 1775573, 1845206, 1478103, 1998813, 1479648, 1566688, 1584099, 541160, 2299880, 1262570, 2150382, 1006066, 2150388, 1521144, 425465, 1293309, 1298430, 2355199]",Ukraine,['GPE'],0,6,-290.0644,113.31969999999976,-403.38410000000044,286,704,990,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
134,[2092686],Grilk,['PERSON'],0,6,0.0772,0.0772,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-17']
135,"[2104843, 1792524, 2144793, 821274, 2101788, 2026013, 1296929, 2355237, 517164, 2338356, 429128, 1497161, 734285, 2062426, 597596, 2158690, 2219618, 425589, 2224758, 625786, 1635467, 1936012, 2092686, 2345105, 528021, 1979029, 824475, 494236, 625314, 2351271, 2114216, 2333865, 2212524, 471744, 2053825, 2028224, 2226371, 2095815, 2242251, 1276621, 1907918, 1549013, 1918680, 1860324, 1963245, 1682674, 1276661, 2279161, 2042107, 1251068, 959740, 2010882, 2063107, 1228546, 704263, 1655560, 2266890, 2170124, 2041615, 1141524, 1588501, 2325276, 1878824, 2081578, 2241325, 559922, 896313, 1092926, 2053959, 426824, 2350926, 678224, 2208607, 627043, 723811, 560493, 2033521, 2334069, 1081722, 1694081, 2262917, 1011081, 2048393, 1896851, 1258901, 2241438, 1983397, 726445, 2150320, 1470385, 2155952, 457650, 1787828, 2203583, 1227715, 2314180, 2094538, 2157012, 1775573, 1845206, 1478103, 1998813, 1584099, 541160, 2299880, 1262570, 2150382, 1006066, 2150388, 1521144, 425465, 1298430, 2355199]",Ukrainian,"['NORP', 'GPE']",0,6,-103.2717,54.77499999999999,-158.0466999999999,133,291,424,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
136,"[517635, 2104843, 1792524, 2144793, 2101788, 2026013, 615453, 1296929, 2355237, 615461, 2023465, 726571, 517164, 1354803, 2338356, 372284, 757828, 429128, 1497161, 931403, 734285, 2311760, 1498194, 2062426, 597596, 1478141, 2158690, 2219618, 2023525, 2346100, 425589, 2224758, 625786, 2134015, 1635467, 1936012, 2092686, 2024078, 2345105, 528021, 1979029, 824475, 494236, 625314, 1511077, 2351271, 2114216, 2333865, 2212524, 1578681, 623292, 2137276, 471744, 2053825, 413890, 2226371, 2028224, 2095815, 1024713, 1089225, 2242251, 1276621, 1907918, 1549013, 1918680, 1860324, 800487, 426218, 517355, 1963245, 2239728, 1682674, 920306, 1276661, 2042107, 959740, 1251068, 2010882, 2063107, 1228546, 704263, 1655560, 2266890, 2170124, 2041615, 1141524, 1588501, 623380, 733976, 1587993, 2325276, 502563, 1878824, 2081578, 2015530, 2241325, 1679152, 2041653, 896313, 1092926, 746815, 1749828, 533829, 2053959, 426824, 2350926, 678224, 943443, 455511, 2208607, 1093474, 627043, 723811, 560493, 2033521, 2334069, 1081722, 623485, 1694081, 2262917, 1240455, 1011081, 2048393, 512396, 1896851, 449428, 1258901, 2241438, 1983397, 726445, 2150320, 1470385, 2231218, 2155952, 1787828, 457650, 2203583, 796098, 2314180, 2094538, 560588, 2157012, 1775573, 1845206, 1478103, 1998813, 1479648, 1566688, 1584099, 2299880, 1262570, 2150382, 1006066, 2150388, 1521144, 425465, 1293309, 1298430, 2355199]",Russia,['GPE'],0,6,-214.8633,124.94249999999981,-339.8058000000001,313,639,952,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-23', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-26']"
137,"[2010882, 2092686, 625314, 2355237, 2333865, 1679152, 1787828, 2053825, 2095815, 426824, 2350926, 597596, 723811, 1584099, 426218, 1963245, 560493, 1682674, 1521144, 1298430]",Belarus,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",0,6,-3.6258,3.3613,-6.9871,11,20,31,"['2022-04-18', '2022-05-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-30', '2022-03-25', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17']"
138,"[2063107, 2262917, 2313861, 704263, 1011081, 2048393, 2170124, 2092686, 2041615, 1551502, 2345105, 1141524, 528021, 1258901, 1587993, 2325276, 615453, 494236, 502563, 1251068, 1511077, 1878824, 2333865, 2081578, 428457, 2212524, 517164, 2023465, 2186286, 2150320, 2155952, 559922, 413742, 2041653, 528443, 2053825, 1749828, 2314180, 429128, 1024713, 2094538, 2242251, 728906, 1907918, 2350926, 2311760, 639144, 1549013, 1478103, 2062426, 1998813, 2208607, 2158690, 627043, 1860324, 1093474, 2023525, 517355, 1963245, 2239728, 2033521, 1006066, 1543153, 2334069, 2224758, 1521144, 425465, 2042107, 959740]",AP,['ORG'],0,6,-28.2909,4.4968,-32.78769999999997,13,58,71,"['2022-04-20', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-24', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-26']"
139,[2092686],https://twitter.com/AP—Sports,['ORG'],0,6,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-17']
140,[2115319],PPE,['ORG'],0,3,-1.0398,0.0,-1.0398,0,2,2,['2022-04-18']
141,[2115319],Sutter Health,['ORG'],0,3,-0.7274,0.0,-0.7274,0,2,2,['2022-04-18']
142,"[1964200, 2097544, 1551502, 1543153, 1227730, 2115319, 1227928, 2069978, 1595579, 1314239]",Sacramento,['GPE'],0,3,-19.4182,0.3182,-19.736399999999996,1,31,32,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-17']"
143,[2115319],Berkeley,['GPE'],0,3,-0.128,0.0,-0.128,0,1,1,['2022-04-18']
144,[2115319],Oakland,['GPE'],0,3,-0.128,0.0,-0.128,0,1,1,['2022-04-18']
145,"[516006, 1497161, 2348780, 1543153, 2115319]",San Francisco,['GPE'],0,3,-1.4325999999999999,0.0,-1.4325999999999999,0,5,5,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-05', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-03']"
146,[2115319],Santa Cruz,['GPE'],0,3,-0.128,0.0,-0.128,0,1,1,['2022-04-18']
147,[2115319],Vallejo,['PERSON'],0,3,-0.128,0.0,-0.128,0,1,1,['2022-04-18']
148,[2115319],the California Nurses' Association,['ORG'],0,3,-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-04-18']
149,[2115319],CNA,['ORG'],0,3,0.7605,0.8885,-0.128,1,1,2,['2022-04-18']
150,[2115319],Amy Erb,['PERSON'],0,3,-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-18']
151,[2115319],Sutter,['ORG'],0,3,1.1439,1.4399,-0.296,2,1,3,['2022-04-18']
152,[2115319],California Pacific Medical Center,['ORG'],0,3,-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-18']
153,[2115319],KCRA,['ORG'],0,3,0.1779,0.1779,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-18']
154,[2115319],Renee Water,['PERSON'],0,3,0.4939,0.4939,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-18']
156,[2115330],Kathryn Kimball Mizelle,['PERSON'],0,7,0.1154,0.1154,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-19']
157,[2115330],Stuart Ray,['PERSON'],0,7,0.2263,0.2263,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-19']
158,[2115330],Ray,['PERSON'],0,7,-0.5654,1.0945,-1.6599,3,4,7,['2022-04-19']
159,[2115330],N95,['ORG'],0,7,-0.3182,0.0,-0.3182,0,1,1,['2022-04-19']
160,[2115330],Guillain-Barre,['PERSON'],0,7,-0.1779,0.0,-0.1779,0,1,1,['2022-04-19']
161,[2115330],the Mayo Clinic,['ORG'],0,7,-0.1779,0.0,-0.1779,0,1,1,['2022-04-19']
162,"[755329, 2115330, 2097544, 1138187, 512396, 1792524, 449428, 1227928, 2144793, 2101788, 2353054, 439459, 516006, 2235430, 524972, 559922, 1354803, 2158132, 746815, 1314239, 780740, 533829, 1281862, 426824, 734285, 1807056, 1227730, 1498194, 540892, 597596, 541160, 2348780, 1682674, 825466]",ABC News',['ORG'],0,7,0.5319,1.2097,-0.6778,3,2,5,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-05', '2022-04-19', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-22', '2022-03-31']"
163,"[2115330, 2348780]",Arielle Mitropoulos,['PERSON'],0,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-19', '2022-05-06']"
164,[2158132],The teachers union,['ORG'],0,3,-0.3818,0.0,-0.3818,0,1,1,['2022-04-22']
165,"[2158132, 2194486]",Vaccines,['ORG'],0,3,-1.068,0.0,-1.068,0,2,2,"['2022-04-25', '2022-04-22']"
166,[2158132],Jen Ashton Dozens,['PERSON'],0,3,-0.5106,0.0,-0.5106,0,1,1,['2022-04-22']
167,[2158132],New York City Education Department,['GPE'],0,3,-0.5106,0.0,-0.5106,0,1,1,['2022-04-22']
168,[2158132],DOE,['ORG'],0,3,-2.2745,0.0,-2.2745,0,5,5,['2022-04-22']
169,[2158132],The United Federation of Teachers,['ORG'],0,3,-0.3818,0.0,-0.3818,0,1,1,['2022-04-22']
170,[2158132],Beth A. Norton,['PERSON'],0,3,-0.4939,0.0,-0.4939,0,1,1,['2022-04-22']
171,[2158132],UFT,['ORG'],0,3,-1.3755000000000002,0.0,-1.3755000000000002,0,4,4,['2022-04-22']
173,[2158132],The Education Department,['ORG'],0,3,0.4067,0.4067,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-22']
174,[2158132],Bill de Blasio,['PERSON'],0,3,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-22']
175,"[1596545, 439459, 1696099, 1281862, 510857, 1850283, 1807056, 587411, 2158132, 1438965, 1497495, 1092926]",the Supreme Court,['ORG'],0,3,9.296,9.8679,-0.5719,14,2,16,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-03']"
176,[2158132],Mark Osborne,['PERSON'],0,3,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-22']
177,"[2170124, 2041615, 587411, 2325276, 615461, 2351271, 726571, 2338356, 1578681, 471744, 429128, 1024713, 2242251, 1907918, 2350926, 1998813, 627043, 1860324, 2239728, 1521144, 2279161]",British,['NORP'],0,7,-4.3781,4.1455,-8.523600000000002,14,18,32,"['2022-04-15', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-30', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-12', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-28', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-07', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
178,[2239728],Conservative,['NORP'],0,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-27']
179,"[2010882, 757828, 2355237, 2351271, 1024713, 2239728, 587411, 1578681, 625786]",LONDON,['GPE'],0,7,-0.9717,0.5755,-1.5472000000000001,3,3,6,"['2022-04-06', '2022-04-13', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-28', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-07', '2022-04-03']"
180,[2239728],High Court,['ORG'],0,7,-0.743,0.0,-0.743,0,1,1,['2022-04-27']
181,"[2010882, 1860324, 1878824, 1024713, 2212524, 734285, 1907918, 2350926, 2239728, 2345105, 587411, 1258901, 1578681]",U.K.,['GPE'],0,7,-0.7173,2.8977,-3.6149999999999993,8,6,14,"['2022-05-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-13', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-03']"
182,[2239728],the National Health Service,['ORG'],0,7,-0.7391,0.0,-0.7391,0,1,1,['2022-04-27']
183,"[471744, 1860324, 1878824, 1024713, 1907918, 2239728, 587411, 1918680, 2325276]",Boris Johnson,['PERSON'],0,7,1.6431,2.4173,-0.7742,4,2,6,"['2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03']"
184,"[2239728, 1878824, 1860324, 1907918]",Johnson,['PERSON'],0,7,2.6039,2.6039,0.0,5,0,5,"['2022-04-27', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09']"
185,[2239728],the House of Commons,['ORG'],0,7,0.4019,0.4019,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-27']
186,[2239728],Matt Hancock,['PERSON'],0,7,-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-04-27']
187,[2239728],Claimant Cathy Gardner,['PERSON'],0,7,-0.5859,0.0,-0.5859,0,1,1,['2022-04-27']
188,[2239728],Gardner,['PERSON'],0,7,0.0258,0.0258,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-27']
189,"[2010882, 2262917, 1011081, 587411, 1258901, 1588501, 733976, 625314, 615461, 1878824, 726571, 2212524, 726445, 1578681, 757828, 1024713, 931403, 1907918, 2350926, 1478103, 1998813, 2150382, 2239728, 1276661, 1521144]",Britain,['GPE'],0,7,7.5173000000000005,12.329700000000004,-4.812399999999999,26,10,36,"['2022-05-05', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-13', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
190,[2239728],Helen Wildbore,['PERSON'],0,7,0.7184,0.7184,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-27']
191,[2239728],the Relatives and Residents Association,['ORG'],0,7,0.7184,0.7184,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-27']
192,"[2292360, 1679152, 1092237]",Rand Paul,['PERSON'],0,2,0.42280000000000006,1.2248,-0.802,2,1,3,"['2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-30']"
193,"[1596545, 898818, 2292360, 510857, 777480, 512396, 449428, 1497495, 821274, 1850283, 524972, 676909, 1679152, 623417, 623292, 1281862, 1089225, 1227730, 540892, 1138141, 597596, 1696099, 2348780, 1438965]",Republicans,['NORP'],0,2,5.4132,15.184700000000001,-9.7715,31,18,49,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
194,"[898818, 2292360, 510857, 512396, 1092237, 340497, 1497495, 428457, 1850283, 676909, 1679152, 559922, 1092926, 1281862, 848839, 1807056, 1227730, 943443, 1138141, 1696099, 1438965, 1480953, 623485]",Senate,['ORG'],0,2,11.4993,14.974899999999996,-3.4756,35,12,47,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
195,[2292360],SMITHFIELD,['GPE'],0,2,0.6124,0.6124,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-30']
196,"[2292360, 943443, 1850283, 1679152]",Ky.,['GPE'],0,2,0.22100000000000009,1.2493,-1.0283,2,2,4,"['2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-30']"
197,"[2292360, 1141524, 2299880]",Paul,['PERSON'],0,2,3.4249,5.0428,-1.6179000000000001,10,5,15,"['2022-04-26', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-03']"
198,"[2292360, 2339286, 524887]",Anthony Fauci,['PERSON'],0,2,1.2012,1.2012,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-03-29', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-30']"
199,"[898818, 1696099, 2292360, 510857, 428457, 1138187, 512396, 1092237, 1850283, 340497, 1227730, 449428, 1438965, 821274, 540892, 1138141, 597596]",GOP,['ORG'],0,2,7.9952,12.426799999999998,-4.4316,22,13,35,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
200,"[1596545, 2292360, 777480, 1092237, 449428, 1497495, 821274, 824475, 1850283, 524972, 559922, 623417, 413890, 1281862, 1089225, 1227730, 943443, 455511, 1554267, 597596, 1138141, 1696099, 1438965, 1480953, 623485]",Democrats,['NORP'],0,2,2.0032000000000005,12.652099999999999,-10.6489,27,21,48,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-30', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
201,"[2292360, 2137276, 471744, 1807056]",Kamala Harris,['PERSON'],0,2,1.2521,1.2521,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-04-21', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-30']"
202,"[471744, 578564, 2169477, 615461, 2292360, 726571, 512396, 726445, 1845206]",Chinese,['NORP'],0,2,0.33299999999999996,2.0838,-1.7508,4,4,8,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-30', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-26', '2022-03-31']"
203,"[1228546, 578564, 2169477, 2292360, 1655560, 512396, 2024078, 587411, 1588501, 824475, 625314, 615461, 2023465, 726571, 2241325, 726445, 2231218, 471744, 1497161, 1845206, 1478103, 2062426, 723811, 2023525, 541160, 1682674, 1276661, 2224758]",China,['GPE'],0,2,-2.395,17.1691,-19.5641,35,37,72,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-05', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-13', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-14', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-26', '2022-03-31']"
204,"[1596545, 898818, 755329, 2262917, 2292360, 2048393, 1635467, 512396, 340497, 476817, 449428, 623380, 1227928, 824475, 1296929, 439459, 1421348, 2235430, 428457, 524972, 676909, 1679152, 559922, 793395, 457650, 623417, 2203583, 623292, 372284, 1092926, 2137276, 471744, 807615, 413890, 796098, 780740, 533829, 1227715, 848839, 2053959, 1024713, 1089225, 931403, 1276621, 1227730, 943443, 1498194, 455511, 1918680, 1554267, 597596, 1138141, 2208607, 1566688, 1584099, 541160, 422893, 1543153, 2150388, 1438965, 1276661, 1480953, 2207612, 623485, 1298430]",Biden,['PERSON'],0,2,-5.2628,38.30649999999999,-43.56929999999999,89,102,191,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-25', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27']"
205,"[2292360, 1850283, 512396, 943443, 623485]",Mitch McConnell,['PERSON'],0,2,2.4083,2.6346000000000003,-0.2263,4,1,5,"['2022-04-30', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-31']"
206,"[2292360, 1850283]",McConnell,['PERSON'],0,2,-1.3039,0.296,-1.5998999999999999,1,4,5,"['2022-04-09', '2022-04-30']"
207,[2292360],Andy Beshear,['PERSON'],0,2,0.3818,0.3818,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-30']
208,"[1596545, 898818, 458246, 2292360, 512396, 1092237, 340497, 449428, 821274, 824475, 419614, 1296929, 439459, 516003, 1330472, 428457, 1850283, 559922, 528443, 623292, 1092926, 1227715, 780740, 848839, 728906, 1227730, 419795, 540892, 597596, 1138141, 1696099, 800487, 541160, 422893, 1480953, 2284154, 1251068]",Trump,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",0,2,-18.1023,26.5367,-44.63899999999999,62,95,157,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
209,"[2292360, 777480, 1138187, 512396, 1227928, 824475, 439459, 1330472, 2194486, 623417, 471744, 413890, 2314180, 1807056, 1227730, 1566688, 422893, 1543153, 1293309]",America,['GPE'],0,2,4.3484,7.27,-2.9215999999999998,12,5,17,"['2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-25', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-06', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
210,"[2292360, 1092237]",Charles Booker,['PERSON'],0,2,0.6369,0.6369,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-02', '2022-04-30']"
211,"[2292360, 1807056]",Booker,"['ORG', 'GPE']",0,2,-0.44999999999999996,0.25,-0.7,1,2,3,"['2022-04-08', '2022-04-30']"
212,"[2292360, 413890]",Medicare,['ORG'],0,2,0.5460999999999999,0.5719,-0.0258,1,1,2,"['2022-03-28', '2022-04-30']"
213,[2292360],the U.S. Senate,['ORG'],0,2,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-30']
214,[2292360],Wendell Ford,['PERSON'],0,2,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-30']
215,[2339286],NYC,['ORG'],0,5,0.6369,0.6369,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-04']
216,[2339286],Foreign Policy,['ORG'],0,5,0.3995,0.3995,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-04']
217,"[2313930, 2339286]",Minnesota,['GPE'],0,5,-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,"['2022-05-04', '2022-05-02']"
218,"[898818, 1438965, 2339286]",Wisconsin,['GPE'],0,5,-0.0046,0.0,-0.0046,0,1,1,"['2022-04-02', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-04']"
220,[2339286],the New York,['GPE'],0,5,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-05-04']
221,[2339286],Fauci,['PERSON'],0,5,0.5267,0.5267,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-04']
222,[2354712],Kathy Hochul,['PERSON'],0,7,1.3616,1.3616,0.0,2,0,2,['2022-05-08']
223,[2354712],Northeast NEW YORK,['GPE'],0,7,0.6808,0.6808,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-08']
224,[2354712],Hochul,['PERSON'],0,7,0.9186000000000001,0.9186000000000001,0.0,2,0,2,['2022-05-08']
225,[2354712],the Olana State Historic Site,['ORG'],0,7,0.3612,0.3612,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-08']
226,[2354712],Ned Lamont,['PERSON'],0,7,0.802,0.802,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-08']
227,"[1281862, 510857, 1850283, 1497495, 2354712]",Maine,['GPE'],0,7,3.1996,3.1996,0.0,4,0,4,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-30', '2022-05-08']"
228,[2354712],Janet Mills,['PERSON'],0,7,0.802,0.802,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-05-08']
229,[2354712],upstate New York,['ORG'],0,7,-0.0772,0.0,-0.0772,0,1,1,['2022-05-08']
230,"[615453, 1296929, 2355237, 615461, 2023465, 726571, 517164, 2338356, 429128, 1497161, 2311760, 1498194, 2062426, 2158690, 2219618, 2023525, 2224758, 1936012, 2024078, 2345105, 494236, 625314, 2351271, 2114216, 2333865, 2212524, 1578681, 471744, 2053825, 2226371, 1024713, 1089225, 2242251, 1907918, 1549013, 1860324, 517355, 2279161, 2042107, 1251068, 1228546, 2063107, 704263, 1655560, 2170124, 2041615, 733976, 1587993, 2325276, 2081578, 2241325, 896313, 1749828, 533829, 2350926, 2208607, 1093474, 627043, 723811, 2033521, 2334069, 1081722, 2262917, 1011081, 2048393, 1258901, 1983397, 726445, 2155952, 1470385, 2231218, 2094538, 2157012, 1845206, 1998813, 2299880, 1262570, 1521144, 425465]",Moscow,['GPE'],1,7,-54.1349,17.803700000000006,-71.93860000000001,50,134,184,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-30', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
231,"[2063107, 2262917, 704263, 1011081, 2104843, 2170124, 1792524, 1936012, 2041615, 2345105, 1258901, 1979029, 2325276, 2026013, 2241438, 2101788, 2355237, 2351271, 2333865, 2081578, 2212524, 517164, 457650, 2338356, 1787828, 2053825, 429128, 2094538, 2242251, 734285, 1907918, 2350926, 678224, 1998813, 2208607, 2158690, 627043, 1860324, 1584099, 1963245, 560493, 2033521, 2150388, 425589, 2224758, 1521144, 1298430]",Donbas,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-33.9346,14.2307,-48.1653,33,99,132,"['2022-04-20', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-24', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
232,"[517635, 2104843, 1792524, 2144793, 2101788, 2026013, 615453, 1296929, 2355237, 615461, 2023465, 726571, 517164, 1354803, 2338356, 429128, 1497161, 931403, 734285, 2311760, 1498194, 2062426, 597596, 2158690, 2219618, 2274916, 2023525, 2346100, 425589, 2224758, 625786, 1635467, 1936012, 2024078, 2345105, 528021, 1979029, 494236, 625314, 1511077, 2351271, 2114216, 2333865, 2212524, 1578681, 2137276, 471744, 2053825, 2028224, 2226371, 1024713, 2242251, 1276621, 1907918, 1549013, 1918680, 1860324, 426218, 517355, 1963245, 1682674, 1438965, 1276661, 2279161, 2042107, 1251068, 959740, 2010882, 2063107, 1228546, 704263, 1655560, 2266890, 2170124, 2041615, 1141524, 1588501, 623380, 733976, 2325276, 502563, 1878824, 2081578, 2015530, 2241325, 1679152, 2041653, 896313, 1092926, 746815, 1749828, 533829, 2053959, 426824, 2350926, 678224, 455511, 2208607, 1093474, 627043, 723811, 560493, 2033521, 2334069, 1081722, 623485, 1694081, 2262917, 1011081, 2048393, 1896851, 1258901, 2241438, 1983397, 1850283, 726445, 2150320, 1470385, 2231218, 2155952, 1787828, 457650, 2203583, 796098, 2314180, 2094538, 560588, 1227730, 2157012, 1775573, 1845206, 1478103, 1998813, 1479648, 1566688, 1584099, 2299880, 1262570, 2150382, 2150388, 1521144, 425465, 1478141, 1298430, 2355199]",Russian,['NORP'],1,7,-262.3649,91.60149999999997,-353.9664,241,640,881,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
233,"[615453, 1296929, 2355237, 2023465, 2338356, 429128, 1497161, 931403, 2311760, 597596, 2158690, 2274916, 2023525, 2224758, 1635467, 1936012, 2024078, 2345105, 494236, 625314, 1511077, 2333865, 2212524, 2226371, 1024713, 2242251, 1276621, 1907918, 1549013, 1918680, 1860324, 1276661, 2279161, 2042107, 1251068, 959740, 704263, 1655560, 2266890, 2170124, 623380, 733976, 1587993, 2325276, 502563, 2081578, 2241325, 1679152, 2041653, 896313, 1749828, 2053959, 426824, 2350926, 678224, 455511, 2208607, 627043, 560493, 2334069, 1081722, 623485, 1694081, 2262917, 2048393, 1258901, 2241438, 1983397, 2155952, 1470385, 2231218, 1787828, 2203583, 796098, 2314180, 2094538, 1775573, 1845206, 1998813, 1479648, 1566688, 2299880, 1262570, 2150382, 1521144, 1478141, 1298430]",Vladimir Putin,['PERSON'],1,7,-21.2171,10.534699999999996,-31.751799999999996,28,64,92,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
234,"[1694081, 2063107, 2262917, 704263, 1011081, 1635467, 2170124, 2104843, 2345105, 1896851, 1979029, 2325276, 2101788, 2241438, 1296929, 502563, 1511077, 2351271, 2333865, 2081578, 457650, 2338356, 2203583, 2226371, 2314180, 2053959, 429128, 1497161, 2094538, 2242251, 734285, 2350926, 678224, 1549013, 1775573, 455511, 1918680, 2062426, 2208607, 2158690, 627043, 1860324, 1093474, 1584099, 2274916, 2299880, 517355, 560493, 2033521, 1006066, 2150388, 425589, 1521144, 2042107, 1251068, 1298430]",Russians,['NORP'],1,7,-29.3144,10.403,-39.717399999999984,28,72,100,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
235,"[429128, 627043, 1521144]",Makariv,"['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,7,-1.2174999999999998,0.0,-1.2174999999999998,0,2,2,"['2022-04-06', '2022-03-28', '2022-03-31']"
236,[429128],"Kyiv, Associated Press",['ORG'],1,7,-0.6908,0.0,-0.6908,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
237,[429128],Yasnohorodka,['GPE'],1,7,-0.5859,0.0,-0.5859,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
238,"[1694081, 2063107, 2262917, 704263, 1011081, 2170124, 1936012, 2041615, 2345105, 449428, 1141524, 1258901, 2325276, 494236, 2241438, 2101788, 2355237, 2351271, 1878824, 2333865, 2081578, 2212524, 457650, 2338356, 1787828, 1092926, 2203583, 2053825, 2053959, 429128, 2094538, 2242251, 1907918, 2350926, 678224, 1775573, 1478103, 1918680, 1998813, 2208607, 627043, 1860324, 1584099, 2299880, 1963245, 560493, 2033521, 1006066, 1682674, 2150388, 2334069, 2224758, 1276661, 1521144, 2042107, 1298430]",Kyiv,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-20.2467,9.951400000000003,-30.198100000000004,27,51,78,"['2022-04-20', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
239,"[429128, 2338356]",Kyrylo Budanov,['PERSON'],1,7,0.9955,0.9955,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-03-28', '2022-05-05']"
240,"[2104843, 615453, 1296929, 2355237, 615461, 2023465, 1354803, 2338356, 429128, 1497161, 931403, 2311760, 597596, 2158690, 2274916, 2023525, 2224758, 755329, 1936012, 2345105, 1979029, 494236, 1511077, 2351271, 2333865, 2212524, 413890, 2226371, 1024713, 1089225, 1276621, 1549013, 1918680, 1276661, 2042107, 1251068, 959740, 704263, 1655560, 2266890, 2170124, 623380, 733976, 1878824, 2081578, 2241325, 1679152, 746815, 533829, 2053959, 2350926, 678224, 455511, 2208607, 627043, 560493, 2334069, 1081722, 1694081, 2262917, 2048393, 1896851, 1258901, 1983397, 2155952, 2231218, 2314180, 2094538, 2157012, 1775573, 1845206, 1998813, 1479648, 1566688, 1262570, 1521144, 425465, 1298430]",Putin,['PERSON'],1,7,-32.3228,31.861000000000004,-64.18380000000005,81,117,198,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
241,[429128],North,['GPE'],1,7,0.8176,0.8176,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28']
242,"[429128, 1470385, 2134015, 471744]",South Korea,['GPE'],1,7,0.7477999999999999,1.4662,-0.7184,2,1,3,"['2022-04-05', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-28']"
243,[429128],Budanov,['PERSON'],1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-28']
244,"[1694081, 2063107, 704263, 2170124, 1792524, 2345105, 1258901, 733976, 615453, 1296929, 1983397, 2351271, 2333865, 2081578, 2023465, 2155952, 1470385, 2338356, 1787828, 796098, 2053959, 429128, 1024713, 2094538, 2242251, 1497161, 2350926, 2157012, 1549013, 1775573, 455511, 1918680, 2208607, 1479648, 2158690, 627043, 1860324, 2219618, 2334069, 2224758, 1521144, 425465, 2042107]",Kremlin,['ORG'],1,7,-22.2972,11.739599999999998,-34.03679999999999,28,62,90,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-26']"
245,"[2053825, 2158690, 627043, 2262917, 429128, 1011081, 2081578, 2242251, 2170124, 1963245, 2212524, 2041615, 2345105, 2224758, 2208607]",Kharkiv,"['ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-6.7157,0.3059,-7.021599999999999,2,13,15,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-20', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-16', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
246,"[627043, 1584099, 2355237, 704263, 429128, 1011081, 734285, 1963245, 457650, 1258901, 1521144]",Chernihiv,"['NORP', 'PERSON', 'GPE']",1,7,-1.6294000000000002,1.6963000000000001,-3.3257000000000003,4,7,11,"['2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
247,"[429128, 1011081, 2150320, 425589, 2026013, 1298430]",Sumy,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-0.4405,1.0,-1.4405000000000001,2,3,5,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-22']"
248,[429128],Mykola Sunhurovskyi,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.25,0.0,-0.25,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
249,[429128],Razumkov Center,['ORG'],1,7,-0.25,0.0,-0.25,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
250,"[1694081, 2010882, 2063107, 2262917, 704263, 1011081, 2048393, 2104843, 2170124, 2041615, 2345105, 1258901, 1979029, 2144793, 2325276, 2026013, 2241438, 2101788, 2355237, 2351271, 2114216, 2333865, 2081578, 2212524, 2150320, 2053825, 2226371, 429128, 2094538, 2242251, 1907918, 2350926, 678224, 1998813, 2208607, 2158690, 627043, 1860324, 1963245, 2150382, 2033521, 2150388, 425589, 2224758, 1521144, 2279161, 1298430, 2355199]",Mariupol,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-57.7641,18.0278,-75.79189999999998,46,128,174,"['2022-04-20', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-05-07', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-09', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
251,"[429128, 2010882]",the British Ministry of Defense,['ORG'],1,7,-0.6565,0.128,-0.7845,1,1,2,"['2022-03-28', '2022-04-13']"
252,"[1694081, 2010882, 2262917, 704263, 1011081, 2048393, 1635467, 1792524, 1936012, 2041615, 2345105, 1258901, 821274, 625314, 1983397, 1878824, 2081578, 2338356, 1787828, 1092926, 2203583, 2053825, 2226371, 2314180, 2053959, 429128, 1497161, 2094538, 2242251, 734285, 1907918, 2350926, 1276621, 1549013, 1918680, 2062426, 597596, 1998813, 2158690, 627043, 1860324, 723811, 1262570, 1963245, 2033521, 2346100, 1276661, 2224758, 1521144, 1081722, 2042107, 1298430]",Volodymyr Zelenskyy,['PERSON'],1,7,-6.9576,8.321100000000001,-15.278699999999997,20,30,50,"['2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-05-02', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
253,"[2028224, 1296929, 1093474, 1694081, 2355237, 704263, 429128, 2351271, 2023465, 1963245, 734285, 2041615, 2155952, 2033521, 1354803, 1251068]",Crimea,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-0.5486000000000002,3.4815,-4.0301,9,10,19,"['2022-04-15', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-22', '2022-03-28', '2022-05-09', '2022-05-07', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03']"
254,[429128],the Institute for the Study of War,['ORG'],1,7,-0.8807,0.0,-0.8807,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
255,[429128],Philips P. O'Brien,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.7269,0.0,-0.7269,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
256,[429128],the University of St. Andrews,['ORG'],1,7,-0.7269,0.0,-0.7269,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
257,"[2262917, 704263, 1011081, 2345105, 1258901, 2325276, 2101788, 2333865, 2212524, 2241325, 2231218, 2203583, 2053825, 429128, 2094538, 2350926, 1998813, 2158690, 627043, 2299880, 2346100, 2224758, 1521144]",Lviv,"['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,7,-5.7757000000000005,0.5503,-6.326000000000001,3,13,16,"['2022-05-05', '2022-05-06', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-23', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
258,"[1228546, 2345105, 1141524, 528021, 1258901, 494236, 1878824, 517164, 2241325, 1470385, 2231218, 896313, 372284, 2203583, 2226371, 1749828, 2314180, 429128, 2094538, 2350926, 2311760, 455511, 1262570, 426218, 517355, 2224758]",Poland,['GPE'],1,7,-4.683,11.780000000000001,-16.463,29,37,66,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-25', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-09', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03']"
259,[429128],O'Brien,['PERSON'],1,7,0.0772,0.0772,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-28']
260,"[2053825, 2010882, 1860324, 429128, 2170124, 2212524, 1907918, 2350926, 678224, 425589, 2224758]",Kherson,['PERSON'],1,7,-6.0804,0.0,-6.080400000000001,0,13,13,"['2022-05-05', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27', '2022-03-31']"
261,"[2010882, 627043, 429128, 2242251, 2350926, 2345105]",Mykolaiv,"['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,7,-3.9741999999999997,0.0,-3.9742000000000006,0,8,8,"['2022-04-19', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-13', '2022-03-28', '2022-05-06', '2022-03-31']"
262,"[704263, 429128, 2041615, 678224, 2033521]",Odesa,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-1.7939,0.2263,-2.0202,1,5,6,"['2022-04-15', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-28', '2022-03-31']"
263,"[429128, 2219618, 2212524, 1907918]",Trans-Dniester,['ORG'],1,7,0.922,2.7686,-1.8466,5,3,8,"['2022-04-26', '2022-04-10', '2022-03-28']"
264,"[2158690, 2219618, 429128, 2299880, 2212524, 1907918, 2150382, 1478103, 2042107, 746815]",Moldova,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-1.1722000000000001,3.7245999999999997,-4.8968,8,11,19,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-13', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31']"
265,"[1011081, 2048393, 587411, 1258901, 733976, 2241438, 2351271, 2023465, 2241325, 2231218, 471744, 2053959, 429128, 931403, 1907918, 2350926, 1845206, 1093474, 627043, 1860324, 2224758, 425465, 1081722]",Western,['NORP'],1,7,-4.4987,3.6515,-8.1502,9,16,25,"['2022-05-05', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-13', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-14', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-07', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
266,"[2262917, 704263, 1011081, 1635467, 528021, 1258901, 1587993, 824475, 2355237, 1983397, 2023465, 2212524, 1470385, 457650, 2041653, 372284, 746815, 1749828, 429128, 1024713, 2094538, 2242251, 931403, 734285, 1907918, 1845206, 455511, 2208607, 627043, 1860324, 2023525, 2299880, 1262570, 1963245, 1682674, 425589, 2224758, 1081722]",NATO,['ORG'],1,7,0.3179000000000006,24.1066,-23.788699999999988,54,48,102,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-18', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-26']"
267,"[2351271, 429128, 1024713, 2299880, 931403]",the Soviet Union,['GPE'],1,7,-3.6244,0.0,-3.6244,0,5,5,"['2022-04-02', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-05-07', '2022-04-03']"
268,"[429128, 2062426, 943443, 2346100]",Afghanistan,['GPE'],1,7,-1.2596999999999998,0.6124,-1.8720999999999999,1,3,4,"['2022-04-02', '2022-04-16', '2022-03-28', '2022-05-01']"
269,"[429128, 2042107, 704263]",Volodymyr Fesenko,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.5631,0.4767,-1.0398,1,2,3,"['2022-04-01', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-13']"
270,[429128],Penta Center,['ORG'],1,7,-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
271,"[429128, 2042107, 704263]",Fesenko,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,"['2022-04-01', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-13']"
272,[429128],Tactics,['ORG'],1,7,-0.5574,0.0,-0.5574,0,1,1,['2022-03-28']
273,"[2262917, 704263, 1011081, 2048393, 1635467, 2266890, 1936012, 2104843, 2345105, 1258901, 1296929, 625314, 2355237, 1878824, 2338356, 1787828, 2203583, 2053825, 2053959, 429128, 1497161, 1089225, 2242251, 931403, 1276621, 1907918, 2350926, 1918680, 2062426, 1998813, 2208607, 2158690, 627043, 1860324, 723811, 2299880, 1262570, 1963245, 1276661, 1521144, 1081722, 2042107]",Zelenskyy,"['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,7,-12.8111,14.7827,-27.593799999999995,32,49,81,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-23', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-25', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
274,"[429128, 627043, 1998813, 704263]",Karmanau,['ORG'],1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-12', '2022-03-28', '2022-03-31']"
275,"[2053825, 2158690, 1860324, 429128, 2242251, 2170124, 824475, 1998813, 2208607]",Robert Burns,['PERSON'],1,7,0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-20', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-16']"
276,[429128],Matthew Lee,['PERSON'],1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-28']
277,"[429128, 2242251, 1860324, 2170124]",Danica Kirka,"['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-21', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-19']"
278,"[627043, 2212524, 560493, 2155952, 2224758]",Chernobyl,['GPE'],1,1,-2.762,0.8446,-3.6066,3,6,9,"['2022-03-30', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-22', '2022-03-31']"
279,"[2063107, 2262917, 704263, 1011081, 1635467, 2170124, 1936012, 2104843, 2041615, 2345105, 1258901, 1979029, 824475, 2325276, 494236, 2241438, 2101788, 1511077, 1983397, 2081578, 1679152, 457650, 1787828, 746815, 2203583, 2053825, 2314180, 2094538, 2242251, 734285, 1907918, 678224, 1775573, 1918680, 1998813, 2208607, 2158690, 627043, 723811, 1584099, 2299880, 2150382, 2033521, 2346100, 425589, 2150388, 1521144, 2042107]",Ukrainians,['NORP'],1,1,-18.3655,14.765499999999998,-33.131,33,57,90,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-23', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-01', '2022-05-02', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
280,[627043],Energoatom,['GPE'],1,1,-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-03-31']
281,"[627043, 1860324, 1011081, 2094538, 2170124, 1775573, 1521144, 2325276, 2026013, 2208607]",Iryna Vereshchuk,['PERSON'],1,1,0.21619999999999998,0.8867,-0.6705,4,1,5,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-21', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
283,[627043],IAEA,['ORG'],1,1,-0.296,0.0,-0.296,0,1,1,['2022-03-31']
284,[627043],Edwin Lyman,['PERSON'],1,1,0.1154,0.1154,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-31']
285,[627043],the U.S.-based Union of Concerned Scientists,['ORG'],1,1,0.1154,0.1154,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-31']
286,[627043],Oleksandr Palviuk,['ORG'],1,1,-0.5267,0.0,-0.5267,0,1,1,['2022-03-31']
287,"[627043, 1860324, 704263]",Irpin,"['ORG', 'GPE']",1,1,-0.6455,0.34,-0.9854999999999999,1,2,3,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-09', '2022-03-31']"
288,"[678224, 627043, 560493]",Hostomel,"['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,1,-1.1636,0.0,-1.1636,0,2,2,"['2022-03-30', '2022-03-31']"
289,[627043],Pavliuk,['ORG'],1,1,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-03-31']
290,"[627043, 1998813]",Brovary,"['NORP', 'PERSON']",1,1,-1.2696,0.0,-1.2696,0,2,2,"['2022-04-12', '2022-03-31']"
291,[627043],Ukrainian Human Rights,['ORG'],1,1,-0.765,0.0,-0.765,0,1,1,['2022-03-31']
292,[627043],Lyudmyla Denisova Ukraine,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.765,0.0,-0.765,0,1,1,['2022-03-31']
293,"[627043, 1749828, 1011081, 1963245, 1470385, 1587993]",Jens Stoltenberg,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.5854000000000001,1.1951,-1.7805,3,3,6,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
294,"[1587993, 627043, 1963245]",Stoltenberg,"['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,1,0.6813,1.2894,-0.6081,3,2,5,"['2022-04-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31']"
295,"[2010882, 627043, 1584099, 2355237, 2094538, 1792524, 2350926, 2345105, 1787828, 2224758, 1521144, 2208607]",Luhansk,['GPE'],1,1,-3.7145,0.0,-3.7145,0,8,8,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-18', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-13', '2022-05-09', '2022-04-27', '2022-05-06', '2022-03-31']"
296,"[2010882, 627043, 2262917, 2355237, 2242251, 2104843, 2350926, 2345105]",Donetsk,['GPE'],1,1,-3.3970000000000002,0.0516,-3.4486000000000003,1,6,7,"['2022-04-19', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-29', '2022-05-09', '2022-05-06', '2022-03-31']"
297,[627043],Denis Pushilin,['PERSON'],1,1,0.0516,0.0516,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-03-31']
298,"[471744, 1296929, 627043, 757828, 1655560, 1251068, 615453]",Italian,['NORP'],1,1,0.4549,1.3559999999999999,-0.9011,4,3,7,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-31']"
299,"[471744, 627043, 757828, 1655560, 615453]",Mario Draghi,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.46269999999999994,0.4384,-0.9011,2,3,5,"['2022-04-07', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-31']"
300,"[471744, 625314, 627043, 578564, 723811, 1024713, 587411]",Australia,['GPE'],1,1,-2.4032999999999998,3.3835,-5.7867999999999995,5,9,14,"['2022-03-26', '2022-03-30', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
301,"[1024713, 625314, 627043]",Jeremy Fleming,['PERSON'],1,1,1.2925,1.2925,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
302,"[2010882, 2104843, 2170124, 1936012, 2041615, 2345105, 1979029, 824475, 2101788, 2212524, 1470385, 457650, 1787828, 2137276, 2028224, 2242251, 734285, 2350926, 678224, 943443, 1998813, 2208607, 627043, 1584099, 2274916, 560493, 2150388, 425589, 1298430]",Pentagon,['ORG'],1,1,-11.9117,6.0696,-17.9813,18,34,52,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26']"
303,[627043],Javelin anti-tank,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-03-31']
304,"[2028224, 2010882, 627043, 1584099, 2274916, 2104843, 2212524, 734285, 2350926, 560493, 1936012, 2345105, 457650, 2150388, 425589, 2101788, 2137276, 1998813]",John Kirby,['PERSON'],1,1,-1.4002000000000001,3.1235000000000004,-4.523700000000001,6,11,17,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-19', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-30', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-26', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-22', '2022-03-31']"
305,"[2219618, 627043, 704263, 2333865, 1792524, 2241325, 2155952, 2338356, 455511, 733976, 425465, 2208607]",Dmitry Peskov,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.6927,0.7985,-1.4911999999999999,2,5,7,"['2022-04-20', '2022-05-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-22', '2022-03-31']"
306,"[627043, 533829, 1635467, 1918680, 623292, 2203583]",the State Department,['ORG'],1,1,-1.1498,0.7579,-1.9077000000000002,1,3,4,"['2022-04-25', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-30', '2022-03-31']"
307,[704263],Penta,['GPE'],1,2,-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-04-01']
308,[704263],the International Committee for the Red Cross,['ORG'],1,2,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01']
309,"[2158690, 704263]",Andryushchenko,['PERSON'],1,2,0.02190000000000003,0.6705,-0.6486,1,1,2,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-01']"
310,"[2028224, 2053825, 2158690, 704263, 2170124, 2212524, 2041615, 2224758, 2042107, 2325276, 2208607]",Telegram,"['NORP', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,2,-3.9666,0.6705,-4.6371,1,8,9,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-20', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-21', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-27']"
311,"[2226371, 2026013, 704263]",Red Cross,['ORG'],1,2,-1.6627999999999998,0.4019,-2.0646999999999998,1,3,4,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-26']"
313,"[471744, 2023525, 704263, 2053959, 1024713, 2023465, 1258901, 455511]",Emmanuel Macron,['PERSON'],1,2,-2.2352,0.4019,-2.6371,1,5,6,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-03']"
315,[704263],Roberta Metsola,['PERSON'],1,2,-0.6249,0.0,-0.6249,0,1,1,['2022-04-01']
316,"[1704546, 1228546, 726445, 704263]",n’t,['GPE'],1,2,0.9194,0.9194,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-05', '2022-04-03']"
317,[704263],Maksim Marchenko,['PERSON'],1,2,-0.5574,0.0,-0.5574,0,1,1,['2022-04-01']
318,[704263],Iskander,['ORG'],1,2,-0.1655,0.0,-0.1655,0,1,1,['2022-04-01']
319,"[2042107, 704263]",Marchenko,['PERSON'],1,2,-0.3182,0.0,-0.3182,0,1,1,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-13']"
320,"[704263, 2333865, 2242251, 2350926, 2041615, 2033521, 2345105]",Russian Defense Ministry,['ORG'],1,2,-3.1297,0.256,-3.3857,2,5,7,"['2022-04-15', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-19', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-05-06']"
321,"[1860324, 704263, 2333865, 2081578, 2242251, 2350926, 2041615, 2033521, 2345105]",Igor Konashenkov,['PERSON'],1,2,-2.6616999999999997,0.7240000000000001,-3.3857,4,5,9,"['2022-04-15', '2022-04-19', '2022-05-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-17']"
322,"[704263, 2033521, 1787828, 1979029, 2224758]",Belgorod,['GPE'],1,2,-0.8818,0.0,-0.8818,0,2,2,"['2022-04-08', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-11']"
323,"[1296929, 1251068, 704263]",Rosneft,['ORG'],1,2,-0.8573,0.0,-0.8573,0,1,1,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-04']"
324,"[2158690, 704263]",Oleksiy Danilov,['PERSON'],1,2,0.2551,0.2551,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-01']"
325,[704263],national security council,['ORG'],1,2,0.1779,0.1779,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-01']
326,"[777480, 1138187, 704263]",Fox,"['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,2,-1.9737,0.128,-2.1017,1,3,4,['2022-04-01']
327,[704263],Popasna,['GPE'],1,2,0.2732,0.2732,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-01']
328,"[2224758, 2208607, 704263]",Rubizhne,"['NORP', 'PERSON', 'GPE']",1,2,0.12700000000000006,0.9828,-0.8557999999999999,2,2,4,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-20']"
329,[704263],Lila,['PERSON'],1,2,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01']
330,[704263],Andriy,['ORG'],1,2,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01']
331,[704263],Andrea Rosa,['PERSON'],1,2,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-01']
332,[734285],Robert Abrams,['PERSON'],1,1,-1.521,0.0,-1.521,0,2,2,['2022-04-01']
333,[734285],Korea,['GPE'],1,1,-0.6808,0.0,-0.6808,0,1,1,['2022-04-01']
334,"[1470385, 457650, 824475, 734285]",Javelin,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.9967,0.2023,-1.199,1,3,4,"['2022-04-01', '2022-04-05', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28']"
335,[734285],the New York Times,['ORG'],1,1,-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-04-01']
336,"[1228546, 517635, 1655560, 1011081, 2048393, 1141524, 1258901, 733976, 615453, 1983397, 2333865, 2023465, 2212524, 517164, 896313, 1578681, 796098, 1749828, 757828, 1024713, 560588, 734285, 2311760, 425589, 2224758, 425465, 2134015]",Germany,['GPE'],1,1,0.10229999999999982,10.168499999999998,-10.066199999999998,22,25,47,"['2022-05-04', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-08', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
337,"[419795, 734285]",Congressional,['NORP'],1,1,0.2459,0.3262,-0.0803,1,1,2,"['2022-04-01', '2022-03-28']"
338,"[425589, 457650, 734285]",Tod Wolters,['PERSON'],1,1,1.0859,1.0859,0.0,3,0,3,"['2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28']"
339,[734285],Abrams,['PERSON'],1,1,-1.2362,0.2263,-1.4625,1,2,3,['2022-04-01']
340,"[2028224, 2053959, 1792524, 734285, 2101788]",Luis Martinez,['PERSON'],1,1,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01']"
341,"[1011081, 1258901]",BUCHA,"['NORP', 'ORG']",1,7,-1.7641,0.0,-1.7641,0,2,2,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-03']"
342,"[1694081, 1655560, 1011081, 1635467, 2170124, 1792524, 2041615, 1258901, 1588501, 1983397, 2150320, 1679152, 1787828, 2053825, 2053959, 1497161, 1276621, 1907918, 1227730, 2157012, 1775573, 1845206, 1478103, 2062426, 1998813, 2208607, 1566688, 1584099, 1860324, 2150382, 1682674, 2334069, 1276661, 1521144, 1298430]",Bucha,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-27.453,5.3849,-32.8379,13,54,67,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-04-15', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03']"
343,"[1228546, 1655560, 1011081, 2345105, 1141524, 1258901, 733976, 824475, 615453, 1296929, 502563, 1983397, 1878824, 2023465, 2081578, 2241325, 726445, 1470385, 2231218, 457650, 1787828, 896313, 2203583, 2053825, 1749828, 757828, 1024713, 2242251, 1907918, 2350926, 2311760, 1775573, 1918680, 2208607, 1479648, 1566688, 1860324, 2023525, 1262570, 426218, 517355, 2224758, 425465, 1251068]",European,['NORP'],1,7,-10.0869,7.314000000000001,-17.4009,19,39,58,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-04-17', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-25', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-27']"
344,"[796098, 757828, 1983397, 896313, 1655560, 1011081, 2333865, 1262570, 2023465, 425465, 1081722, 1251068]",the European Union,['ORG'],1,7,-1.912,2.1539,-4.0659,5,5,10,"['2022-05-04', '2022-04-04', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-14', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03']"
345,"[2028224, 2053825, 1860324, 2262917, 1011081, 1907918, 2041615, 2155952, 2033521, 1549013, 1258901, 2325276]",Defense Ministry,['ORG'],1,7,-3.3935,1.1583,-4.5518,5,10,15,"['2022-04-15', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-22', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03']"
346,"[1011081, 2137276, 1258901]",anti-Russian,['NORP'],1,7,-0.675,0.4215,-1.0965,1,2,3,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-03']"
347,[1011081],Hanna Herega,['PERSON'],1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03']
348,[1011081],Herega,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.3612,0.0,-0.3612,0,1,1,['2022-04-03']
349,"[2028224, 1011081]",Oleksiy Arestovych,['PERSON'],1,7,-1.1364,0.0,-1.1364,0,2,2,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-03']"
350,[1011081],Grammy Awards,['ORG'],1,7,0.7579,0.7579,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03']
351,[1011081],Las Vegas,['GPE'],1,7,0.7579,0.7579,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03']
352,"[2114216, 1011081, 1497161, 2015530, 2150382, 1896851, 1276661, 1588501, 1478103, 1845206]",the U.N. Security Council,['ORG'],1,7,3.4874,3.9396999999999998,-0.45230000000000004,8,2,10,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03']"
353,"[1566688, 1497161, 1011081, 2150382, 1258901, 2042107]",Security Council,['ORG'],1,7,0.7967,1.5794,-0.7827,4,2,6,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03']"
354,"[1011081, 1258901]",Motyzhyn,['GPE'],1,7,-0.6705,0.0,-0.6705,0,1,1,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-03']"
355,"[898818, 615461, 2203583, 2299880, 1011081, 340497, 1682674, 2137276, 1787828, 1438965, 1896851, 455511, 1587993, 623292, 2241438, 2208607]",State,['ORG'],1,7,-1.5231999999999999,1.7776999999999996,-3.3009,7,6,13,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-25', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
356,"[1011081, 2208607]",Anthony Blinken,['PERSON'],1,7,-1.3460999999999999,0.0,-1.3460999999999999,0,2,2,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-03']"
357,"[2028224, 2053825, 848839, 1011081, 2212524, 1792524, 1936012, 1682674, 793395, 2346100, 2207612]",CNN,['ORG'],1,7,-4.1006,0.128,-4.2286,1,7,8,"['2022-04-25', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-08', '2022-05-01', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03']"
358,"[1011081, 2053825, 2262917]",Vitali Klitschko,['PERSON'],1,7,-1.3979,0.0,-1.3979,0,3,3,"['2022-04-29', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-03']"
359,"[1655560, 1011081, 1141524, 1258901, 733976, 1983397, 1878824, 2333865, 2023465, 517164, 2241325, 726445, 2231218, 1787828, 2041653, 896313, 746815, 757828, 2242251, 1907918, 2311760, 1775573, 1479648, 1860324, 2023525, 1262570, 517355, 2334069, 1081722]",EU,"['ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,3.2439,19.1994,-15.955499999999999,45,38,83,"['2022-04-05', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
360,"[1011081, 2081578, 2094538, 2212524, 2333865, 2350926, 2041615, 510857, 1470385, 476817, 1936012, 2338356, 1549013, 425589, 540892, 1998813, 2241438, 2203583]",Defense,['ORG'],1,7,0.8317,3.2592000000000008,-2.4275,16,5,21,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-05', '2022-04-15', '2022-05-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-25', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-12', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-03', '2022-04-17']"
361,"[1011081, 2212524]",Christine Lambrecht,['PERSON'],1,7,0.6047,0.6047,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-26', '2022-04-03']"
362,"[1228546, 1655560, 1011081, 1141524, 1258901, 733976, 615453, 1296929, 502563, 2212524, 896313, 1578681, 471744, 796098, 426824, 560588, 425465, 2311760, 2279161, 1251068]",German,['NORP'],1,7,2.9010999999999996,8.755300000000002,-5.8542,22,13,35,"['2022-04-30', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-25', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
363,[1011081],ARD,['ORG'],1,7,0.128,0.128,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-03']
366,[1011081],RBK Ukraina,['PERSON'],1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-03']
367,"[1011081, 920306, 494236]",Istanbul,['GPE'],1,7,-0.6683,0.0,-0.6683,0,2,2,"['2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-03']"
368,"[1011081, 1258901]",Qena,['PERSON'],1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-03']"
369,"[2158690, 2262917, 1011081, 2333865, 2212524, 2350926, 2345105, 1258901, 2224758, 1521144, 2325276]",Yuras Karmanau,['PERSON'],1,7,0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-23', '2022-05-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-29', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-26', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-03']"
370,[1521144],ANDRIIVKA,['ORG'],1,7,-0.9337,0.0,-0.9337,0,1,1,['2022-04-06']
371,[1521144],Vadym Boichenko,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.7906,0.0,-0.7906,0,1,1,['2022-04-06']
372,[1521144],Boichenko,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.4939,0.0,-0.4939,0,1,1,['2022-04-06']
373,"[1521144, 2333865, 2325276]",the Red Cross,['ORG'],1,7,-0.4504,0.0263,-0.4767,1,1,2,"['2022-04-06', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-04']"
374,[1521144],Capturing Mariupol,['ORG'],1,7,0.5106,0.5106,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06']
375,"[1694081, 1696099, 2355237, 2351271, 1850283, 2338356, 1521144]",Nazis,['NORP'],1,7,-3.2072000000000003,0.4286,-3.6358,2,6,8,"['2022-05-05', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-07', '2022-05-09', '2022-05-07']"
376,"[2063107, 1936012, 1551502, 528021, 1964200, 428457, 639144, 2186286, 2155952, 559922, 2226371, 1907918, 2350926, 1775573, 1093474, 1963245, 2033521, 1006066, 1543153, 1521144, 2042107, 1251068]",The Associated Press,['ORG'],1,7,-0.6637,2.7381,-3.4018000000000006,6,7,13,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-15', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-24', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-02', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
377,[1521144],Andriivka,['ORG'],1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-06']
378,[1521144],Valentyna Klymenko,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-04-06']
379,"[1521144, 1907918]",Borodyanka,"['ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-06', '2022-04-10']"
380,"[2158690, 2212524, 1792524, 1787828, 1521144, 2325276]",Pavlo Kyrylenko,"['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,7,-5.1643,0.0,-5.1643,0,7,7,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-08', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-26']"
381,[1521144],Sievierodonetsk,['GPE'],1,7,-0.34,0.0,-0.34,0,1,1,['2022-04-06']
382,"[1521144, 2262917]",Dnipropetrovsk,['GPE'],1,7,-0.4588,0.0,-0.4588,0,1,1,"['2022-04-06', '2022-04-29']"
383,"[1655560, 2023465, 726445, 1775573, 1521144]",The European Union,['ORG'],1,7,-0.34560000000000013,1.1939,-1.5395,2,4,6,"['2022-04-07', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-14']"
384,"[1296929, 1497161, 2266890, 733976, 1521144, 425465, 1251068]",the United Kingdom,['GPE'],1,7,3.2821,3.5305,-0.2484,7,1,8,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-29', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28']"
385,"[1497161, 1635467, 1896851, 1588501, 1478103, 1521144]",the Security Council,['ORG'],1,7,0.3155,2.2044,-1.8889,6,4,10,"['2022-04-05', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-07', '2022-03-29']"
386,"[2262917, 2048393, 1635467, 2024078, 2345105, 1896851, 1588501, 2325276, 2333865, 2015530, 2212524, 2150320, 623292, 2226371, 1497161, 2350926, 1845206, 1478103, 2208607, 2219618, 2150382, 1682674, 1438965, 1276661, 1521144, 2279161, 2134015, 959740, 2355199]",U.N.,['ORG'],1,7,-9.872499999999999,15.205600000000002,-25.078100000000003,27,43,70,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-03-29', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-21', '2022-03-27', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-02', '2022-05-03', '2022-05-08', '2022-04-22', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-26']"
387,"[1521144, 2150382, 2114216]",Dmitry Polyansky,['PERSON'],1,7,-1.27,0.0,-1.27,0,3,3,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-11']"
388,"[1521144, 2048393]",Soviet Union’s,['GPE'],1,7,-1.53,0.0,-1.53,0,2,2,"['2022-04-06', '2022-04-13']"
389,[1521144],Cara Anna,['PERSON'],1,7,0.4215,0.4215,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-06']
390,"[1521144, 1478103]",Edith M. Lederer,['PERSON'],1,7,0.843,0.843,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-06']"
391,"[2219618, 2226371, 2262917, 2015530, 1635467, 2350926, 2150382, 1682674, 587411, 1276661, 1845206, 1478103, 1521144, 623292]",the United Nations,['ORG'],1,7,7.2523,9.8376,-2.5853,17,3,20,"['2022-03-27', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-06', '2022-04-04', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-26', '2022-04-11', '2022-03-31']"
392,[1860324],Civilian,['NORP'],1,0,-0.9081,0.0,-0.9081,0,1,1,['2022-04-09']
393,"[2053825, 1860324, 2262917, 2242251, 2041615]",KYIV,['GPE'],1,0,-4.2772,0.0,-4.2772,0,5,5,"['2022-04-15', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-29', '2022-04-16']"
394,"[2053825, 2010882, 1860324, 2333865, 2081578, 2242251, 1792524, 2150382, 2041615, 1787828, 2208607]",Kramatorsk,"['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,0,-11.7836,0.0,-11.783599999999998,0,18,18,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-19', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17']"
395,"[1860324, 1983397, 1878824, 2081578, 1907918]",Austrian,['NORP'],1,0,-3.8296,1.3194,-5.149000000000001,2,9,11,"['2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17']"
396,[1860324],Britan,['PERSON'],1,0,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,['2022-04-09']
397,[1860324],Sky,['PERSON'],1,0,-0.8885,0.0,-0.8885,0,1,1,['2022-04-09']
398,"[1860324, 1907918]",Kharkiv — Ukraine’s,['ORG'],1,0,-0.5859,0.0,-0.5859,0,1,1,"['2022-04-10', '2022-04-09']"
399,"[1860324, 2194486]",CBS,['ORG'],1,0,-0.3589,0.0023,-0.3612,1,1,2,"['2022-04-25', '2022-04-09']"
400,"[2155952, 1860324]",Crimean,['NORP'],1,0,-0.3182,0.0,-0.3182,0,1,1,"['2022-04-09', '2022-04-22']"
401,[1860324],Peninula,['NORP'],1,0,-0.3182,0.0,-0.3182,0,1,1,['2022-04-09']
402,"[1228546, 1860324, 1983397, 2023525, 517164, 2241325, 726445, 2311760, 2231218, 1787828, 1276661, 2224758, 2041653, 1918680, 896313, 1081722, 746815]",European Union,['ORG'],1,0,-2.6420999999999997,2.3652,-5.0073,7,10,17,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-08', '2022-05-02', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-13', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-03', '2022-03-31']"
403,[1860324],Konashenkov,['PERSON'],1,0,-0.6908,0.0,-0.6908,0,1,1,['2022-04-09']
404,"[1860324, 1983397, 1878824, 2081578, 1907918]",Karl Nehammer,['PERSON'],1,0,-1.4824000000000002,1.3194,-2.8018,2,5,7,"['2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-11', '2022-04-17']"
405,"[896313, 1860324, 1983397, 1907918]",Austria,"['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,0,-0.06520000000000001,0.8831,-0.9482999999999999,2,3,5,"['2022-03-30', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-04-11']"
406,"[1860324, 2333865, 2350926, 1907918, 2345105]",Anna,['PERSON'],1,0,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-05-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-09', '2022-05-06']"
407,"[1860324, 2224758]",Jill Lawless,['PERSON'],1,0,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-04-27', '2022-04-09']"
408,"[2158690, 2170124, 1963245, 1907918]",Maxar Technologies,['ORG'],1,7,-1.1018999999999999,0.128,-1.2299,1,2,3,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-10', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-11']"
409,"[1963245, 1907918]",Velykyi Burluk,['PERSON'],1,7,0.128,0.128,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-10', '2022-04-11']"
410,"[2311760, 1276661, 1907918]",the European Commission,['ORG'],1,7,-0.3662,0.4404,-0.8066,1,2,3,"['2022-04-04', '2022-04-10', '2022-05-02']"
411,"[1024713, 726445, 1907918, 587411, 2339287, 733976, 425465, 1138141, 2208607]",Canada,['GPE'],1,7,2.1016,2.4699,-0.3683,4,2,6,"['2022-04-20', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-10', '2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-03-29', '2022-03-28', '2022-04-03']"
412,"[1878824, 1907918]",World Bank,['ORG'],1,7,1.2192,1.2192,0.0,2,0,2,"['2022-04-10', '2022-04-09']"
413,"[1878824, 1963245]",Ukraine LONDON,['GPE'],1,7,-0.1674,0.6597,-0.8271,1,1,2,"['2022-04-09', '2022-04-11']"
414,"[2355237, 1963245]",republics,['GPE'],1,7,0.0,0.0,0.0,0,0,0,"['2022-05-09', '2022-04-11']"
415,[1963245],East Ukraine,['GPE'],1,7,0.25,0.25,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
416,[1963245],the U.K. Ministry of Defense,['ORG'],1,7,0.25,0.25,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-11']
417,[1963245],Ukrainain,['GPE'],1,7,-0.0258,0.0,-0.0258,0,1,1,['2022-04-11']
418,"[2279161, 2345105, 1998813, 2350926]",the Azov Regiment,['ORG'],1,1,-1.2972,0.0,-1.2972,0,2,2,"['2022-04-30', '2022-05-06', '2022-04-12', '2022-05-05']"
419,"[2010882, 2063107, 1998813]",Eduard Basurin,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.8808,0.0,-0.8808,0,2,2,"['2022-04-15', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13']"
420,"[2010882, 1998813]",Hanna Maliar,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.6157,0.1027,-0.7184,1,1,2,"['2022-04-12', '2022-04-13']"
421,"[1694081, 2010882, 2063107, 2333865, 2170124, 1998813, 2026013]",Vadym Boychenko,['PERSON'],1,1,-2.5758,0.0,-2.5758,0,5,5,"['2022-04-15', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-21']"
422,"[2158690, 2219618, 2224758, 2042107, 1998813, 2208607]",Mykhailo Podolyak,['PERSON'],1,1,-1.4496000000000002,0.45899999999999996,-1.9085999999999999,2,3,5,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-20', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-26']"
423,[1998813],Podolyak,['PERSON'],1,1,0.4404,0.4404,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-12']
424,"[615461, 587411, 1998813, 726571]",Liz Truss,['PERSON'],1,1,0.8052999999999999,1.2456999999999998,-0.4404,3,1,4,"['2022-03-30', '2022-04-01', '2022-04-12', '2022-03-31']"
425,"[625314, 723811, 578564, 1998813]",Australian,['NORP'],1,1,-8.3322,0.0,-8.3322,0,13,13,"['2022-04-12', '2022-03-26', '2022-03-31']"
426,"[578564, 1998813]",Marise Payne,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,"['2022-04-12', '2022-03-26']"
427,"[2010882, 1998813]",the Chemical Weapons Convention,['ORG'],1,1,-1.6585,0.0,-1.6585,0,2,2,"['2022-04-12', '2022-04-13']"
428,[1998813],Marc-Michael Blum,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.836,0.0,-0.836,0,1,1,['2022-04-12']
429,"[517355, 2242251, 1141524, 1276661, 1998813, 2208607]",Netherlands,['GPE'],1,1,-1.3902,0.831,-2.2212,3,5,8,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-03-29', '2022-04-03']"
431,[1998813],Anatoliy Fedoruk,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.4939,0.0,-0.4939,0,1,1,['2022-04-12']
432,[1998813],Shevchenkove,['GPE'],1,1,0.3182,0.3182,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-12']
433,[1998813],Peremoha,['ORG'],1,1,-0.8481,0.0,-0.8481,0,1,1,['2022-04-12']
434,[1998813],Vostochny,['GPE'],1,1,-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-04-12']
435,[1998813],Starokostiantyniv,['GPE'],1,1,-0.4588,0.0,-0.4588,0,1,1,['2022-04-12']
436,[1998813],Khmelnytskyi,['GPE'],1,1,-0.4588,0.0,-0.4588,0,1,1,['2022-04-12']
437,"[2094538, 2170124, 2026013]",Vereshchuk,"['ORG', 'GPE']",1,5,-0.7374,0.2732,-1.0106000000000002,1,2,3,"['2022-04-18', '2022-04-21', '2022-04-12']"
440,[2026013],Wells,['ORG'],1,5,3.2401999999999997,4.3774,-1.1372,10,4,14,['2022-04-12']
441,"[2355237, 1497161, 2170124, 2338356, 2026013]",Nazi,['NORP'],1,5,-2.7967,0.0,-2.7967,0,5,5,"['2022-04-05', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-21', '2022-05-09']"
442,"[2010882, 2026013]",the Associated Press,['ORG'],1,5,-0.7717,0.0,-0.7717,0,1,1,"['2022-04-12', '2022-04-13']"
443,"[1694081, 2010882, 2063107, 2333865, 2170124, 2026013]",Boychenko,"['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,5,-3.3512,0.7363999999999999,-4.0876,2,7,9,"['2022-04-15', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-13', '2022-04-07', '2022-04-21']"
444,"[1694081, 2026013]",ICRC,['ORG'],1,5,0.7896,1.2739,-0.4843,2,2,4,"['2022-04-07', '2022-04-12']"
445,"[2053825, 2158690, 2333865, 2242251, 2170124, 2350926, 2345105, 2224758, 2325276, 2026013, 2355199]",Zaporizhzhia,"['NORP', 'PERSON', 'GPE']",1,5,-0.4302,2.5028,-2.9330000000000003,5,7,12,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-19', '2022-05-04', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-12', '2022-04-21', '2022-05-03', '2022-04-27', '2022-04-16', '2022-05-06', '2022-05-08']"
446,[2026013],Berdyansk,['GPE'],1,5,1.0734,1.0734,0.0,3,0,3,['2022-04-12']
447,"[2010882, 2063107, 2114216, 2242251, 2279161]",Azov,['PERSON'],1,1,-0.5956,0.424,-1.0196,2,3,5,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-30', '2022-04-13']"
448,[2010882],the Ukrainian National Guard,['ORG'],1,1,-0.6613,0.0,-0.6613,0,1,1,['2022-04-13']
449,[2010882],Interfax,['GPE'],1,1,-0.4404,0.0,-0.4404,0,1,1,['2022-04-13']
450,[2010882],Basurin,['NORP'],1,1,-0.8402,0.0,-0.8402,0,1,1,['2022-04-13']
451,[2010882],ministry of defense,['ORG'],1,1,0.128,0.128,0.0,1,0,1,['2022-04-13']
452,"[2158690, 2242251, 2041615, 2155952, 2033521]",The Russian Defense Ministry,['ORG'],1,7,-0.3494,0.5860000000000001,-0.9354,3,2,5,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-19', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-22']"
453,"[2028224, 2053825, 2158690, 2041615, 2155952, 2033521]",Moskva,"['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE']",1,7,-7.0443,0.23070000000000002,-7.275,2,14,16,"['2022-04-23', '2022-04-15', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-22']"
454,[2033521],Snake Island,['GPE'],1,7,-0.5994,0.0,-0.5994,0,1,1,['2022-04-14']
455,"[2333865, 2242251, 2350926, 2033521, 2345105]",Maj,['PERSON'],1,7,-1.6423999999999999,0.256,-1.8983999999999999,2,3,5,"['2022-04-19', '2022-05-05', '2022-05-04', '2022-04-14', '2022-05-06']"
456,[2033521],Vadym Denysenko,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.8338,0.0,-0.8338,0,1,1,['2022-04-14']
457,[2033521],Current Time TV,['ORG'],1,7,-0.8338,0.0,-0.8338,0,1,1,['2022-04-14']
458,"[2033521, 1896851]",David Beasley,['PERSON'],1,7,0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-14', '2022-03-29']"
459,"[2033521, 1896851]",the U.N. World Food Program,['ORG'],1,7,0.34,0.34,0.0,1,0,1,"['2022-04-14', '2022-03-29']"
460,"[2053825, 2094538, 2350926, 2041615, 2033521, 2208607]",Mariupol’s,['ORG'],1,7,-4.7628,0.34,-5.102799999999999,1,7,8,"['2022-04-20', '2022-04-18', '2022-04-15', '2022-05-05', '2022-04-14', '2022-04-16']"
461,"[2033521, 2041615]",Maksym Marchenko,['PERSON'],1,7,-0.5,0.0,-0.5,0,2,2,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-15']"
462,"[2155952, 2033521]",Sevastopol,['ORG'],1,7,-0.25,0.0,-0.25,0,1,1,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-22']"
463,"[2033521, 2053825, 2041615]",Neptune,['ORG'],1,7,-0.372,0.128,-0.5,1,2,3,"['2022-04-14', '2022-04-16', '2022-04-15']"
